Welcome guys to test in Lavo this is a beginner's guide to test our applications and see how we can
use techniques like Stevensville Ogmund to make our workflow better have a fresh install of level and
I'm going to be walking you through how all of this works.
So first of all let's start by defining what testing is.
We obviously have a in and writing obligations and novel writing code and seeing those code break in
production and receiving very Arjun requests on fix this feature.
Make sure this is working on all of that.
Now Destin is going to give us a very very huge advantage when building web applications.
And one of those advantages is actually reducing the amount of box or issues that we have on that particular
application.
So imagine that pitch that you broke by maybe moving a controller or changing the name of something
and then realize that by moving this feature you broke another feature and you push your code to production
and when it gets to production you have all sorts of complains that this is broken.
Whoops there's something going on on this page.
But then what if you had a suit that you could run every time to actually test every single feature
every single method in an application before you actually push it to production such that if you have
a built in system and you change something in the billing system and it affects the use of striation
on something like that you can be able to point it out or figure it out before you push your code to
production.
That's what testing is going to do for you.
You create an application and for every single thing or feature that that application does you write
a test for that.
And before you put to production you make sure that all your tests pass I'm going to show you an example
of a test.
And obviously by default lavish gifts ph be in it as a testing framework.
So in a test directory We have a unique entry and we have a feature directory.
So what is the difference between a feature test and the unit test.
Now let's take for example we are testing the use of the PH B class and we simply want to filter the
name of the user in an array of users right.
So we're going to create a method and this method will take a name and is going to be of words they
use are ones that names like that.
Right.
So we're going to call that a unit test because we want to make sure that that method actually works
the way we want it to work.
But then let's imagine we want to make sure that our applications log in and registration system as
a whole which comprises of a lot of classes and a lot of my thoughts walks together.
Then we're going to create some feature test and in the feature test what we're doing is actually making
some posts request to that end points that is in charge of authentication to make sure that it returns
to us or displays the correct result.
But for units as we're going to be making requests to my thoughts all classes to make sure that the
attributes and the thing are the thing that they are supposed to do right.
So we have a bunch of classes right here in our testing directory and we're going to just walk through
each and every one of those for you to understand what's happening.
So first of all we have this test case the PH p.
And what does this do.
It uses creates application as a.
And then it's an abstract class and we extend the base test case.
So if we try ahead what's the best test case we see it's in the vendor level frameworks source eliminate
Fondation testing task is the piece.
So let's head over there and we see the test case that we are extending actually extends based case
right here which is PH You need framework test case.
Right.
So what you see lover doing is simply creating a little wrapper or wrong the default ph B unit framework
and you're going to see how helpful and wonderful that is.
So obviously it has a lot of concerns for example concerns that is to be request.
For example if you want to learn the API in Lavoe testing framework that takes care of asked questioning
you can just head over to that file and we head over to that treat you see that in my office my thoughts
like with Vagos without middleware.
Again I thought if we want to make get requests to an end point and get Jason want to make that an adjacent
request post and all of that.
OK we can see we also have to watch with authentication if there are three data base on all of that
we're going to be working through this.
Yeah but then what I want you concerned to be focused on now is this it extends a business case and
this business case extends PH BE unit framework.
So what I'm doing is creating a Simbu up to our own PSP in unit.
So by default you should be able to understand be in it before you actually write us to love our case.
So it uses creates application.
And what those creates application do is but the application right.
So before you're actually able to run a test cation you need to boot up the application.
So this is exactly the level of the application.
Anytime we make a request or try to visit a page.
OK so now that we have that clip we won't actually be needing to touch these two files novels taking
care of that for us.
The main things are going to be focused on are the features directory directory and how to actually
set up a test.