Let's look at an example test that will provide for us project in the feature directory we check out
the test.
And like we defined the feature tests are going to test particular features an application for example
authentication.
And in this case if we look at the first is no need to worry about all of this boilerplate.
What we have here is making a GET request to this endpoint and the notice that we are using get and
actually ph does not provide us with this method but because we are using levelness a wrapper Lavoe
has this helpful method that can help us make a GET request to an endpoint.
So we have this GET request to this end point and then we are making sure that when we make a request
to that end point we have a status of 200.
OK.
So this is a feature that's destined that visiting this point actually returns a 200.
So this method does not care about controllers.
It does not care about methods that take care of returning a view and all of that.
All he cares about is making sure that the future of visiting this page works right.
So that's a feature test.
What about a unit test a unit test.
It's going to look a little bit different and obviously right here it's not testing any method or any
class but it's not visiting any endpoint and it's not making sure that a particular status code or particular
session is set right.
So we are just searching true of true.
And this may be true of maybe the users locked in when we call a particular method or something like
that.
OK.
So how do we want to test.
Obviously like I said using ph be unique.
So for head over to my vendor bin directory you see that we have ph B unit in this directory and this
is an executable.
And once we execute that command is going to actually run all the tests in application.
Let's try the vendor bean ph B unit.
So you see we have to test that was successful and two assertions so let's go ahead and try to break
something in our future test.
What we're going to do is try to break this test.
So now when you try to visit this end point just like in the browser you have a successful response
because that is actually written in your view which is a 200.
Now how do we pick this test.
That's what or what that Ph be.
And right here we see that by default Lavoe gives us a route.
And when we visit this route it returns this view.
Right.
So let's go ahead and change this by actually making sure this end point does not exist.
Which means novel is going to an error which is a 500 instead of a 200.
So I'm just going to see nothing right here on the slash end point does not exist.
That's one that says the game to see what we get.
Vendor BHB in it and you see we have a phileo.
There was one phileo expect a status code of 200 but received 4 or 4.
Which means that endpoint does not exist and filled asserting that false is true.
Because right here we are searching in the example feature test that status of 200 is equal to 4 or
4 which is what we returned right.
So this is a feature that is not work in an application.
And a lot of things might happen.
Ms.
Let's say you're working on a team and accidentally team member actually leads the slash route and it's
no longer working.
Now you're not going to know.
But before this portal production you're going to run your tests to make sure that all your test as
you are passing and in case does not pass.
Dannion how to fix it before you push it to production.
Right.
So that's one of the greatest advantages of actually testing your code.
I'm going to fix that back run test and get back to green.
So everything is awesome.
So let's head over to our one unit test and try to break it.
So we are asserting true.
While if we assert false right.
So we are asserting that something returns true.
But then it's actually returning false.
That's one that Venda been BHB it and now we have a failure.
And this is the second test failing failed asserting that false is true.
As simple as that.
So that is exactly what we are going to be doing to create a test.
Do some stuff and assert assert innocently saying I wanted to behave in this way.
Make sure it isn't that way if not an error.
And that's the wrong way sitting right here.
So those are very busy examples of our feature and unit test.
But how do we actually create this test and naturally use them to test our application.