Let's make our first test and run it.
Now this brings me to the point where I have to tell you about test driven development not the normal
way for us to write the code is to write code then write a test and make sure the test passes and then
we push the production right.
We are going to be using a different approach which is test driven development meaning rather than words
and code and writing tests we're going to write test then we write code.
Now there is one big advantage of of involvement out of so many advantages and that advantage is that
it gives us some time to think about our code.
How do we want our applications work.
How do we want them with features to work and how do we want our code to be organized.
Right.
That is one of the biggest advantages test humans are in is going to give to you.
Sometimes they sit in front of computer and for a very long time I cannot write any single line of code.
Why because I'm thinking about how to write my next test if I don't think about how to write my test
I'm not writing in a line of code and that's just one of the greatest advantages that Trumans of them
and is going to give to you.
There are a lot of advantages but we're going to be learning them as we go along do we.
So how do we use this idea of test driven development.
Let's go ahead and check it out.
So in our Web page we found we have this end point which is the home page and it returns this view.
Let's just see what clann wants on about page.
And when you visit about page you just see a big about page on The View.
Let's go ahead and create a test.
And this is going to be a feature.
That's right because we don't care about how it's connected to control us or if it's using closures
but we just want an about Beach and that a boat should display about me on The View.
So let's go ahead and create a test.
And obviously Lavoe as awesome as it is has to help with this.
So ph be our son make test and this test is going to be about Bache test.
Now there are two options we have here.
We are creating a unique test or we are creating a feature test kitchen of each It's us with Lavo.
This is the common but if you're in a unit you just need to pass in unit right here and that's going
to created in the unit directory.
So not interested in a future test.
Let's go ahead and one that the test that's been created for us about Bache dust.
Now I'm going to clean up this boiler plate and we're going to take care of it ourselves.
How would our test look.
First thing about writing test that a lot a lot of ways of writing your test for PH be to recognize
that there are tests and I try them but we're going to go with the simplest.
So public function and it's the way lover does it.
So if you check in DUMBO test it starts every test with the test keyword and then it gives a description
of what the test does.
And then it does this thing within.
So let's go ahead.
What about Beach test and do that public function.
And we're just stuck with test.
And then we can write a description about that.
So tests can view about Ph.
Now we have this set up if we want it it's not going to actually do anything.
So we need to do something assert something and then run a test right.
So how do we want this to work.
Basically we want a user to visit a Ph.
So what's the response.
Because this and you visit a page by making a get request right and we want you to visit the about page
and Wendy's the about Ph.
We're going to see response as search stutterers 200.
Right.
So we want to make sure that when you use of this is this route catalyses the status of 200.
So it means he was successful and he saw a reasonable ph.
So we can also run another assertion and the assertion we're going to be in is respon assert.
See about me.
So when they use this route we are making sure that he's successful and we also making sure that he
actually sees this piece of text which is about me.
So this is all about testing.
This is how we want applications to work.
We haven't written any code but then we have the basic skeleton.
So in order for us to run the stairs I'm just going to delete this basic test.
Call me labo.
Because we don't need them and we're going to focus on this one.
So let's head over to our army now and run that test.
And you're going to see this a lot when you're doing test driven development.
You write a test.
You know it's going to fail.
But then you still run it from the errors that you have to really make those errors go away and continue
doing this till the test passes.
Then at that point you refactor your code to make it better.
OK.
So let's run this and see what we get.
And one phileo expected status of twanged but received a 4.
0 4.
And we know a 4 or 4 is not found exception meaning we didn't actually see the about rods.
Right now I'm going to tweak something a little and that's in my OP exceptions hand-lettered ph B.
And what this class does is actually handles the exceptions in lover.
Let's look at this random thought.
So when there's an exception to an AGP response and that's because for example if you try to visit the
about routes now in our Vasa we don't receive an exception we are actually receiving an S2P response
which is a page telling us to everyone that we're strong right now.
What level does is when an exception is when in the application of that exception and then it tries
to render it into a page that is beautiful so we can see it.
So what we're going to do here before I go refunds and S2P ph.
We're going to fill that exception again.
Right.
So we catch the exception that has been done before it's looking such that we'll be able to see the
exception itself.
And this is going to actually cause a hassle because if we refresh now the page is not working because
that exceptionally strong and the Vaso doesn't know what to do with that exception.
Now even though the boss doesn't know what to do with it it's really going to help us in access because
if we run this now you can see right here we have not found S2P exception which is helpful rather than
saying that we failed to assert a 4 0 4 2 0 2.
OK.
So that's how we can actually talk exceptions and see them in our terminal when we are running our tests.
So this is completely novel.
Don't convert this joint S2P page just yet.
I want to use the exception so for it and that's a retweet.
So how do we fix and not phone SATB exception.
Very simple we just need to create a route.
Right.
So let's have the virtue of what that ph be and where we're going to create a Roths which is going to
be a gets and it's going to go to the slosh about let's just passing closer right here.
I'm gonna run this again.
And now we have Phil asserting that an empty stream contains about me because disclosure doesn't return
anything.
Therefore it is an empty string.
And then we are failing to answer that he contains about me.
If we are receiving this error it means that we actually passed the first Test in our code by returning
a status of 200 right because we are not returning anything.
He just gets a 200 and then we are not seen about me on the pitch.
Now remember this is an approach that shows return the string about me and see what we get.
So we are trying as much as possible to fix this test and then when we fix the test if it passes we're
going to try to refactor our courts.
Actually the way we want it to behave.
So we have written about me here.
Let's run the test again.
And now we are successful.
Why.
Because we have about me right here.
But then let's have a of refresh and we have a what about me checks wider Outlander is seen.
But wait I don't want to bug me as a string.
I want a beautiful page with about me in the page and all of that.
So how are we going to do this.
This is what we call the refactoring step right.
We want to actually make the courts will find a way we want it to work.
So how about returning a view.
So let's go ahead and return a view rather than returning a bobby and begin to return the about view.
So what above you doesn't exist.
But after every single refactor all the best way to do is actually run your test to know what is breaking
and what you've done.
So right here we have the view about not found and we can fix that error by simply heading over our
resources tree view and then creating that new view.
So I'm just going to call these about the blade.
Now we have that view.
Let's go ahead and run a test a game and then we have failed our search engine the MC machine contains
about me.
Obviously the views empty right.
So if we had to watch our Basar it's empty.
So what we're going to do is actually just write about me in the view and see if one ancestor game and
we have a passing test again right.
We return we refresh and then we you have about me which means a testis passing but then we don't still
one this right.
We want a view and we make sure that this test isn't it.
So I'm just going to copy everything in my work on the blade to be pasted right there and I'm just going
to remove all of these things.
We don't need them and the for one at SEST right now we're going to fill to assert that all of this
is Jimoh in the page contains about me.
That's why we have the top field as such and that all of the demo contains about me.
So somewhere somehow in our code court we have to Acourt about me for this test to pass.
So let's go ahead and cole about me right here safe and let's run a test again and we have a test passing
again.
And let's refresh our browser and there we have it.
We have about me now.
It's been a long while to actually write this simple simple very basic amount of code right.
So we have a lot of fires fires one a lot of test as such that a lot of stuff just because we want to
Creedon about the blade the HP and put in something about me to extend it right.
Yeah but then as I walked you through the simple steps that we need to take before buten a future obligation.
Right and it's actually a lot helpful when you build the application in this way because let's say you
want a ship to put action on a team mates things are not good enough.
Let's change this to about us.
So when you run your test again now it feels so before you push on you know it feels and you know why
it feels now because it tells you that a body takes is not included.
So you can either choose to now into this future your application by simply changing the test to make
sure that it sees about us.
And when you run it you have a successful test or you can tell the thing that we want to stick to about
me so make sure that the test procedure is the same way it works.
So that's a very very brief example of using students with a mentor to really accomplish stuff and not
just sleep in day to day life we're going to have more complex stuff to take care of but this is going
to give you a really good footing.