You might not know it but you're ready for me to actually put the big stuff at you.
For example a full blown application or something like that.
So let's go ahead and jump right into it.
I'm going to use a very basic example and that's going to be creating a block.
And I'm just using a blog because everybody knows what a blog is and how it works.
So it's just going to be very busy.
A user visits a page he sees some blog posts with the Dade's on the title and all of that and an administrator
can also create deletes or stuff like that.
OK so how do we work on this how do we make it come to life.
We're going to be using Jelf tester in development because we want to think about how our code works
before we write the code right.
So what is the first test or what is the first feature we want to build.
Do we start with nothing.
Occasion we start with creating posts do we start deleting post or do we start with returning views.
What do we actually start with now.
First of all from my experience that we have to take care of is actually making sure we start with a
simple feature test a feature test that is going to guide us to how our application wants to work for
the user rather than for us.
OK.
Because remember uniters is naturally for us because we want to check if our classes and methods work
perfectly but then feature its for us.
Yeah but then it somehow has to do with how the user interacts with application.
So the basic rule of thumb is write a feature test for us and then in writing the feature test in case
you have some methods to test write unit test to test those features right.
So for example for BLOCK What is the very first feature we would want to create in a blog post but then
that some of the essential of actually creating a block.
So if we check out a blog The main thing in a blog is viewing a post and thats the core of a block.
Now creating post we could do creates imposing any manner.
For example user can just goods of the deeds of his audience or the post or do whatever he likes a person
away from the controller just to display it.
So that's my obligation.
So the basic rule of thumb is the core of your application should be where you start.
So if you're building maybe a school learning management system and the first thing is for us to be
able to view students or that's the main post and quit that feature first authentication will come in
later.
That's because you once a week for people to be able to create post and it'll come in later.
Right.
So we're going to be using this idea of Desdunes of government to actually create a blog post.
So from what we've talked about what is the first that we are going to be creating We're going to be
making sure that a user can view a blog post.
Right.
So let's go ahead and create a test for that.
PH BE areason make test view a blackboard test just create it for us.
Therefore if we head over to our feature directory and if we have that test a cloud of boilerplate and
we're going to write our own function public function test can view a block post so our users should
be able to view a blog post right.
So it's just going to have literally exactly the same idea like we had with our about Bache.
So first of all we need to visit that route a route where we want our users to view our blog posts and
then begin to assert that we have a status of 200 and we're going to assert that the beats are on that
page is actually the data that we want to see.
OK.
There are actually steps involved in every test and some test might actually not have these steps but
then basically every test you're going to see is going to have these steps and the first one is going
to be arrangements step which is the step in which you prepare your data base stuff that has to be taken
care of before you run your test.
And then we also have the actual step which is going to be taking care of and that's just a reaction
that we are trying to perform dysfunctionality and then we're going to have to assert step.
So if you take a look at that about PH We actually didn't have any arrangements because we didn't win
anything.
We just went ahead and made an action.
And after that action we had our asserts and that is how I put a space right here just to demonstrate
that this is a different step from this one.
So this is the action step and this is the assertion step.
So for our test we're going to be having all three steps and we're going to start with the arrangements.
And then we're going to go to the actual stuff and then we're going to go to that assertion step.
So for the arrangements what do we want our age.
The first thing is we actually want to be able to have some post-white a user cannot view a post that
doesn't exist.
So in the rangemaster we are going to create a post savey to the database for what actions we are going
to navigate to a route that we want to view all the post on and then follow our search.
We're going to assert that the status 200 which means the page exists.
And also I said that the title or the body or the content or the creator for the particular post is
actually on that page.
So let's go ahead and take care of this in the very next video.