We ended up having to speak up and we agreed that we're going to be creating a book post right here.
And then from our actions we are going to be visiting a route and then for our search step we're going
to assert stutterers code 200 which means we actually found that beach and also assert that we see post-Idol
because that's what we actually have to see on the page that is viewing the post and then assert that
we see Post body.
And let's just so that we see published data.
So let's take care of this for arrangements.
We need to create a post right.
This is what does driven development comes exciting right.
So how are we going to write create a blog post.
We don't have any migrations.
We don't have any post table.
We don't have anything.
How do we create a blog post in Lavo if you want to create a blog post.
So we're going to have maybe a post tomorrow and you're going to call or create a thought on that tomorrow
and discrete mathematics and an array of the data that we want to create.
Right.
So this is where we have to really have to decide what is going to have to be on a report table.
Notice how it has to make us think we have no other option member actually creating a migration.
I think what tables after the migration and all of that but right now we have to think about what feuds
are going to be in our database table.
So for us we we're going to have a title and I'm just going to see a simple title.
It's going to be the title we're passing in and we must have a body and we're going to see a simple
body.
And we're just going to leave it at that.
We have a title we have a body a simple title a simple body for our post.
So the auction is actually visiting a route right.
So let's visit a route we're going to see a response like we always see if the response this.
And we tried to visit a beach using a get.
And I'm just going to say visit Borst and we want to view a particular post right.
So we are going to pass in the idea of this post right here.
So I'm just going to add a dot right here and just say post I.D. or if you not be more flexible we can
pass this in double quotes post and slash post ID right here.
OK.
So we're just in an end point which takes in a parameter and that parameter is the idea of the post
that we're trying to view.
And then we need to make some assertions on what we expect.
Right.
So I assert that we have a squad of 200.
We're going to see response.
So it's that's years of 200.
No I say that we see the post title response assert.
See the post title right.
So we can just call post title like your supposed title.
I assert that we see the post-Bali it's going to be exactly something like this.
And this is going to be Buddy.
And then I said that we see published date.
Now obviously when we automatically create a post we have created a timestamp for this which is going
to give us the date that it was created.
Right.
So right here at the bottom we're going to assert that we actually see that time.
So asserts C and we're just going to pass in a post created just for now.
OK so that is our test.
We are saying create a post visit aroud.
I said that we have that word.
I said that we see that title.
So now we see that body.
And so we see that created the timestamp on that page.
OK.
So let's run this.
And we haven't ever seen feature post.
Not fun.
Now this is where it gets exciting.
We have a test and we need to fix each and every one of these arrows down to the last beat where everything
works perfectly right.
So how are we going to fix this feature.
It's not fun it's saying this glass does not exist.
So let's put that last and we didn't know we are using this as a model.
So we're going to use Lovells.
PH We asked Uncle man to help us see our son make model and it's going to be post model created successfully.
So after taking a little action we were not digging and we still have that we're seeing says future
post not found.
But then we know that the Adari tree exists.
But then why is it still telling us it's not fun obviously because we haven't imported it.
Right.
So let's just use our post right here.
Let's run our test again after taking that action to fix.
And we have a different error seen mass assignment exception for title.
So we are much assigning these data into our model and level automatically protects the database from
that.
So how do we fix this.
We can create a protected fillable property to specify the database entries that should be must assignable
or we could just tell Lovelle that we don't want any more assignment for any field by passing in an
empty array to the godat property.
OK so this has no risk at all.
You cannot do this in your production applications.
Most of the time you're not going to face the risk of mass assignment.
So let's run this again.
Now we have another arrow saying eliminate database quivery exception access denied for home at Lucar
host the com password Yes.
Now what is happening.
Remember the creative method actually Tresor safe or post into a database.
We don't have a database set up we haven't set up any databases so it receives that error that we cannot
assess homestead.
So that is a way to save this or to fix this is to head over the energy file and set up our database
configurations.
So right here for a database I have a database set up for testing and Lavoe and my user name is rude.
And my password is nothing.
So Setubal your database.
Let's run this test again.
And now we have an ever saying base table of view not Faolan testing Lavo that post.
So it was successfully able to access that database but then we tried to save this to the post-IPO but
it didn't find the post table.
So how do we fix this.
Let's simply use BHB arrest and make migration.
And this is going to be create more stable and just help or we can pass and create equal post to that
command.
So we've created our migration.
Let's run that test again.
And then we still have that it was seen the best of all of you not found.
And that's because we haven't migrated to a data base right now.
We can migrate our database right here by calling access on call and we can call the migrate common
right Lavoe gives us the possibility of migrating using the axon command right here.
But level always gives us a very easy way of wanting our migrations before our tests.
And that is simply by using this database migrations test so use database migration.
So if we try to get the database migrations file which is in our interest in that BHB we'll see what
it does.
It causes one database migrations my thought and what this method does is it made with a database and
after everything is destroyed before the application is destroyed.
I was setting up Kishan.
It was about the migration as simple as that.
So you see it does exactly the same thing but just by using this trait level he's going to do everything
for us.
OK.
So that run the command again and then we have unknown column title field list.
So it's trying to create a post using the title and the body but then it's seen the column is known.
So let's head over to a quick post to my question and obviously we are migrating to the data base but
we don't have a title.
So let's see if it's right or I see a string field and name is going to be title I save that remember
I'm trying to fix just the error I just got.
I wonder again and then we haven't seen a column buddy so let's fix that by creating a text field.
And this is going to be buddy.
So let's run that again.
And here we have not found S2P exception.
That's because if we had a all our best we have title we have buddy and then we're trying to make a
get request a route that does not exist.
So we've successfully taken care of this part of our application and at the end of one in this test
and gets into this step we have a model for positive role.
We have a migration for our post-IPO knifing is giving us a lot of structure in our application.
So let's go ahead and continue doing this in the next episode.