We ended up with having this not fun.
S2P exception error.
And that's because in our test rich range you get this right.
But then it doesn't exist.
So how do we fix a not fun Espey exception error simple right creating that Grotz right.
So in a way that Ph be.
We're going to create a new route down here and this is going to be a GET request because that's what
we want to assess and it's to the slush post slash idea and point where the ID is a parameter and we
have two choices right here.
We could actually use a clue just because we want the code to work or we could actually write the code
the way we want it to and by creating a controller and all of that but to keep it simple I'm just going
to pass in a closure right here and let's run that again.
And we have Phil our in an M G string contains a simple title.
Right.
Because we are creating the post.
Never get into that about with the ID of that post and expecting to see that try to see that body and
see that creates a feud right.
So how do we fix this.
We have the ID of the post that we are trying to assess right here right.
So what if we get that post and then return that data it's going to fix this error obviously.
So we're going to see a post equals Post find using the ID that was passed in as a parameter which we
obviously have to collect twice here and then return post title and see what we get.
So that's one that says again and we have an error seen plus post not found.
Let's go ahead and fix that by simply writing post right.
So specifying the namespace for that class run the test again.
And now we have a simple title contains a simple body so field searching that this text that we receive
contains this.
Right.
So the easiest way to fix that is to have a view and then that view is going to contains Konting all
of that data.
Right.
So let's go ahead and try to fix this by returning a view.
We're going to call this view post.
But blader BHB and we just need to pass in the post right.
So we boast boast.
Simple right.
So that's one test.
And then we haven't ever seen the view post cannot be found.
Let's head down and try to create that in our resource view newfound Bolstad blade that pitch be real
not just a game for a search engine and enter a string contains a simple title which is this spatial
IKYA.
So I'm just going to quote the post title I quote the post and run tests again Field asserting that
the post now contains a simple body.
So we just need to call the body.
That's not just a game and then we have this error that is being run by PH framework exception and it
says A certain things first permits or must be a string Bohdan.
It looks like we are passing in a string but we actually are not passing in the string like we are passing
in an instance of carbon which is scallawag a class.
So so for us to fix this we're just going to use two form outside dead string right here and this is
simply a method that is going to take this instance of carbon and convert it to a string in a better
or beautiful format right.
So that's one that says again.
And then we have filled a search in that the body actually contains this so we can see that this detail
is nicely formatted.
But then it's not in the view so let's go ahead of you and cole the final piece of data our post creates
and we convert these two formats.
Did string Arcel so hopefully our test should finally passed right now.
Because we've actually reached the last line and we have a successful test.
Finally right.
So using that idea of test driven development we've been able to test drive our first feature and that
feature is a user actually being able to create a post into the database.