Access to this person successfully but it's not really application friendly it's not going to kill well.
When we start building and adding more features for example in the web the HP we have closer's right
here.
And what if we had to perform like 15 auctions before actually returning a view what were we going to
do in that case.
So what are going to be doing is simply refactoring this code to a controller.
And remember our refactoring says we're just going to refactor all sets and make sure that we still
get green at the end of everything.
All right.
So I'm going to stretch this out with a pulse Quantrell on that.
I wan to exist which doesn't exist yet and this is going to be the index method which is going to take
care of returning a post to us.
Right.
So let's run our test now and see what we get.
And we have an error post control that does not exist.
Let's create a controller BHP Arsen mic control control controller created.
Let's run not just again.
And then we haven't ever seen the method index does not exist.
That's how the rods or to create the index method.
Not test again and then we have filled such in an empty string contains a symbol to Ardo.
We've gone to this level and we know how to fix it.
We just need to find the post and return the view with the data.
Right.
So I'm just going to use the post class right here and then right here I can just return a view and
this view is opposed.
And this is with post and I'm going to find a post in here using the ID that was passed on the vision
we need to receive that ID right.
OK.
So find a post which have you read that post data.
That's one test.
Now we're done with our refactoring.
Hopefully everything works perfectly as it used to do before we started refactor.
OK perfect.
Everything works good enough.