Looking at the code right now it looks pretty unknown.
But then what happens when a user tries to visit a route that does not exist.
For example passing in an ID of a post that doesn't exist.
We don't want to just ban an error message in production right.
So that's why this is a good test of this.
So will your view of block post test and Reagan to write a new test and this is going to be a public
function test views or for for speech when post.
It's not fun when the post is not found we want to view of four or four page.
So let's take care of that.
First of all we need to take care of all of our interests and our actions.
And obviously with our search staff but for our rings I think we want to visit a post that does not
exist and then assert that the status is forceful and also so that we see a particular type of string
on our screen our Ahrendts terp is not really going to cut the deal right here because we have nothing
to avenge for our actions.
We're going to be visiting about that does not exist or rather exist with the wrong parameters.
And then for us to assert that we have a fall or fall so that we see some sort of takes on the screen.
So for action step we're going to see a response because this gets and we're going to go to the post
and point slash and we're going to see invalid ID right here.
OK.
Because this I.D. does not exist.
And then for assertions they're going to assert that the status of that request was a form of fraud.
So a substitute is a 4 0 4.
And we're also going to assert that we have a text that is displayed.
So we're going to see a search see the page you are looking for cannot be found.
So we have asked how do we want it.
So this brings us back to the idea of literally running our test we could actually run it the way we've
been running.
But then as you see as application Those are tests increase and we could have hundreds of tests at the
end of this exercise.
So we're going to introduce a very simple way to run our tests and that's going to be using groups and
it provides us with a lot a lot of ways to run the test.
And so I'm just going to use the easiest possible if we want to run only this particular test to see
if it works because we already know this one works.
Then what we could do is pass a good break here and we're just going to call these posts not fun.
So when we to come on we're going to pass in a good option and this is going to one only test that have
that particular group.
So let's get our heads or termino on one that Venda ph B unit and then begin to see who should be most
not found.
And now we have only that test running.
If you look at the top we have only one test and we have an error exception trying to get property of
an object in the post that bleed the PH P.
Right.
But this is not what we want.
Remember when you visit this route is going to still retain that view even if it doesn't find the post.
Right.
They're getting the trying to get parts of object because the law is returned to our view and this is
what we want to fix.
Right.
We want this to pass.
So the very simple way to fix this is to make sure that our controller pulls an exception when the post
is not found.
So I'm just going to cut this out and pass in a verbal portion right here and post two posts.
Fine.
But then we're not going to be using the find method anymore.
We're going to be using the fine of failed methods that level provides for us.
And this line of feel mid-thought is not for an exception if the post is not found.
It's not going to return to the view so let's run the test again.
And here we can see no results for be opposed invalid ID.
So model not found exception has been torn from us.
So this is the exception that we want to try and cut right here.
And if we catch that exception we're going to be 24:4 ph rather than a post ph.
So let's wrap this in a try catch block and then catch and we're going to be catching the illuminates
database eloquent moment found exception.
So which would be exactly what we have here.
The Queen Mother non-fun exception was this exception any time he doesn't find that database record
using the final fill method.
OK.
So what do we want to happen when we catch this exception.
We are simply going to see return of view which is to fall or fall that need to be and we're going to
be setting that up.
So let's run that test again and see what we have the view for for not found so far.
And I'm just going to create a forum for the lead ph be.
Let's run that again.
Now we received this.
Ever seen that we expected for 200 obviously because actually returning a fall for the lady is a successful
response.
Right.
So how do we convert this to a failed response with Lavoe writes us with a very helpful abought method
and what it does here is it's returns an ESPY responds with a particular message.
So we are seeing the return of forward response and the message right here is just going to be not fun
for example.
Right.
Let's run this and see what we get.
I'm sorry I needed to pull out this piece of code right here obviously so that this method can run right.
So let's run that again.
Now why are we receiving a not fun exception.
This is because Tesla receives the stutterers code and then it tries to respond by returning a four
or four page with the arrow.
So the 4:4 picture that it looks for is in a directory in the views right.
So it goes to the views and doesn't every tree and looks 24:4 for that data.
But then we don't have one.
That's why it's seen the page cannot be found.
So let's go ahead and try to fix this by creating our errors directory and then moving this fall further
into that fire.
OK done.
Most of for the better screen my air was a tree everything should wall everything should work perfectly
right now.
So let's check it out.
One that's asked how you receive exactly the same error.
Now why is this an open letter ph.
B We have to find that exception again means Lavo actually does not have a way to turn that into an
STV response.
Therefore when that gets in that view.
So I'm just going to commend this and then I'll run that.
And now we haven't ever seen for such an empty string contains the pitch you are looking for cannot
be found.
Now this makes more sense.
And remember we are simply an exception so that we have more help for I was forced to be able to work
with.
It's not a necessity at all for testing so you can't actually send it to production.
If not a lot of stuff are going to break.
OK so now for that we all we need to do is actually make sure we have this sentence in our view right
so it works.
So I'm just going to copy this plea from this page pasted right here.
The links.
I don't need that.
And to be exact.
I'm going ahead of to my view a blog post and then I'm going to copy this sentence head over to my full
4 and replace the lovely sentence with this.
Run my test again and now we have a successful response.