Now let's run our first unit test and I'll be able to view blog posts if he visits the Coreg route like
this.
But then imagine displaying the creator that field fodder for the particular post.
Every single time I'm using this long method so what are you going to do is write a unit test that is
going to abstract this to a method that we can just call Creator or something like that.
OK so we're going to have post created or we can call these creators art or whatever.
And this is going to actually give us a little bit of flexibility on this complex way of writing this.
OK.
So let's go ahead and create a unit test so ph we are sun make test and this is going to be post test.
And like we said if it's a unit test we need to pass in the unit floc And now we are quits in a unit
test because everything works well in our feature but we want to give ourselves an easier way to display
the dates rather than using such long my thoughts.
That's why I was in the test.
So we have our post-test and I'm just going to clean up this boiler plate and create mine public function
test and we're going to seek and get created formats formatted dates.
So what do we do for what sustain for us.
We need to arrange some stuff right and then act and then assert.
So what do we do.
Instead we just create a post and then for X or we get the value by calling the method and then for
assert we assert that returned value is us we expect.
A member of a unit to sell posters the functionality of a particular method or class.
So we are going to be calling them method and making sure that it returns what we wanted to return.
Let's create a post for creating a post.
I'm just going to head over to my view a blog post and copy what I have here based study.
Now I have a post.
Let me just use a post at the top and then after regional push we need to act right and our action is
get the value by calling a method and the value we want to get is from outside that is equal to post
and we call Creator that as a method an issue returns unto us formatted date and then we assert these
are Surt equals.
We're supposed to be unit Methot and we're going to assert that the date that was written from here
is actually as we expected.
So the date we expect is what we have in our view right now which is this.
So I'm just going to grab that copy and then head of our page study and then make sure that it's required
to format that date.
So we make sure that this value actually equals the formats that date method.
So we are trying to make sure that our formatted method actually returns exactly what we wanted to return.
So let's go ahead and give this method a group so we can run it individually.
So hope is going to be formatted dates.
That's how much I mean on one that four months date is going to be a group that's run that test.
And best of all you're not found posts.
That's because we don't use our migration.
Let's go ahead and use it.
Use database migrations.
Run the game and we have called on the find method creator.
And what happens is it's saying it can find it in the query builder class but we actually are calling
it on the post instance because the posting's stands extends the middle class and the model also extends
a class.
And so Lavoe checks if this methodes is on the post class.
If it's not it checks on the model and then if it's not also checks on the builder and they can find
it.
So he tells us that method does not exist.
So let's head over to a post that Ph.D. and create that thought public function creator that run it
again and right here we have field assets all marches expected.
June 30th 17.
So what are we going to do right here is simply return exactly the same thing we have in our view right.
Because this is what we want.
So return this.
And obviously we're going to be changing this to this and put in a coma right there.
And this mythology is going to help us return the pretty format's date.
Let's run that again and sure enough we have a successful test.
But now in our view we don't need to write all of this when we are trying to get the created a date.
We just need to write this method.
So it looks neater.
You call a creative method.
It formats that for you and returns you the result.
Right.
And we've been able to drive that functionality using a unit test.
So also now you're going to find a lot of use cases for actually writing unit tests for your models
because you don't want to have a lot of complicated stuff.
Let's say you want to have a method that returns the full name of a user by concatenating the first
name and the last name.
You don't want to concatenate the first name and the last name every time in your views.
But what you want to do is actually create a method on your model.
Or you can also create a level attribute on SSR which uses a little bit of labo magic make sure that
when you call that mid-thought or attribute or assets or it returns to you the expected value.
And then once your test passes on that class you can be able to use it any way you put it Puddock.