One little thing I want to talk about is the database we are using right now we are using my skill for
our test.
And that's not the best choice for our test because it takes some time for us structurally safe a record
to our database which is on the hard disk.
And then we try that data before our test is completed.
So if I run a test shoot right now everything we can see it takes almost six seconds to run.
But then what I'm going to do is actually switch up switch to a data base that we are using for a test
and I'm going to use my skill light.
So first of all let me just create a Maskil like database and I'm just going to college testing that.
Q All right.
And I'm going to see it in my database directory.
So touch database slash Destino that's going right.
And sure enough in the what is the real tree.
We should have testing that skill like created for us.
Now how do we tol'able to use unless it's a beast which is much lighter much faster than my skill because
it works in memory rather than using the default that it's using.
So how do we tell Lavoe to actually use a secure light which is much faster and better for testing rather
than using my skill.
Let's head over to our database the Ph.D. and right here let's check out our connections.
We have the Escola connection which is database or that's called like we change the connection to testing
that's light and the mice go connection is already set.
So we're going to be telling the HP unit in particular to use this database connection rather than using
this one.
So let's go to HP unit ex-MIL.
And what are we going to do right here is create a new environment variable and this file is simply
a configuration for PH P unit.
So a lot of boilerplate is putting right here for us by Lavo.
But let's not really care about that.
Let's just go ahead and create an environment variable that is going to set the database to use so G-B
connection like we said we want to use a secure line for testing.
And the last thing we need to pass it is D-B database and we're going to see the database should be
in memory.
So that's it for configuration.
Let's try now to run our test and we can see the amount of speed that we gain just by changing our database
driver.
So first of all we were using my skill connection if I change this to my skill and cut this out we can
see that it took almost four seconds.
It took more than four seconds to actually run our test.
But if I change this much as light and use an in-memory database we can see the amount of time that
is saved.
So it's really really fast.
The difference is outstanding.
And by the time you're writing applications that have about 100 to 200 test this is going to really
be very helpful because you don't want to send your code to a developer and he takes hours upon hours
to test your code.
OK.
So this is as it's not even after half a second and it's perfect for testing.