More than six or seven episodes ago we are able to actually complete the view a blog post test birth
we've been doing a little bit of Refractories making our test bed time making our controllers and doing
all of that stuff and we haven't created a new feature so we're going to create a new feature and move
on with application next feature we're going to be taking care of is viewing our blog post for application.
So actually our son makes us view our blog post test so we have a feature test.
Clean up the boilerplate.
A As public function test can view our blog posts and we have a little bit of steps to take care of.
So first of all I arranged our action and then assert.
So what are we going to be doing instead.
We're going to be imposed and will quit more than one.
And for action step we're going to be visiting a particular route and we'll make sure you know search
step that we view all of those posts on that page.
OK.
The rats that we visit in are action stuff.
So first of all let's create some post.
Post one is going to be factually and create my thought on the post class.
Sure enough we need to import this as just import it use up post right here.
OK.
So that's our range.
But we said we want to quit.
All right so let's just create a second post.
And sure enough the fracture my thought i truly dig in the name of Paul.
We want to generate.
But then we want also assert using this data.
So we are going to separate them into two separate post.
So on the X10 we're just going to see response equals this gets lost.
And this is the end point where we are going to be displaying all the post or user and then for our
search to assert that the response was actually successful.
So I search stutterers of 200 and then I searched also that we see that data on the page so our search
see and what we're going to be seeing.
We're going to be seeing post one title and a push to title.
So what about the content of the post.
We're going to be asserting that we actually have part of the content of the post on the page.
So we're going to be seen as Surtsey string limits which is a novel method and we're going to be passing
the post buddy rider.
OK.
So we're going to be also doing that too because we don't want to display all the post data on the page
right.
So we just wanted to assert that the user can see the first 100 US which is the default value for this
method on the page.
So I said that this was 200.
I said we see the title I said we see the title of the second post I said that we see part of the body
of the first part of the body of the second and we can also assert that we see the data.
But we're just going to skip on that.
OK so we have our test set.
Let's give it a go.
So a group is going to be Bowse that's one that is not you know from the past in a group of posts.
And we have this or no such table post let's just go ahead and use that is migration street Magwitch
our database for us run our test again and we have expected to receive four or four remember in our
hndler we just about the exception.
But then it's OK now we know what this means.
It's not finished.
Exception.
So let's head over to our Web BHB and create the endpoints show route slash posts and rather than passing
in occlusal.
I'm just going to pass in the controller that we want to use art dimethyl that we want to use for sure
our post is the that I want to use.
That's one that and received 500.
Okay.
Actually walking without the exception is not really helpful because we just received in the S2P response
that level provided in the rendah method.
So I moved it.
Now I have the exception it's been fun for us.
That's one that now we have a more helpful method method showboats does not exist.
Let's head over to our post Consuela and created my thought public function.
Sure all polls run tests again.
I sat in on an empty string contains the title right here.
So we just need to return something right.
So we are trying to return the post from our database.
So let's simply return a view which is to post the data.
PH We and with post.
And we'll just say post or let's run that and we have this ever seen the view post that's not been found.
Let's head over to our resources directory views and create a new post that lead the pitch be run the
test again and we have fill in that empty contains this.
So we still have nothing in this view.
Now we want to display all of the post right.
So we're going to use an A for each loop and we're going to see for each post I suppose.
And for each we just echoed the post-Idol.
Let's run again.
And then we have fruit asserting that this contains this.
And this tweet datcha actually tell us that that's the Lovell's limit function that is working which
means we have to Al-Quada content.
Right.
So we're just going to say post buddy and we're going to rub this in a string limit function.
Let's run that again.
And right now we have a successful test.
Now we can actually display all the polls that we have in our databased view.
You can obviously go ahead and actually did this so we have something prettier.
But I'm just going to leave this on to you and make sure if you're refractory into a more beautiful
view just like we did in the about a bid that PH BE YOU make sure everything in your suit passes.
So finally let's want everything in a test to make sure everything is working and we have this same
basic not found in the test veers off of our page when push is not found.
And obviously that's because in our handler we still have this on.
Let's run the test again and we have a successful search.