Let's give the user a possibility to create a post.
So we're going to be creating a new feature and this feature is going to be create post test.
So it's all a test feature directory and sure enough we have to create post-Castro either.
In other words a page create a function public function test can create portes.
OK.
Now how do we test that a user can create opposed to first of all Instead it's not really going to have
a lot to do but we're going to have an actual start.
Assert obviously now our actions step Regnum making a post request to our application to a particular
endpoint with some data and we're going to assert that the database has based data.
Are we going to be asserting that that post actually exists that contains that data.
Ok so first of all we need to make a post request right so response equals this post to an endpoint.
So let's just see it goes to the store post and point and then we're going to pass in as data for the
crest.
We're going to pass in its title which is going to be noon post title and we're going to pass in a body
also which is going to be noon post buddy.
OK.
So how do we assert that the database contains something we simply called this I said database hahs
which is a re use for my father level pro-rights force.
So for us to see this method as you said who interacts with database which is in our foundation testing
concerns directly and we can see the assert database Highsmith and why do checks in the table the table
we are trying to check.
Fixing the real data breach on the check that exists in that table and then you'd reach Astro falls
depending on what the result of that check is.
So right here we're going to be checking into a stable and we're going to proceed in exactly the same
way that we passed in right here.
So we are making sure that these data actually exist in the database.
OK.
Now this test might be enough but then there's another extra step that we can go right.
So what we can do is find the first post in our database with ID of one because remember our database
is going to be cleaned and this is going to be the very first post that is created for this test.
And then we're going to assert equals new title right here should be equal to the post title that we
got.
Obviously it is supposed to be equal to you.
And then we're also going to assert that the body's also equal.
OK.
So new posts buddy should be close to the post buddy.
Awesome.
So we have a number of assertions just a little bit of security for our database to make sure that this
is actually doing what we wanted to do.
OK.
So let's run this test credit.
And this is just going to be Crit. Boston Globe.
Let's run that test and it's going to give us a nasty Aeros saying we should use this database migration
straight.
So let's just use it.
Awesome.
Let's run that test and passing a group create post and we have filled a search in a row in the table
matches the attributes this and this.
The table is empty.
We're making progress to that end point and we've not done anything to assert that it contains the data.
Now I not even a more helpful metaphor to tell us that this does not exist because no handler when it's
just temporarily for the exception so we can have useful data.
Now we have not finished the exception better.
So let's head over to our Web BHB and create that exception.
So I'm just going to see routes get.
And this is just going to be to the slushed topples route.
Just like we defined right here and also we need to decide what controller we are going to be using
for this right.
So I'm just going to stick with a pulse controller for now and I'm just going to say use the soap post
method.
Awesome.
Let's run as a game where you have a non-menthol not allow the exception.
That's my fault because this is supposed to be a post request.
Sorry about that.
Let's run again.
We have this ever seen the methods of of the Sun exists that's said What's or post control are and create
that method.
Run the test again.
And now we have failed asserting that it contains that data in the database.
So what do we need to do we just need to create the data right.
So we're just going to see post equals post creates when we're passing a title which is request title
and we can get the request from the request from I thought that level pro-rights and we'll get it title
and half body which is going to be requests.
Get the body safe.
Run the test again and then class Test future not found.
Let's check out our test.
And it means this passed and then it reached this point where we have to find the person in it and find.
So let's use our post as one final time and sure enough we have a successful test.
So we are now able to create test in our database but don't let any user create a post in our application
to take care of that in the next episode.