We don't want any use that should be able to create post but only authenticated use us.
But before we write test for that what are we going to do is actually write some validation test for
creating Borst So we are going to be writing tests to make sure that a title must be required to create
a post on a body must also be required.
So let's go ahead and create that public function test.
Title is required to create most.
So how are we going to do this.
We are going to send a request to that and point but we're not going to pass in a title so we're going
to said the title to no and then we are going to assert that the session has arrows.
And one of those arrows is going to be title.
Right.
So in our test response that BHB we have these asserts session has errors because remember we feel a
validation feel in Lovelle it's going to redirect the use of block or thematically and it's going to
set some sesshin keys containing the rendition areas that we have.
So let's go ahead and assert this.
So we're going to see response asserts session has errors and we're going to pass in the title as a
key.
OK.
So if you make a request to that end point without the title it should give us an error in the session.
So let's run this test independently by giving it a go and is going to be title we quiet is the name
of our group.
That's how the term you know one that we title we quiet as a group and we haven't seen in take constrained
volition not no constraint field on post title.
OK.
So this is coming from our database saying that the first is not supposed to be null.
But then we give you all.
So what we're going to do is actually mirror that error a little bit by going to a clipboard stable
and then we're going to meet that error by making this an off label.
And this is just going to help us actually drive our validation.
So let's run that again.
And then we have session is missing expected key areas because if we had the words on what test response
first of all our role for them are checks if there's a key for cross and then it starts checking if
the error has the title key right.
And so that's because we don't even have any validation at all.
So let's head over to our controller and here again to validate the data that is being passed in.
So this validates we're going to take in the session and we're going to pass in an array of our nation
laws.
So first of all I'm just going to create available here for a session and then our request radiation
was sayto must be required.
OK so now that we have this validation rule for what it's all let's run that test again.
And really we have a validation exception that is foreign and that Videsh an exception is thrown because
in our handler we are twinn the exception that's uncommented a little bit.
And check out that and obviously we have a successful test.
Now let's wait exactly the same test for our body in our quick post-test.
So I'm just going to duplicate all of this.
And here is going to be body required for a good name.
And I'm just going to quit this too.
Body is required to quit posting.
And here we're going to have new post-Idol and this time around the body is going to be normal and we
are going to assert that assertion has the body aasan.
So let's run that test.
And this is going to be body quiet for a surgeon that has key areas because the radiation is just passing.
So we said that body required run that again.
And we have a successful test but let's not forget in our create stable we want to move this low level
flight that we used to test to make sure that the test give us expected.
So everything works perfectly.
Let's run everything in a suit and we have all successful responses.