Let's introduce love a dusk into application and this is simply a test now when there's a test.
Are they going to help us test some functionality in the application which is going to be a little more
complicated if we're using a traditional BHB unit for test.
So what lever does is going to do for us.
For example let's see if we want to test that when the use of the home route he actually says this button
that he can click and visit like has the cup.
Well if we actually try to run that with our traditional test obviously we going to actually be able
to do that.
But then Lavoe gives us a very cool way to run that in a browser in a very simple manner.
So first of all we need to install does great and the installation as usual with novel is really easy.
So let's just require that the composer require Lavo that's awesome.
We have to live with those and start the next game for the complete installation.
Structurally registar that does service provider but then we don't ones really state for it to be available
in production and also available in testing.
So we are going to try to put it in a service provider who probably the service provider or we can also
create a provider for those.
But for now let's head over to the social media and just place that in it.
So in register metho to register it with our application.
So first we have to import that so use level service provider and then we need to register it.
So love is going to check if the level is going to check if the app environment is testing all new called
meaning on your local machine that is going to register the dosage.
So will either meaning my time change and Romainville go to production.
Dusk is not going to be available for you to use next you just need to run dusk stores.
So HP our site DOS install does scaffolding successfully.
And that's a red dotted with such an Daskal.
Now if you check in out there we will see that we have a new browser directory and it contains Konsole
pages screenshots and an example test.
This is surely a lot but we're going to go into all of this.
So first of all we have for example test which extends does this case.
And if we check out our dust test case which is in that test just ask is dashi right here.
We'll just go right Chris the application just like for a Peachtree test and then it starts the clum
driver and you can specify the parts to which is going to navigate.
Right.
OK.
So let's head over to the example test and see what it does.
First of all we have a Brown-Smith thought which is going to help us to navigate the Brasa So he takes
a closure on land for the slows or we can pass different commands.
So first of all we can see browser visit the slash lounge.
And then I said that you actually see Lavo on the page.
So how do we run those commands.
We just run.
We are assigned the dusk and then we enter so it opens the browser navigates that endpoint and gives
us a feel that it did not see Lovelle readings.
The Elliman body but let's check up our welcome that Bladud PH BE we have an room right there.
So dust was not actually able to access the beach right.
And that's because we need to settle our application roots right here.
OK.
So I'm just going to change this to testing lab with that death because that's what I'm using for my
application.
And then run ph be honest and ask again
never gets to that.
And we have a successful test.
He was able to assess it.
So if you have localhost and you're running on ph me Alasan surfing's.
Exactly the same thing.
But if you have such domain's make sure you actually configured the arm you are in your ear because
that's what those he's going to use.
OK so what if we change days to something like this and run.
That's common again.
We have Ophelia and we have feel expected to like but it was not in the body.
So that's before all of those works gives us the possibility to actually test some stuff.
For example if you want to test the luggin ph or even once or to test that a user can create a post.
We just need to write a test saying visit the endpoint create posts type in some data into this field
type data into this other field click this button and then assert that your redirect to this page assert
that the database has these.
I said that this and that and this.
Awesome.
So it's kind of give us a lot of flexibility and fun stuff to take care of in our test.