Stuff by introducing new lover Guscott the last lesson.
Let's go ahead and take a look at that with us by driving a simple logging functionality in our application
to Crinan dusk test by 1 mph be our center does make logging test.
That's created for us.
Therefore you know a browser to have you logging tests.
So I'm just going to clean this off and we're going to walk step by step to the process of creating
this public function test a user can log in.
So then there is a use off or instead.
This is simply going to be factory for the user class creates and obviously we need to import that User
class at the top and then on that does this case class we have a method that is available to us so we
can see this browse and this method takes in a callback that gives us an instance of Vassall that we
can use to run our tests.
So the browser class that isn't what I I here we receive an instance of this callback automatically.
That's what I would ask.
And then right Kubik we can do a little bit of things that we want to happen in the application.
So first of all using Windows is simply following the process that you're going to use to test job allocation.
Right.
So just like I noticed in this is what we're going to be doing.
But automap but automating it.
So first of all what do we do we navigate to the loggin page right.
If we want to plug in the user if you want logging.
So we're going to see also visit the log in page.
So visit slash logging.
And once we are on the log in page what's the next step we need to type in our e-mails right.
So I'm just going to see type and we're passing e-mail here which is the name of the input field we
want to typing.
And then we can type in the user e-mail and this user has a user generated here.
Therefore we need to proceed into this construct all so use user.
And then after you've typed or email we need to type our password.
Right.
So we'll just type use our password right here and we can't use the possible because these are passwords
are really encrypted.
What we can do is passing an encrypted version the unencrypted version which we can find in our model
factory right here.
OK.
So after typing the password we just need to press the log in button right.
So we're going to press the button that has Aztec's logging and then we're going to see a search path.
Yes this is our search step and we're going to assert that the path is whole meaning after we Prezza
log in Butsu.
We provided a code red credentials aspect that this user should be directed to the actual route.
OK.
So this is our basic test or we just need to do is run this test.
Now how do we run it.
We can run it exactly the same way we've been running our test by simply passing a group right here
and we're just going to see the name of this group is luggin.
And I'm just going to use this migration right here so that Lavoe can migrate and we're back at least
to the database after it's done in the test.
So let's run our test.
PH We are excited DAs and the group is luggin
and we receive a failure saying that unable to locate the Elliman this because like we saw it navigate
to the 4 0 4 page because it didn't find this out.
Now how are we going to fix this.
We could go ahead and create a logging route and create a page where there's email and password and
then also where there's a button and then make sure that once he clicks on this on this button it takes
that e-mail is the password lofting the user that makes the whole bird Lavo really does it for us so
we're just going to want to be areason make off now that we've created off PreCheck and always be Socius
views that we have an off topic tree.
We password log in and register our views and also in our web ph.
B We also have an off routes that as registered for us which registers a slash logging slash redstart
and all of that and also which starts to slash homework.
OK.
So let's run our test again.
Our show we have a successful test.
So we've been able to test that the user actually can logging into the application.
Now whether we're functionality can we test with Lavoe dusk.
Remember we have a web page and we just start the post route and when we visit this post route we see
all the post on the page right and or when we visit when we when we visit the slush post ID road we
also see a particular post with the ID that was posted.
Right now let's write a simple test to make sure that if we navigate to this page and we find a particular
link with a particular button and we click it it's going to navigate us to the particular page for that
post.
Right.
So we're going to take care of this in the next episode.