Another test I want us to write is Vistula post-speech clicking on a particular post link and then actually
viewing the post right.
So let's go ahead and write that public function test.
A user can view our post and we can do almost exactly the same thing when I get a factory.
But the structure is going to be for the posts that we want to view and he's going to use the post class
that's just in the post-blast at the top.
Then we need to get him a boxing stance and in the callback.
We're not going to be visiting this page.
And men are going to be passing the user or going to in the post and right here will visit the post
page and then would click a link and this link is going to be the view posts GITTOES.
And then after clicking that link will first of all a search that the past is the past to view this
particular post which is post slash Nepos ID and then just assert that we see the Ditto's for that post
even though we've already covered this in our test coverage.
Let's just say we assert that we see the post title and assert that we see the contents body and also
Ostrow that we see that these supposed creator that using are helpful methods that we create up.
And that's pretty much it.
Let's just give this a group and run it.
And this is going to be both.
Page right.
Let's just give it the group.
And then we run it by saying ph we are San dusk and the group is post page.
Now it points out to us the error we are having which says we cannot read pop actually property of undefine
meaning we don't actually have that link that we are trying to click right.
So when you write tests like this and we head over to.
So when we write just like this and we now see that we don't have that link.
One of the great advantages is in case you want to switch out your theme that see you want your website
to have a new theme and you want to bring in a new theme and you replace every single view you can just
simply want all of this automated says to make sure that everything works the same.
Making sure that you haven't changed the way that works towards making sure that the linkage actually
view the post is still available.
A lot of that stuff.
So let's go ahead and simply create a link such that when the browser tries to click that link it's
going to view it.
Right.
So helmets are post that only the Ph be.
And right here in the For Each loop we want to generate a link for each of our posts right.
So I'm just going to paste in that post that takes their view post GITTOES and this is what the process
is going to look for.
And then I'm gonna specify that it should go to the slushed post route.
And pressing the post ID as simple as that.
Awesome.
So let's run our test again to see what we get.
And we have a successful test.