Let's use the US to actually test drive the ph that we're going to use to create a post by the authenticated
user.
So let's go ahead and create a new dust test yet.
Our son does make
create post-test awesome that's been created for us.
So we have our quick post-test right here.
Let's clean up this and we're going to see public function test off the user can create post.
So what's the first thing let's just use or abuse or right here then generate a user with our factory
and the next thing.
We just need to call the browser I thought restricts in a callback.
And in that callback we have available and an instance of Vasa.
And let's just use I use our table right here.
Awesome.
So we have access to that user.
So what are we going to be doing to test if a user can create a post.
First of all we want to use that to be authenticated right.
So we're going to call browser luggin ours which is a very helpful method that does provide us with
passing the user that we want to authenticate.
And then the next thing we just need to visit the page that we want to use to create a post right.
So viscid to create speech and then what do we want to do we want to type in the pipe the title type
in the body and then click on the Create post button right.
So we're going to see type and I'm just going to see the name of that future title and I'm just going
to type in a new post.
And I'm also going to type in into the body and this should be my new body.
And I'm just going to see assert and I'm just going to say I also press a button on the text and this
button is going to be safe post.
And first of all for the assertions we're going to make sure that the US-CERT path yse slash post.
So when a user commits or successfully make sure that he's redirected to the post route and then we
are going to assert that we see the new post that we just created.
So I said that we see new post on that page and also assert that we see the new body aasan so viscid
to create each type.
This type does press this button so that when we get to that page make sure you see this text and see
this text as simple as that.
What is a very readable.
So let's go ahead and give this test group so we can run it.
So group and this is just going to be create Post had a sermon on ph we are saying ask with a group
called create post based above your not found this.
Obviously that's because we haven't used the trait so let's just go ahead and use it as a game.
Awesome.
So now we have an embassy.
We don't have that page right because we saw a peach for for display to us.
Now we're going on first of all fix this and then make sure that our sessions pass.
So how do we fix the visit what's our weather picture be and make sure the registar gets routes and
this is going to be gets and it's going to be create post and it's going to go to the Create post route
which is going to display the view where we can actually create a post.
Let's check out that test.
So it's the creators we fixed this.
The next thing is to make sure that we have this create Bosma thought in our controller right.
Boesch controller public function Crit. post and it's simply going to return a view create post right
head of a test.
This viewer should have a title field and you should also have a body Phew.
So let's head over to our views directory and we're going to have to create a new file.
So resources views.
And we're going to create create post that blade PH BE AWESOME.
So we said from our test that we should have a title field a buddy field and a safe post button.
Right.
So let's take care of that.
We need to have a form and an input which is of name title.
And let's just make a text area of name body and all of this is not necessary.
And finally we need a button and the text in that button should be safe post.
Right.
So this and this and these assets what else we have to make sure that after the post is saved we redirect
to this path.
Now remember we've already driven the process of starting a post.
So we just need to do is submit that form to this endpoint and it's going to create a post for us.
So we already have this method right here.
The stop loss method of quitting a post for us.
So let's head over to the cripple's and make sure that we direct this form to this end point.
As simple as that.
Now hopefully hopefully everything should work as aspects.
But now it brings us to the point.
Hopefully everything should work as expected.
But if we check out our stock plus my thought once the post is created we are not redirecting the user
anywhere right.
So let's just return redirect to the slash posts route so that we can fix this session and then on the
slush route we've already made sure and written tests that we're going to see all the posts.
So we're going to see the spores and also see this body.
Awesome.
So let's go ahead and run that test and see what we get.
OK.
We received a method not allowed exception and let me check out what we have right there.
What do we have in our quick post and if we need to specify that this should be a Metro posts.
Awesome.
That's one that says again
mismatch a separation.
OK.
Now to a crowd there who can.
So let's head over and echoed C-s RF field right here.
One that a staggering
also so now we have a successful test can finally create a post.