Why don't we write another lab or dusk test to make sure that only an authenticated user can naturally
create a pause.
Right.
So if I use a trice viscid this endpoint he's redirect that's the logging page.
So let's think of that.
I'll just copy every single thing in this test just to save some time.
Paste this right here.
Says the user can create post.
No need to create a user because we want to make sure the user is not authenticated.
We're not going to be logging the user in then we're going to visit this route and we're not going to
be asserting any of this.
We're going to simply see a certain path IISS slash logging.
Right.
So I'm just going to pull this off and we have what's asked.
Revisit that page.
I said that it is slash logging simple.
So let's create a group so we can run this stairs individually and we'll see create host of whatever
name you want to give right.
So that's one quick post off the group Yikes.
And we have a figure saying filled searching that's two strings are equal because the use of words to
redirect that to this page and he actually quit the post-white.
So let's head over to our Web PH BE and see how we could fix this so we could simply attach a middleware
of auth to this route to make sure that only the authenticated user can visit this and point.
Right.
So let's go ahead and run this again.
Awesome.
We have a successful test.
So any person trying to visit this route must be authenticated on why we're here.
We could really just protect the post side of the road to make sure that only authenticated users are
truly make a request to this end point.