OK guys let's talk about aggregation we're going to be Buellton and we're going to build this from scratch
with a test driven development that poured right into us for everything.
And it's going to be real fun.
So if you want a true introduction yourself it leaves an immediate bad cast that come.
OK so what's this application.
It's a SAS application.
Like when you actually have in real life and it has courses and these courses are video lessons that
the subscribers on the platform can use.
Some of them are free.
Some of them are not.
And for the ones that are not free to use actually has to have a subscription which means you're going
to have a lot of cache and stripe in this project.
And this is going to create a subscription for the user giving him permission to watch any sort of lesson
on the proper form.
OK.
So if you go ahead and visit one of the courses right here which is actually created set by one of the
students here and this costs you can actually see that we have fortunately right here that detects if
you stay locked in use or has already started this course and they use and readies for that and we're
going to also write tests for that.
And if we continue learning right here then it kicks us to the page where we have the title of the series.
And we also have the title of the lesson.
OK.
And we actually have the play right here which loads videos for this but plan a lesson from the meal
and then we also have next and previous lesson Bateson's and notice how it redirected us to the second
lesson because this is where we left off the last time we started the series.
OK.
So we also have tracking right here with Reddy's.
We also have next lesson the previous lesson for Chanology right here.
Go to the next one.
We also have complete lessons functionality.
So for example if I forward this video today and right here automatically you see right here it fires
up on events that tells us hey you completed the series but then if not the last lesson of the series
then it's going to redirect us to the next automatically.
OK.
Another functionals I want to show you is to create Sui's functionality where you can literally create
your own series as an administrator.
So if you have an administrator account you can create your own series upload images.
I'm going to be teaching you how to upload images to storage and how to test these laws to make sure
everything is fine and we are also going to be able to edit and deletes erase all of the functionality
and right here if we check out all the see.
This is for the users that are not administrators.
They can see other series.
But as administrator we can also visit all the service right here and we can see all the crates that
series if I click into this one then it takes us to the content area where we manage this series.
OK.
So we have this functionality right here and this dashboard is completely created in view G-S.
OK so if we want to delete this last one right here we can go ahead and delete right there.
And it gives us an alert and if we say OK then we have lessons with that successfully and we can actually
go ahead and create another son in case we want and this is simply going to add another lesson to the
dashboard.
We can also choose if a lesson is going to be premium.
And by default it's false.
But we want it to be true then means only subscribers will be able to watch that lesson.
OK.
So that's unfortunately we have quit with our day to day view.
Yes this is the most part where we're going to be using VHS and it's going to be real fun because that's
a lot going on right here.
Craig added late updates communicate with Sarratt and stuff like that.
So I'm just going to edit this lesson and I'm going to make it premium right here.
OK.
So if I saved this lesson then I visit the home page visit that particular course and then continue
learning.
I can actually watch it because I have an active subscription because if I visit my profile then check
out my payments on subscription.
You can see that my current plan is yearly right here.
OK.
And that can actually change my plan so we have change plan for you right here.
And if I want to change my card details I can also do that so I can update cards Ito's which parcel
this pretty Strype subscription form I can put in my details.
Basically every single thing you want to do in a stripe sarce live application.
We have that functionality right here.
OK.
So I'm not going to be showing you to everything because there is a lot but that's the basic idea of
the application.
And this actually has a lot going on behind the scenes tracking stuff with Reddy's making sure that
we write tests for everything so that everything once successfully hosting this application and deploying
it live.
It's going to actually take a lot of work and I'm going to be walking you to each and every one of that.
OK.
So thank you so much and I hope to see you in the course where we actually start building this awesome
stuff.
Thank you.
And see you then.