A blank install or flower or 5.5 for IKEA and I'm just going to go straight to the point the first thing
we're going to be doing is such really taking care of our authentication system by default level provides
us with the components logging components for registration.
So what we're going to be doing in this video is editing the system to fit our needs.
So like US uses an Ajax request or something like that authentication system so you just need to put
in your data in a model and then logging and it's automatically done.
So what we're going to be doing is trying to replicate that system.
So before we actually do that we need to understand the defaults that level provides for us right.
So I'm going ahead of what my Abdur a tree S2P controllers of the tree and we're going to be taking
care of the logging controller seen my logging controller.
Yeah it doesn't really look like it has a lot.
But then what we're going to do is run ph be re-assign make off.
So I just show you what that Kommandos for us.
And it's simply going to register some rounds quite some views for us.
So now I'm going to run ph be areason roadless to show you what we have.
Now we see we have a couple of logging or restriction routes for authentication that are being registered.
Now you look at this it points to the log in control but we don't really see this method in our class.
It also points to a log in method for the post method.
But we still don't see it right.
So let's go ahead and dig in and see where all of this is going for now.
Love is this idea of single responsibility traits and this trait actually that it uses right here.
Authenticates use us.
It's in charge of our truly the logging controller functionality behind the scenes.
So let's dig into that and see what we have.
So that saturates the authenticates users.
It actually uses the redirects users and Tartaros plugins but when not going to look into into that.
So this is our show looking for some method that is registar here for our get real help for the log
in page.
So this method simply returns to view of the logging that was generated with our Ph.D. We Assan make
off commands.
So if we go right here into our resources there a tree views or a tree in or off there a tree sure enough
we have the log in the ph ph be OK.
So that's what the method does.
It simply returns that view.
And if we are truly trying to visit that page we're going to see this view then we have a log in mid-thought
which takes care of our authentication.
So if we check that out first of all we have a valid log in my thought on this class or on this street
right here which simply validates the data.
Make sure that we have the correct validation for to use only and that we use to validate the user and
the password.
Right.
So this use of the method is simply a best way for Lavoe to give us to customize the functionality.
So for example let's say you wanted to switch your functionality to a username based functionality.
Or rather maybe a former baseball analogy.
All you need to do is actually change this name or this field and everything is just going to walk as
expected.
Right.
So Messy you want to use for a number and you have a field in your database table for us.
Then you just get a feeling for number right here.
OK so let's continue with our deadlocking method.
So the value for this Court invalidates the username fuel that we passed in and obviously we can customize
this if we wish.
Then once our logging method posses logging method continues now to check if the user has too many logging
attempts on this obviously is accompanied or accomplished by the Trotter's logging method.
If these others not have too many logging items obviously this is going to be skipped and then we're
going to call the attempt to log in on this try to game.
So right down the bottom we have an attempt to log in and it's simply going to call on them mid-thought
on the prison guard that we're using.
And this is and we're going to call the credentials from the request get the credentials and right here
we have the credentials for that gets requests only this username meaning if you specified e-mail is
going to get the e-mail and if he spits frightful nobody's going to get phone number.
And then he gets also the password.
Now it passes that into the offense metod and also passes this house remember bullion right here.
So in case they use clicks on the Remember Me button and it's also going to pass it to the FNMA.
No offense phone is simply going to return a boolean.
True or false.
Was the use of successfully authenticated or Motz.
So right here if they use those authenticated successfully we're simply going to return this send log
in response.
So the send log in response method on this tread again takes care of what happens as soon as the user
is authenticated.
So first of all we have a session generated for the user.
We collect the log in our terms and then we return this authenticated.
So now this authenticates an mid-thought on this trip.
It's like a hook that we could use.
So as soon as you use something to get it will generate a session logging attempts and call this method.
So Lavoe is calling this method behind the scenes or it's simply redirecting the user to the Internet.
But.
Right.
So if this method is not reach it is right now by default since it's known Lavallee simply cannot be
done with the use of the Internet.
But now what if we want to do something else.
If the user was actually successfully locked in.
So what we can do is simply take care of our authenticated method and level is going to call it once
the user is successfully locked in.
Now another thing that happens is what if the user was not successfully launching.
It means this is going to be skipped.
And this is what is going to have happened here.
So incremental logging items is going to be caught.
We just simply cannot see.
OK this user has failed to catch on.
One more time increase that and then somebody's gonna send field log in response to the user.
So this Sinfield log in response is a metaphor on this lost again.
So if you go ahead and try to find that method here it is simply true validation exception with messages.
This username and it would call our translation and pass in the off the field flag.
If the user was not successful we you start going to call the send field log in response to a validation
exception and pass in this message to the user.
Right.
So for us to customize this method of this system only thing we actually need to do is to overwrite
or is to provide this authenticated method to Lovelle Lavo to know what to do.
That's just it.
Right so once you actually get the hang of how this Treach works you know how loved those behind the
scenes.
It's very very easy to overwrite.
So in the next video let's take care of overwriting it and actually making it work with Ajax requests.