Like grabbing the last video when we have a luggin response which is positive Ravell is going to generate
a session all the log in attempts and call authenticated method on this trait.
So what are we going to be doing is actually creating these authenticated method in the controller.
So I'm just going to copy the templates that we have and for the purpose of this video I read said a
test user that we could use larger ships in with issues use of factory that we could use.
So I just use this for each region of the news using Peachtree or San Diego.
So I'm going to copy the templates that we have here.
There we go.
I'm going to cut it out.
Truly sort of a writer.
So in my log in control I'll paste that in and sure enough I need to import the request class right.
So I'm just going to copy this path and make sure I use it at the top.
Use eliminate S2P request and automatically inject the request for us.
So what do we want to do.
We want to test to see or make sure that level is going to call this method once the logging is successful.
So let's just start by returning a string.
So when the result is successful we're lovers of article you can call these authenticated thoughts and
know what to do.
So we should expect a loggin successful response when we visit a browser.
Let's check this out.
Go to our logon page and are putting the e-mail of the user I created under password is secret by default
for Lavo.
Now click on mugging and sure enough we have this logging successful response that we gets from all
authenticated MATHO.
So you see just by writing one single method we can actually completely switch form a view based logging
system to an AJAX based system.
So let's just jump street and try to make this walk from the front end.