Let's get moving as you can see I completely changed the template that we're going to be using.
We're going to be using the default level templates because I think we could do better.
So what we're going to be doing is using a theme called the SAS.
And you can find it on theme for no affiliates or anything but I've used the template I bought and used
it and I think it's really awesome.
Very lightweight.
So if you want to use it in any production applications make sure you get the license.
But if not you could just use my copy for development purposes.
What I did was just to create an app that bleed that page and putting the theme.
Just install three simple siestas for hours and try off in the cold for these lesing you'd actually
have this theme food that contains all the files that you need for the theme.
So I just took that in have a ZF of idea of app for viewers navigation right here home plug in.
Dan I have a used header and used content then I have my work on the blade.
That simply extends that lay out your header and then use the content.
Very simple stuff.
I don't want to bore you with all of this because that has little or no real learning in it.
OK so what do we want.
We want to click on this loggin button and actually see a luggin form.
Right.
And then if we successful logging the page simply refreshes just like Jeffrey does it.
So let's go ahead and dive straight into it.
Now in the duck component of the Stillmore you can actually see this component which is a model and
I'm just going to go ahead and use it.
So I'll head over to my dock components and we have this model.
I'm going to copy it and then had to run my example to you which is the default lawn that comes with
Lavoe paste in that template.
And sure enough I you to rename that.
I'm going to rename that to plugging the view head over to my iPod.
Abda just so I can change how that is when you start.
So I need to change this to luggin the view and I'm going to change this to view plug in.
This is a component we can use in our view.
You can also see I have Flavell makes already running as a watcher.
OK so now that they have that the first thing was to put in that same plate.
I've done that.
But this template is going to be a model and it has to be triggered so I'm just going to change this
to logging mode on.
Which is going to be the I.D. I'm going to have to watch my Abda blade.
And one of the navigation components on navigation is there were still luggin so I'm going to make sure
these dates are Togo equals Modahl.
This is simply put structure and data are Touggourt is sequel to the lemon with IGY logging on.
So when you click on this it's going to trigger the mood on with this ID.
So now we need to actually Mullins This component in our view.
Therefore in my obdurately ph we just write down some way after all the fruits are on the for the future.
I'm just going to mount you luggin and that will make this template available in our view.
OK.
So nothing complicated we just start a new components and it's a more dump and contains the template
for that with all we have a link in our layout file which is the luggin and this simply triggers that
and we don't.
And we have we just start that component as villagey.
Therefore in our template We've mounted it as you logging right here.
OK.
So let's go ahead and see how this works.
A quick refresh.
And when I click on that.
Sure enough I see my model.
So let's go ahead and do a little edits to that model.
And what I'm going to do is actually simply paste in a luggin registar template right here just so why
don't waste your time trying to design stuff that will not even help us in this lesson.
All right.
Done.
So let's check out what we have now.
We simply have this loggin form and this is exactly the log in form from the template I just copied
and socket straight into the model dialog.
Dave So what do we want to happen.
We want the user to fill in his details into this form.
He does select remember me or not and then click on the login button.
Let's take care of that in the next video.