Regular sunbaking Ajax request to go backhand so we can log in to user.
But before we actually start doing that let's just take care of this.
And this is naturally coming up form after G-S check that out.
Or rather of a bootstrap the jest.
And what happened in this novel would automatically try to register the six hours as a common header
with XOs so that all are going to be requests automatically have it attached.
But then how does it do this.
It simply gets a Mets are called CSIR tooken from the head of the document.
And if it doesn't find that it can so that locks the error that we find here.
And since I changed my template that's why we don't have that.
So let's go ahead and stick that in.
So we have a mess.
And the name is going to be quote you see as our token and the content you because you don't we just
need to call osseous our token method.
OK.
So we refresh and now that error is going we review a patron or three or four seats or a token injected
into the page also so we can now make Ajax request to a server using XOs.
And yes let's go ahead and take care of this in our luggin view.
We need to start doing some work right.
So I know I'm going to be sending the e-mail password and remember talk and feel to the server.
Therefore why on I just said that are going to change the placeholder to email and the model is going
to be called to email going to change to the model password.
And for REMEMBER ME field I just need to see the model because remember are some so let's define these
properties on our model.
So we have our DTMF thought which returns an object and we'll have our e-mail initialized to an empty
string or password initialized to an empty string also.
And I remember initialized to true.
OK.
So I had just tried to take a look.
Sure enough this is automatically checked for us and we check out our view tools we have our view logging
which has all that data are from us.
So if we actually try to change days using VM Zobel that member equals false then we see automatically
it naturally deactivates the checkbox.
So it means we actually successfully binding to this fall.
Let's consignor now we want this button to be activated when the user data is not actually correct.
Right.
So what we're going to be doing is actually creating a computer property to take care of validation
for us.
So let's just go ahead and say computer it and we're going to have an ECE Varley logging form thought
or computer property and this is simply going to return true or false.
Now we are going to be checking if the e-mail is a valid email and if the password is a valid password.
Right.
So let's just start simply by saying return this that e-mail and days that pass word when we want to
submit the form we're going to check for that property.
So right here where we have a luggin button here we're going to see buying that this property is valid
logging from.
So obviously we need not.
Right.
So if it's in value then we're going to have a mode set to true.
Let's check this out.
So if open or logging sure enough we have this button disabled.
But if you put in something here and something here it's automatically enabled.
So why don't we have a method that actually checks if the e-mail is a valid e-mail.
So let's just see just grebes check valid email and this is simply going to be using regular expressions
to check for that.
But since I don't want to actually get deep into that is simply going to copy the Meffert So he has
a method for that to check valid email.
So I'm going to come into this complaint right here and I can create my thoughts property and this is
going to be our first method.
So validate email.
Right.
So let's from this on each of validate e-mail or let's just change this to e-mail is valid and what
it does is it uses this regular expression to test of value that this past week.
Therefore let's just pass this the e-mail.
So if this that e-mail passes this test return TRUE else let's just return false.
So this mythology is simply going to validate an e-mail for us then what we could do is actually call
this methode return this.
That e-mail is valid and this is the cross-wired.
So let's try that out.
We have a log in form we put in Grish.
It's not activated but we simply tried to put in a valid e-mail and automatically a button is activated.
Wow that works right.
So our e-mail method is called Every time the e-mail property changes.
OK.
So let's continue it enough for the next.