Why don't we find some requests to see what we get.
Now we have a couple of toys this year either extracts or methods that have to do with authentication.
It's one of integrations or something like that.
Oh we just make the sequence right here in our component.
Now I'm going to actually make it right here in a component but in case we see that it's overloading
complains we are going to move it future to one of service.
OK so let's go ahead and set that up for us to make an Ajax request.
Import Agnew's from yours.
Because this is what we're going to be using.
Now we just need to find a click event to this Matsen which is a logging button.
So a click equals attempts logging.
OK so let's create that thought.
No MFX object attempts logging is going to be one of the thoughts and this mid-thought First of all
making a call to use that post and simply of the slash logging routes and the object that repassing
into exiles is an e-mail which is this email password.
This is distant password and remember a key just so clarity and can show that we're actually passing
in the correct attributes that are the ones who are logging control and also into our authenticates
use US creates to see what our End Point is actually expecting.
So validate logging method is expecting also to pass in an e-mail because that's what this username
which turns on a password and an optional Parminter is used in logging.
Mid-thought right here which is called member.
So e-mail password and remember are passed to the server and then simply listen to what we have as a
response.
So for now we're simply going to see console that lock the response that you have on the server.
And in case you catch any errors just speed them to the console for now.
OK.
So let's go ahead and try this out and we're going to be trying this out with a valid user.
So let's just go up and use our pitch we are Sun sync our app user.
And I'm going to grab his e-mail and I'm to open up my phone.
He's studying us in secret us the password watch out for my console.
Click on the log in my thought.
Looks like we have a successor who responds because of the 200 stodginess but the dates are that we
receive is not really expected.
Let's go ahead and check up on networks to see what we have.
OK so we have dashboard you are locked in.
So it's actually the return of you to us.
Let's go ahead and fix this in the very next video.