Your last reader ended up receiving the home page as a response.
Once we successfully locked in but wasted Actually we were already locked in.
I'm sorry about that.
And there's really no problem our system works as expected.
So just to make sure that we are always locked out in my web Ph.D. I set up this whole form I thought
all this hopeful about reaching out and you know authenticated users.
When we visited.
OK.
So before we actually test out our log in a game I'm going to log out in case I was locked in and then
I'm going to visit the home page and I'm going to open my logging modem pasting that e-mail address
typing secrets for a user and then keep logging on and off we have these loggin successful response
that is coming from our controller.
So the next step is actually determining what we want to return to our user.
Once he successfully logs in let's head over to a high level part of the application which is in our
logging controller and once we authenticated what we want to do first of all I'm going to be using our
session to flash.
So when the page loads we're going to check if there's any notifications in the session.
And we're going to display using the components or maybe an investigation service that we want to use.
So session flash and he's going to be success message and this is simply going to see.
And this is simply cannot be successfully locked in.
Right.
So we flushed the session and we return logging successfully.
Now this is actually where we have to decide what sort of response is we want to give back to Will front
and right.
Because we need to actually have a stand up because there are a lot of standards are there to actually
written responses to our front end.
OK.
So when an attribute any price I have a helpful method which I call maybe does send success response
and this Mithal is always in my control or that BHB So that is available to all of my control us and
the method it actually takes in the stutterers code and the data that I need to pass through the front
end and formats it in a particular response format as a response.
Now in this case with communicating with our love our petition directly so I think we could actually
take care of responses directly in the methods.
Right.
So we can just say we don't response Gee son.
And another thing is you can actually decide to use Lovell's responsible responsible interface to what
your response is.
But in this case we just need to confirm to viewers that the user is Loftin.
Right.
So I'm just going to see such use of.
OK.
So VGX once it sees a status of OK in those issues or was successfully Loftin.
Now back in some of your components if the response was successful we cannot really check from the status
code right here.
We can actually check for the data to see the statistical it was.
But if everything were successful meaning we success we lost our user in will just refresh the current
page.
Now we can simply use javascript's default API by saying location reload and it will take care of that
number.
What's the advantage of doing this.
You Abdur blade ph.
B Now we can actually make sure that that our template is rendered in the correct way.
So right down the bottom where we have this log in we can actually wrap this in an east edition and
see if or check else and if so if the user has not authenticated we'd have that link.
But then if the user really have indicated why don't we go up his name.
So we're just going to see us use our name.
OK.
So we can just say hey our user name.
So once our request to the server is successful an address receives a success response.
It's simply going to reload the current page and once it reloads that page sure enough what template
is going to re render and we should see the users name.
And we should not see the logging button.
Right.
Another thing we want to do is make sure that this is not mounted if we authenticated.
OK.
So no need to have extra SJM or templates.
So if I Sitrick and naturally we want the Motz.
Right.
So if it's not a check and if we're simply going to actually mount the components now model provides
us with some custom made directories that we are actually going to be switching.
I'll bring the refactoring but for now let's go ahead and just see this walk or creek or lockout and
point.
So we make sure we are truly locked out.
Visit our home page and let's try logging our personal e-mail type in the password.
Click on logging on automatically will piece it's refreshed.
And here we have our no ports or code or whatever.
And that is actually the use we have here.
So I will luggin by Ajax is successfully walking.
But what about validation checks or actually aerostat that we see from our server.
Let's think of that in the next video.