I don't like seeing Albertson active when we are truly making an Ajax request So let's take care of
that.
I'm going to introduce a new field and this is going to be a lot in-field.
So your clothing should be set to fall by default.
OK.
So there's no current Ajax request Dan in my computer property that checks if the form is valid.
I'm also going to see check and make sure that it's not loading.
OK.
So if it's actually loading then this is going to activate the phone right because this is true this
is true but this is going to be false.
So if this is actually loading or if there's actually call INS agents request then this is going to
disable the button right.
So because this is going to be true.
True but it's going to be false making the whole thing false.
OK.
So when we are attempting to logging.
We just need to set this to the loading Sutro.
And if we have an error meaning we are still going to be on the phone we just need to see that loading
was false.
So no need to do that.
If we have a successful response.
OK so let's check that out.
Now lugging if I put in an e-mail on a password of secrets or let's just say I put in a password that
doesn't match when I click on the button.
You see just a mode.
And then we have a 4:22 from our server.
And if I change my correct password it's still going to be just a mode to we have a successful refresh.
OK that's what I said.
Now let's think about how we can actually handle responses from our server.
So for example when we have to put you in the wrong password just now we actually received a 4:22 which
means a fill in validation error.
And if we actually head over to authenticates use our strengths that is coming from the field logging
response method because the string of validation exception we the off that filled message.
Right.
So if we actually received Videsh in exceptions for email or password or stuff like that it's going
to be taken care of.
Right at the top of our logging method right here.
But then since we are already receiving this because they use those e-mails in on March 1 in our database
or the password was not correct.
This is of addition exception that begin to receive.
OK.
So what happens when we actually receive this validation exception.
So what did this exception actually do.
If we head over to that class and check out the messages methode all it does is actually populates the
area back and then and then it would redirect the use of back with the validation errors.
So in the very next video we can actually customize this functionality to suit our needs.