Self-love five point five.
We actually have the possibility of it in our own cost time extension exceptions and so that we will
have complete control over what happens when we throw this exception that squarehead and use that to
our advantage.
First of all I'm going to have to watch my exceptions I'm a tree and I'm going to create a new custom
exception.
So like innocent we see logging field exception.
We or rather just change this to us.
Maybe we might want to use this exception also with arbitration.
So Orfield exception and right here we see we simply need to create a class and extend the base exception
right.
So who's Celan namespace two are exceptions.
And now that we hear something or like to do is actually change our application name so we Arisa an
app name and I'll change that too.
But cost.
OK so now that we've changed that we no longer have our.
But we have but cast's exceptions then we can now create a class called off field exception which extends
the exception class.
And what we could do is actually pulling the exception for sea level for rights Cross.
OK so now for Lavoe to be able to actually render exceptions in the carets we will need to provide two
methods.
One is a report method and the next.
So when the method.
Right.
And this report method is going to be taking care of maybe reporting our error also exceptions.
So services like custom logger when obvious in production or whenever we want.
But in this case what we just want to do is handle this exception in our application so we're just going
to say set up a public function render.
We're not interested in reporting obligation all the parts in the exception so this random thought is
simply going to return a response.
So each response Jason on what actually said the status school 2 4 2 2 and here we need to pass in an
army of data so we cannot dominie's are we by seeing what detail we can actually parse into this class
and when are as an error.
OK so let's try to see what we have let's head of about authenticates user and what level does this
actually uses the translation files to render that response.
So if we just head over to our resources long directory and head of that BHB This is the message that
actually sends this credentials to non-Markov records.
We cannot really use this by default.
So let's just head over to our field section and let's just see we set up a message key and this is
going to be called to these credentials do not march of Eckhardt.
Right.
Because remember this method is only going to be called in the case where either the use of password
is not correct or the email is not correct.
Right.
So we need to simply on our ideas mid-thought and call of our own custom exception.
So backing of a logging controller I'm going to base this right here and rather than to any radiation
exception I'm going out for a noon off field exception.
And for now we don't have any palmettos that we're passing into this method.
OK.
So at the top we need to pull that in.
So use but coarse exceptions of field exception are.
So let's try this out.
If everything works perfectly we should actually receive a response with this message on the status
of 4:22.
So let's try this.
So log in my row and I'll paste in that e-mail was a wrong password and see what we get.
Sure enough we have 42 like before but let's go to our Anette what's up and actually see the data that
we received.
So we received a message property which say these credentials to non-match are records.
So it means our custom exception is actually being called and since we can actually override all the
methods in a lot of things could use us traits.
This gives us a lot of flexibility to do whatever we want with our application.
OK so we are successfully getting this message.
What do we want to do when we receive that Carol.
For now we just console that log in but we need to give a little feedback.
All right.
Let's take care of these in the next video.