Research getting an error response on my server.
But one thing we can do in the catch block to make sure we actually get some feedback so we use our
ears to set up some errors in our form.
So what we're going to be doing is having an air force object and this object is simply going to be
just plain arrows in our phone.
Once we get that error or from our database we could actually check the status of the error.
OK so we can see if error or not response and naturally forced to get the on line response in the exhaust
area we need to get that response and we can get the stutterers and we can see if the status is 4:22.
That really means this you did not provide us with the correct logging details and we're simply going
to push to the object.
This is the process that Bush and we have a message like we couldn't verify your account details.
OK.
So that's good enough for us to do this let's just instantiate this find way.
Then once we push that aerosol he automatically let's make sure we actually displayed in templates.
Barrett if this is a 1:56 it means everything went well on our site but the users credentials were not
correct.
But we cannot actually check if it was 9:42 maybe it's 500.
Now we could actually push through the airport and seen something went wrong.
Refresh and try again.
OK.
So that's what we have.
Let's take care of that in our template.
So right after we have a farm let's set up a default on alerts that are alerts of danger.
And this is simply going to be displayed Eve.
So evasion of the if condition are right here for us but that's greater than zero.
So if the arrows.
We actually it has more than one element that we're going to display this block.
And are you afraid we may actually want this to just lead us so on at least and then we can actually
add a class of let's go up here and inside that or at least we can have this go up items.
Then we wrapped it in a V for our inheritance and simply Eckard error.
Now we have this ever seen.
It would be preferable for us to bind to a key which we might not really need to do but just to shut
all these errors.
Let's just go ahead and buying this to a key and see that index of error.
OK.
So that's just me.
Just shut up.
So now for each other that we have no where else are we we are simply going to actually output this.
OK.
So another thing we want to do is make sure that if the user clicks on the attempts log in Marsan which
simply said this that error has to be called to an empty array again.
And by Thing that should do it for our validation.
Let's go ahead and try this out.
Open up our logon window and paste in our email.
Putting the wrong password.
Try to logging and sure enough we have that error all right even though it looks really really bad.
But then we have it right.
So now let's make a little change.
Try to log in again.
And the error goes away before coming back all over again.
Right.
So looks like authentication is working.
I'm going to take care of this really bad for my team behind the scenes.
But I think over 80 years of integration works perfectly.