90 percent of the time when you're in love or you might never need to actually test your authentication
API because you might never actually need to customize it.
But then in cases where you've created classes which are different my thoughts and I truly customize
the logging it's really helpful to write some test.
So let's go ahead and create a helpful test that is going to help us solve logging functionality.
So ph we Arissa latest logging tests are good.
So in my test directory sure enough in the future we have these logging test then I clean this up and
I'm going to create public function.
So as a user and actually the first thing I want to does it's actually the message that we receive when
they use others not pass in the correct credentials.
OK.
So tasks are user receives correct message when parsing in want credentials.
OK so that's a really crappy name but it is descriptive of what we want to do.
How is this desk going to look.
We just need to get a user.
And then maybe call that logging and point passing in the wrong password and then make some assertions
on the response.
Right.
So let's go ahead and take care of this.
First of all our use our squatch in our factory for the broadcast use Archelaus and adequate methods
of persistent aasan.
So we just need to see this post Jason because that's the kind of request we are making and the End
Point is slash logging and we need to pass the data that we send into the server right here in an array.
So we are parsing the e-mail and would pass in the user last e-mail that was generated and would pass
in a fake password right.
So let's just see one last word and then write another response we can actually call assertions.
So our search statutes for this response would be 4:22.
So we are asserting that the status must be a 4:22.
And let's also assert that the adjacent contains a message the message that we are passing in and and
we'll get this message from our off field exception class.
Right.
So I think for now we could actually work with this and this is what we can to make sure that everything
we're doing is working right.
So clearly use up make a post request to that end point crossing the Emoto password and then assert
that the status is forcing you to.
And also I said that the Jessen response that we receive contains a message key with this exact stream.
OK so how do we run our tests.
We can use Lovell's refresh database straight.
And when it just sets up the little bit of PH be unique configuration for our application during testing.
So so I'm going to pass in an environment database right here.
So the connection should be as secure writes testing which I'm going to set up so I'm going to set up
a testing connection and I'm going to actually make sure I tell people we need to run our tests in memory.
So dbd to me is not going to pass in a memory flag right here.
So let me set up this testing database connection in my database that the PSP configuration file.
So we have a secure like connection my scope connection or setup testing connection.
This receives an array and the driver is also going to be asking on lights.
They me this is going to be from the database and would get testing that Esco light.
OK so let's generate that test in the Esco light fire.
So torche in our database there's a tree slash there in the rescue all light.
And sure enough we actually want to check in our database directory.
We have our test in the let's go right.
OK.
So I think we're ready to run our test.
Let's try to see what we get.
So in my friend or a tree in my brain I have my Ph.D. unit executer on and I'm going to filter this
to logging dust's.
So let's run that and sure enough we have a successful test.
Right.
So because we really are with the right because we actually really what the production code for that
test.