I mean for writing test for one logging functionality is because we've actually added that the default
state law will provide for us.
So every single place where we actually admit that something that level provides by default we're going
to write a little test for that.
For example if we had a waterlogging controller and check out what I think kids at mid-thought we're
actually doing some things.
So let's go ahead and write a little test to care of this.
So we're going to see public function test correct response after use our lost in.
Right.
So we are making sure that the response that we get is actually what we need right.
So first of all we're just going to use user.
And secondly we're going to make that post request and that is always going to look exactly like the
one we just wrote.
Now we want to actually pass in the correct password here.
So we make sure that the user is actually authenticated.
And then we assert that the status is a 200 meaning successful response.
We are certain that we have this are we as part of the sun in the response.
So statues.
OK.
So that's the response recently from this.
And the last thing we want to answer utterly absurd is that the session has a particular key.
Now this key is going to be success.
Now we have two options like your of what's test response that ph B which is actually in our level call
human foundation testing and research for that METAR assert session has just discover that it takes
in a key and it takes in an optional value so that key is what we just passed in here which is session.
And then we could actually make sure that the value of that is specified right.
So right here we could say okay we want to make sure that the success message is specifically you are
successfully lofting just like we having a logging controller or not.
So in this case I'm just going to help to my logging controller and I'm going to copy the message that
we have in the session and I'm going to make sure that are logging tests I truly checks for it.
So I think that's going to work perfectly.
Let's go ahead and win a test and see the results that we get.
So for us to run the specific tests let's just use BHB unit and we're going to filter out to this particular
test.
OK.
We run it and sure enough we have a successful response.
So it means our session was set.
Our starters here was you know a decent response and the status of the response was 200.
So we had successfully overturned the defaults for Lavo and our test of told us that everything is OK.