Let's begin with our ministration.
So first of all I'm going to go to my theme and I have the space register.
Accion all I'm going to copy it at what's on my registar the late the PH We are going to pull everything
right there in space.
Now I don't really have any problem actually duplicating this because it's seemingly complicated to
actually use exactly the same layout for now because we're going to have to use a bunch of your Stedman's
to actually check if this is the registration page because this is such a little thing doesn't really
matter.
I'm going to go ahead and do it this week.
OK.
So we have just register page.
Richard Travis this the box and see what we have registar.
And we have this recession page with this beautiful background image and shake it off.
We could actually use this registration page to copy or get the user's credentials.
He's caught to subscribing to a planet.
But that's going to be needed.
So for now let's focus on what we want.
We want to get to use this e-mail address and the password right so that we get the user name and then
we're going to automatically urging them to use US username behind the scenes which means we're still
going to write a little bit.
The default for Lovelle.
So first of all let's set up this form.
You walk like Lovelle expects it to.
So head will form.
Make sure that we have a CSR field.
We have our action attributes and issue a truly VC slush registar and the name of this should be name.
So this is actually going to be full name if that's what we want.
And for us treacly exactly what Lavallee suspecting from last letter are the words or just stuck on.
And we're going to check out of conditionals.
So loverly suspect in a name field an email which must be unique to the table and the password.
So we need to pass in the e-mail.
So a name for this field should be e-mail changes to type e-mail just voice unified validation crossword.
And I don't want to do a password confirmation so I'm going to make sure I placed the name because password
and just range Arista control.
Let's just go ahead and see how it walks.
First of all we make a request to register and point.
And let's actually check out what the default is called.
So we are Sun Rock at least and it looks like largely calling a registar method.
So let's go ahead to this class and we can't find any reached effort here so we should be in a trade.
And then we go.
So let's get over it soon.
This tread is so registar use OSS and should actually find a register method.
There we go.
So first of all calls and this validates or validates that and maybe returns Barkworth any of us for
us any ventures see to use or successfully we just start and actually embedded in that event.
It's actually going automatically creates the user.
So user this creates.
So this is it's actually creating the user.
So it's going to create mid-thought on our register control right down here on the bottom and then it
lsen the use of romantically and then calls this Williston method.
All if this were just a method it's not defined just like authenticated.
It's automatically going with redirects the user to redirect path.
And with Derek puffa methode comes from these we Daryn.
Suzanne.
OK.
So what are we going to be doing.
Let's just stop writing from our on.
And then we're going to move forward.
So like we said we don't want a password confirmation so we just need to move the confirmed validation.
That's the first thing.
And we just need a name with an e-mail with us and a password.
I think that validation is actually good enough.
So we just need to submit the correct data to a post and point.
OK.
So let's try this out.
Registar new use off I'm just going to try to register them for myself.
So seems like it was actually passing the correct data on.
Right.
So what are we going to do such really generate a new username for the user.
So I want my user to have a user name and the main reason why we're doing all of this is so that you
see how you can actually override the system and customize it to your needs.
OK so I want a user name for my field but I want automatically generated from the Forni.
So why would you still control to make sure that when I'm creating a user I also actually create a user
name field so username and automatically generate the username from the name.
So strange SLOC dates on name.
And obviously this is not really feel right because we don't yet have this field in our database so
why don't we actually drive this with a test.
So I'm just going to credit this out and I'm going to create a new test.
So we have to son make test registration test.
OK.
So you know a registration test and write a test run up public function it or use has a default user
name after registration.
So we actually tested this functionality because it's not provided to us by Lavoe by default.
And once Michel we had actually you know making an errors.
So how is this squinch look we're going to create a new user or actually make a post request to our
register controller and points and I said that the database actually has a use or with a particular
username.
Let's see how this is going to look.
This post to slash registar.
I mean it'll pass you know.
And we were getting passed in name is going to be my name and we're going to post in an email.
And we need to pass a password.
And at the end of that request that's just a search statues of 200.
And the assertion augment a session we won't so actually do is assert that the database has a particular
user.
So we're going to be finding in the use oste more on the really passing in is going to see find the
user using the username and we can pass in the streets location of my name because that's what we want
right.
So we are not passing in any username here but what we just Rhaetian we want to make sure that there
is a username field and there exists a user whose username is actually this username.
And I think that's going to make sure that the registration process takes care of this username.
OK so let's go ahead and try to run this.
So be in it for this coming up.
And sure enough it feels better since we received a tweet or two rather than 200 because you read a
letter or we just use the controller.
We actually are retreating to use us to this path.
If the registration is successful so follow assertions we really shouldn't be searching for 200 which
we are searching for three or two or we should actually Corda said redirect method.
So that's wrong.
And now we achieve half what we expect.
Right.
So it's study knows that filled assorting that you wrote in the table we use as much as to attribute
username is this.
Right.
So let's go ahead and start by actually making sure we yes a user name for the user on the fly.
So strange lock and he's going to taking data on me.
OK.
So we are actually passing the username and just so we don't have to go through the cycle of violence.
We know we need to actually provide this you know create these.
So let's go ahead and take care of that immediately.
So let's quickly use field table.
It's going to be a simple stream and I'm going to make that unique one last stop or use a factory.
We have to make sure the dosage and who eats the username on the fly.
So we don't have to figure.
So there should be strings long and you're taking names.
So what I can actually do is create a name to be able to be close to a fake name and we're going to
reference it here.
OK.
That's all it's asked.
That's one of the tests and see what we get.
Looks like we haven't ever chickened out and it seems that's giving us an Taguchi country in violation
because this username is actually not seeped into the database and that should be coming from our users
or the PSP which does not permit the Masao Simon exception.
So what we should do is show each other love will flock flat as an arrow.
OK.
Run that again.
And sure enough we are back.
GREENE So looks like everything successful with Telecom customization after registration.