Are like this to go street you naturally start to make use of a vacation.
So I want to shoot an email to the user as soon as Chris and I count and we're not going to give him
access to anything until he actually confirms his e-mail address.
Now let's just go ahead and use a test to bring this functionality so we have to actually think about
what we want to implement.
So as an e-mail he sends to newly registered users.
OK so how would we want to know.
Let's just see which stuff you use.
And then we assert that a particular e-mail was sent.
That's all going to be doing.
So stop a question and use up or actually registering a user which means I'm going to be visiting my
endpoints.
So basically isn't.
So as soon as the user is I'm start to assert that mail was sent.
So looks like we're going to be meeting our middle seat from now on.
And what are we going to be doing is actually seeing Lovelle please switch out and Millward rival and
give us a fake.
And if we want to actually know what these feet methadose let's have much more with that PSP which is
lunette support for seats and actually see that we have this week met.
And most of the proceeds will actually have this fee method.
So it simply swapping the old regional mail handler with a fake We're getting it from support system
fix.
So what's more fake all the magic happens.
And what is simply going to do is send in messages.
It's not going to do that.
So for example if we check out a Senate vote on this morphic last what is up and NE's chasing the view
that we have to send data on a callback.
And then what it does is simply pushes the view that we passed into a millibars.
Are we right.
It's not sending emails at all.
So what is going to happen is if we call us sense mid-thought it's going to check if the view of the
millibar that we passed into the I said since mid-thought actually exists on the Malibu's are we right.
OK.
So let's go ahead and use this so much attrition we fiqh them a lot.
So it's going to swap out and the most of me.
And then right here we can call us at St..
So M. assert that a mail was sent and the name of this e-mail is going to be confirmed.
Your email last.
OK so for now let's just make sure that this e-mail is sent.
Now let's just run that test expected to confirm your e-mail mailable was not sent right so filled such
false is true.
Let's send this email on how are we going to do that.
That said to you John registration.
And we're going to take a look at what happens at this event new we saw saw history.
And that's also a registar method.
And these were just them or just like authenticates at mid-thought.
It's a simple gives us to do something once the registration is complete.
So let's head what's all rigid Stoss are going to override this method.
So right down here I'm going to paste nothing.
And what they want to actually do is make sure that I also redirect after I'm done with that method.
Right because now we're going to call this method and then it's going to be that way for us.
So you know register all of us for everything I need to do make sure I return this redirect path.
So this is where I'm going to be sending my e-mails so mail send.
And before we actually call to send mid-thought Let's call the two men thought to pass in this use object
and we're receiving to a user who just got we just got into this my thought so now to this user send
a new that's had much of what's asked.
And Michel we had the same e-mail.
So new you confirm your email mailable.
So you bought that.
And I know it's going to break because we don't yet have that loss but let's let access to us that.
But the BBC was actually not helpful.
So what are we going to do is simply attach and US-CERT redirects to this myth up right here and lovely's
of how much can actually fit with this test and then tell us what is going on.
So let's try that and see his response to US 500.
It's not a redux That's a school at 500.
So we need to just.
Exception handling so we can see what the 500 is all about.
OK.
Run that again.
And there we have our role.
It seems like women want us to there we just thought must be an instance of oh I'm sorry.
That should be because we haven't imported this at the top.
Let's go ahead and make sure we do so.
So use Lumi S2P request one that again.
OK.
Now it's also she can find that confirm email.
So let's go ahead and read that we are sent mail confirm your e-mail.
And while I'm here I'm just going to generate a map down you for that.
So it's going to be e-mails that confirm your e-mail but let that be.
And I like that convention where this actually matches your name.
OK so that's one that milkweeds that let's make sure we actually import the class at the top before
calling our test again.
OK.
So you know at M. tree sure enough we have this so use our mail actually but costs me to confirm your
e-mail.
Let's run that test again.
And now this is an error seen first feature confirm your e-mail was not sent.
OK.
So that's because we have also imported these in our test.
Right.
So let's go ahead and do that now.
Had a lot of my restrictions on us and used up at the top.
One that says it again and great looks like we have a successful test this time around.
So we are actually sending a user an e-mail every time he's registered right.
Do you use actually an e-mail to confirm his e-mail address.
But what about the underlying functionality that goes reconfirming e-mail addresses.
Let's tackle that in the next lesson.