That's such a you make a confirmation e-mail system work.
So we want to actually see if we're talking on the users table that belongs to the user not just where
you start.
And then if the user clicks on a link in his email then we're going to remove that token and then we're
going to have a middleware that checks if the users conform to Tcl is still in his database column.
So if it's not law then it means that user has not yet confirmed.
So let's go ahead and take care of it.
We thought that we might actually decide to stop too fast.
So let's go ahead and do that public function test or use has it all.
Can I salvage trillion.
OK so let's just start with this.
We need to just use.
Right.
So we're going to just fix the middle so it doesn't trigger the Confirm e-mail meal then right here
we're going to see this syrup Motson or for the use or confirm talken.
Right.
So we going to reference a user on the User class and make sure that it's not load because if it doesn't
exist then it's going to be No.
Right.
So I said that it's NOT.
Let's go ahead and run this test and see what we have just for a start.
I think we can do so feel towards you.
The new test my thought we have a message on Friday we will use our and this use of that we actually
are referencing here is the use of that was just Queechy it and we're going to get the use of by simply
fetching the first user.
Right because we are using the refresh database and it's going out to metrically refresh and create
a new use.
Once we have to gather for each user.
Now right here and all that.
So use but cost use zong.
Now let's head over to our seminar on tests and we have filled a search in that no it's not no.
Now then I'm always forced to make this property exist under use or clause.
We could just create a property but then I think I'm just going to go ahead and solve the problem because
we know what we need.
So head over to my queries of Steamboat and how much are you going to create a string field which is
going to be from Tolkien and I'm going to make sure it's not the rule book because I want to make it
all about when these are confirmed seats.
Eamon OK now that I've done that it's still not going to pass.
Let's head over to our registar our and you fill that field wants to use our registar so confirm talken
should be close to streambed random 10:5 contest.
Matsue show this is the name of the help of my father I will provide for us but we're going to see.
OK so generic 25:1 on card us store when confronted can field of the database.
And finally you know I use other B we need to make sure that level permits that field to be filled.
So that's one test one more time and see what we have.
OK so we have a successful test.
So it means we actually generating in disconfirm talking and inserting it into the database at registration
time.
Now now another assertion that I want to I try to run right here is just an assertion to make sure we
have help from my father.
Tell us if they use or is confirmed or not.
So I'm just going to see a assert false use or he's confirmed and I'll call this awesome method.
Let's run let's see what we have.
We actually have on the Find My thought is confirmed this is what we expected.
And you know we use the b b.
We're going to have this is going from mid-thought probably function is confirmed won the game and then
it sees fit as such and that is false because we truly nothing at the moment.
So which we cannot see which on this confirm so come across.
OK.
So you can Fonzo can it's more than we're going to see the use I can find because at which time we actually
few in this field.
Then if the user confirms himself then we're going to pull out the token and then make sure it's long.
OK.
So let's run this test again.
I should pass it right now and he does that for actually having our confirm right here.
Now what I would love to do is actually make sure that our e-mail order we are fairing contains the
token for the user right.
So we have to confirm your e-mail that bid may be a tree.
And this is simply above me level.
So we're just going to see one more step before join back cast and this is going to be.
We need you to confirm your e-mail and this is you can see confirm email and we're going to see thanks.
Config aptonym.
So let's just actually take this opportunity to change the name of the BHB in the configurator tree.
And here we have an app name that's just changed in that EMV.
So I'm going to change my theme park costs and that's you all to feel into the email please.
OK.
So we need these buttons actually click and take us some way.
And this is where we are actually going to verify to use on.
So I'm going to do it just yet.
But one final thing before we go we let's just take this opportunity to actually use one of Laufman
news future and that's actually on on the balls and the puzzle to see if this changes that we made that
really took effect.
So what headbutts or what the PH We were simply going to swap this out for now and we're going to return
the mailable.
So we turn new broadcasts merely confirm your email and let's see what we get.
So visit the home page and looks like what emotion is good enough right.
So we have seen one more step before we joined but cost we need to confirm your email.
And that's our motto on that.
Awesome.
So looks like everything works perfectly.
Thank you so much.
We're got to take care of actually confirming to you as you know in the next video.