Oh OK so I'll do the ones from the US.
We want to use that on this march on.
And we should actually take us to our results on our web application.
That's going to pick up the token.
So it might actually be a POST or GET request but probably get to work with.
So we're going to pass the token as a promise.
You know I get requests and then I pick it up with an obligation find to use that to come and make sure
we can from the use if we don't find and use then we're going to handle the kids.
So why don't we do this with some tests.
So let's just generate a new test.
So here are some quick tests confirm e-mail tests.
So let's head to whatsoe'er confound e-mail test and try another function on the superbly function sayst
a Yusof can confirm email.
Ok so how are we going to be doing this.
OK.
So how are we going to be good and then send that email of sending the e-mail whatever walks.
And then we'll make a get request to the confirm and then assert that they use all these confirm.
So let's go ahead and do that.
Create a use always Simplicio use or use for actually for own use or class Craigavon.
OK so right here let's just use but guess use of how we use or the next thing is to send that e-mail.
I don't think this is actually necessary in this test case.
So we just go ahead and make that Kate and Chris.
So we're going to see this gets.
And how do we want to you know we're just going to see registar confirm and remember like we agreed
we're going to be passing in the can into the get requests I support.
So what I'd like to do centrally use a better US and such right here so double Portes could simply on
sites where it's open he calls and hustling use are confirmed to come right here also.
So suspensory so rich you start confirm then pass in the can and for the response let's just assert
redirects and in this case we're going to be posting in the beach to make sure that you use such a newbie.
That's the home page.
We make that request so that essentially that makes it.
And we also have said that in USALS confirmed this a search through news or confront create a use or
make a request that in point person in the can.
And then I said that you use I should be directed to this point.
And then I said true that the user is confirmed.
So let's go ahead and do this.
I'm going to use Refresh database and I'm going to run this specific test only.
Ok that's funny.
OK.
So I was promised us I would fall for it's not that we don't make stuff to school.
Now if you want to have more information about it section those when you can actually disable exception
handling.
But now we know what's a full force which is squarehead Aquilius endpoint.
Right.
So you know what that BHB we want to create a routes gets which is a registar session for him.
And let's just say it maps to confirm.
Email construal Arts Index Mitha one on to gain share info.
We have a 500 but let's just go ahead and disable exception handling.
So this without exception mean that's funda.
Now we have more help for everyone that sees this control of us and they exists.
PH We Irish Sun Macon's long confirmed email.
Well now that that's created let's run the test again.
SUGI Sison all because we don't have the index misthought.
So let's just have to watch and confirm.
IMO controller and the next marathon run that one more time and we have 200.
It's not a direct at school because this is a skill we need to do because we have nothing here active.
So what do we want to do we need to get the token from the request to come and then we need to find
a use on where these two can lead.
So use on where I'm confused is equal to the token that we just got then.
Let's just check if we have a user then see user or confirm which is a helpful methadose and begin to
help us confirm the news.
And then we turn directs to the homepage.
OK.
So can they use a way that confirms or can exist or can that we get from the request.
And then we turn these up to the home page.
OK let's try out another area.
Colchicine you find coming from that's expected.
So it generally means know use.
So you know use all the Ph.D. there's just create that confirm with a public function for one audience
and we still have an interesting course on the Feynman fought on the ground you know confirm and that
should be my fault because these are which Strawson Kraybill that instance right.
So let's just get the first use of which is to the result from the query one that says we have green
that's so unexpected.
Let's DeBoer and see what we have.
First of all you know comes from email.
We are such an a redirects that's died on the use of right to see what it gets.
And the thing is we're actually essentially.
The thing is actually such actually on reaching the conference could say we forgot or did not.
So our factory needs to generate a confirmed token for the news stream pattern for us and less for not
just now and see what we get.
Our key expected LR feel a sense that false is true.
Because obviously right here on he's returning false because we are confirming the news.
And we are trained.
True.
So you know that we all we need to do is confirm the news right here.
So these confirm tokin equals.
And we just need to save those changes.
That's it.
OK.
So we pull out to confirm so can such an all.
And then we see if the user objects and hopefully notwork says should pass.
So let's run that test one more time and we still have a feel and I'm going to show you why we have
Freedia because when we get the use I'll just wait here even after we updated level does not refresh
its copy for the test rate so it's not like it's cost.
So what we're going to do is use law was Freshmeat thought to get a fresh copy from the database because
we the check and then would see what we get.
Let's run again.
And yeah we have green.
Okay.
So let's go through the system again to see what we have we have this new test can confirm email and
what this is doing such and making sure that the Zicam confirms even now we quit use up and after doing
that we make sure that we use are actually actually generates confronted for that.
So then we make a good question that points passing in the token to that Mithal.
Right.
As I said maybe that's a decent beach meaning that was successful.
And then also as such would not be Yousaf is confirmed.
And if we check over so our use of PH We we have that is confronted with all the checks from toucans
and all I know confirm mid-thought that actually sets that second to none.
Then we have all confirmed the smoke.
We simply gets the token finds a use of the token and then come from news use and we directly use the
home page.
So we could actually in line the so we don't create useless we will and it's going to work.
So let's want access one more time and that's good.
We're good to go.