Now let's do some clean up and finally test our system my own test.
I want to include one assertion and that's the assertion to make sure that we have a session.
So a set session costs success and this success should actually say your email has been confirmed.
OK.
So let's work on that test and sure enough we don't have that session said.
But let's head over a confirmed email control and set up this session session.
Flash success and the value for the key should be this string like your kids.
So let's run that one more time.
And we're back to green.
OK so waiting we write a test for when things go wrong test or use all these redirector.
If so can be is wrong.
So we'll just do exactly the same thing create or use or make a request to that end point.
But this time on whether that person in the right tool can read just cannot pass in wrong token and
we're going to run some assertions so assert redirects to hold.
And we also assert session horse and error key and that he sees for mation.
So can mark.
We cognized.
OK.
So that's what happens when the talking is not correct.
Let's go ahead and one that says already and sure enough we have a feeling because we 22:00.
Now let's head over to our controller and then you know what else block is simply going to see session
flash Iraki.
And that message is going to be exactly what we have here.
Conformations who can not be customized and return redirects to the home page.
Arkie we have a successful test.
Final step.
Let's go ahead and make sure or confirm your email Matsen.
I tried the leads to that approach.
Right.
So we can actually simply use avouch name that sees confirm email.
And then in a way that we we just need to give these routes a name right.
So name confirm email and we should be good to go.
So for us it is this.
Let's go ahead and tweak it sets r.p.m. drop us.
That's a track to receive our emails copied and used only right here in my anyhow.
I'm going to be studying the mail truck usernames is going to be here.
Copy the password and I'm going to put it here.
OK so that's basically all I need to send e-mails.
And now if I tried this out in the Masayoshi that it truly truly got via e-mails I think I left out
something and that's in our template we need to actually pass in the token Trudy's you know what we
could do here is just concatenate this to where a token equals and still concatenate these to use or
confirm token.
So we actually in of Heartbeat token to that Motson for us to actually have access to the user.
We need to head the virtual Me level and actually receive it right because the properties that are existent
on these Magdalens simply are the public properties of this class.
Therefore we need to set up a public use our property and we see it in here.
So use and this user because user I'm just going to be generic right here.
But of course you can take into to make sure you've not seen any subtle beats.
Then we need to go to whoever is sending this mail which is in all registar control.
You know we just stopped mid-thought and we need to pass in the user.
OK.
So confirm your email and will post in the news.
So we have access to that user who will confirm your email the bleep that it should be.
OK.
So let's make this walk or visit maybe just about rigid state test.
And that takes the whole means no loss.
Let's check out that Chanoff we have an e-mail to test our test at converso but cost one more step before
joining us from your e-mail.
And right now we discovered that this e-mail actually is Fosi need to talk and right.
So let's click on it takes us to that end point.
And he says an error.
I commenced to function this.
OK.
So this is simply because remember we switched out this route just to test out confirm your e-mail functionality.
But everything's OK.
Perfect.
OK.
So when you clicked on from your e-mail you got to really get that done.
Now let's just check out our database to make sure that the news is confirmed so our users get on off.
And so it's not options but cost run that and we see the conference or can you not.
So it means we have one confirmed use in our system.