I think be good for the coffee just of authentication.
Why don't we go into something much fun each actually has to deal with serious lessons of loading juice
on all of that.
OK.
Let's get started.
So looks like we're going to need a serious model for our series which are sun make models TVs and they
need a migration for that.
Not that's generator.
Let's go ahead on my question and see what we are going to be having.
OK so I want the series to have a title.
I also wanted to have a SLOC and I wanted to have an image field.
So I'm actually going to be storing the image for all four paragraphs.
I want to have a short description and I think that's going to do it for now.
So we have a title SLOC and this is simply kind of like a a presentation of the title than the image
or a description.
I'm going to head over to my series model and I'm simply going to make sure that I remove my Simon protection
so protect that guarded because MTOE then I'm going to generate a factory for this series.
I think there are some common the commissary 5:25 for this.
So P-H be Arsen me factory.
There we go.
So he would be our sun make for tree.
And this is just going to be serious factory Asaf.
So let's head over to see restruck free and what do we want.
We want the title and this is going to be focused intense we can pass in a number of words into this
my thought.
We can also pass in the SLOC and what we could do is actually save the focus and then into a variable
such that Pasquin a title here and then we the title to be watchful focus sentence and we just need
to reference same variable right here.
Then for one image you are all we can use this Ficarra image you are on I thought and we can pass in
the dimensions of the image or just make it for us.
And finally we need a description.
So Flaker Bargo are a record on method.
OK.
So that's a treat.
We can now generate fake Sui's to be able to use both.
And yeah we need to update this right.
So but cause serious loss.
Now the next video let's go ahead and see how we could do accrete beat bit of Britain's elite four series.