We don't waste any time.
We dice tweeting to seen how we can or should prepare a forum so we can create series.
So the demonstrators are going to be able to do this but we can all come out like lieto.
OK so I have my block on suggestion and I'm simply going to pull this one from there and then I'm going
to formatting.
So block inserts and looks like I'm looking for contact too.
So just copy of this section I want to create a new view so I can literally create my form in that.
So in my view Socius views are mean directory.
I'm going to have a tree and I'm going to create that bleep that Ph.D..
And this is where I'm actually going to be stopping everything the concerns on us.
So I create that.
So I mean she was under a tree.
I'm just going to Piscina my phone there.
Oh and by that we extend the then four section.
It's going to be the content section.
OK so looks like we also need a header section and I'm looking at this quote for you beach.
The beach would for you to assume and I'm going to copy the header that you have here.
OK.
So what I want to do is actually register some quotes that are going to be in charge of everything administrates
or everything creating series.
So while it's up and I'm going to preface this with an injury and I'm going to change this to a good
method that's going to create the group for us.
Crossing a cruel joke on the kind of carry on definitions.
So watch resource because I'm going to be Christian reading of the tenens elite in series with us Rojos
to find a resource.
And this is going to be our series and it's going up to a Swiss controller class.
So why don't I just create that class right now.
So Peachtree and sun make control of serious control and are told are able to create and so forth.
We saw such an awesome.
So if I had was my series controller for us to view the routes that it's going to display that page
let's just return of you.
So it's in the admin directory that is a tree that creates Marchi and I like when this Mithal matches
this thing.
OK.
So let's go ahead and see what we get from viscid slash series solution creates Chanoff.
We have that view.
But that winner has a pretty terrific Ani's.