That's the Kalf actually quit in our series nursery school.
We need to think about how we want to handle this.
So this is us toman thought level of Muscatine Jex and then up the request that contains all the request.
So now we have to maybe do things like validation rules like here are actually building the image inside
here and saving us so the database just inside this method.
So what I actually like to do is create custom requests just for obl. a series or actually creating
a series.
So R-La. validation rules are going to be there all our policies are going to be there and maybe some
of the logic that we have to use to create a series.
So let's go ahead and then read up on his son make request create serious requests so we can go to a
great series we Quest right now and we're actually going to inject an instance of this class into our
series controller.
So rather than these We're going to take hands and level is still going to give us an instance of this
class and simply are quite serious requests extends the formal request by law.
So we're going to be able to maybe customize some live settings right here but we're still going to
have access to the underlying requests.
OK.
We need to use not so use but cost HGP Quest's and that's to create Sui's request class.
OK so how do we want this to work.
Let's just discuss the request last.
And I'm just going to change this chatroom and this otherwise my thought is actually a method to determine
if they use less or twice to make these requests.
And this is one of the flexibility that quitting customer request gives us.
So we can actually run a middleware or run a particular check here to see if they use something straight
off or if he's authorized to create a series.
And then this is automatically going to protect us rather than having complex statements it will control
us and we can also have our Nation host right here.
OK.
Now what are we going to do is a lot to follow.
So we want to upload the file that was sent to us.
The second thing we need to do is create the series.
And finally we're just going to redirect use up to a page to see our series.
So how are we going to upload the file.
Now our tickets are below that for instance and that is what we get when we are truly on the.
And that's.
Eliminate S2P overloaded file and I'm going to walk it through some thoughts that we have.
So now provide us with this fake which is for testing and we're going to see that the.
Now we have this for that saw the overloaded fire on a farm system disk right then.
This caused us tossed meth off behind the scenes and looks like this store is simply a wrapper under
our eyes.
And he provided a hashed name for our fire buddy who called us toss method directly.
We can actually pass in a custom name then.
Looks like we also have some publicly file so sort of blow the file on a farm system just with public
visibility.
So maybe if we wanted to display the image the top level would permit us to do that.
Then we also have also publicly as found which would actually let us customize the name of the file.
So you see the stop publicly simply hushes a name and gives to us.
But the public the US simply gives us the possibility of passing on them.
So it looks like this is what we want.
So start publicly us he's going to store it on a discreet public visibility in a very simple way for
us.
So we're going to see major cross requests M.H. because that's the name we are using in our form and
as a public it us and we need to pass in the path and the name.
Right.
So let's pass in a bath.
We simply wanted to being a series of a tree and the name should maybe be strings SLOC of the request
title.
Right.
We're going to get back to this in a short while but I just want this to work.
And we're going to customize this the way it's supposed to be.
OK.
So we're passing in a name right here on the directory We want to see if that then we need to quit the
series right.
So let's just say serious great passing on a rate of title.
It's going to be request title description which is going to be request description and we have to take
care of this image.
You are so field.
So I'm just going to see you are off now.
OK.
Then they use lots of peach to see our series.
So return redirect Mike just for now.
OK.
We're going to be coming back to customized days later on.
But what we want to do is try to see this walking.
And I think this is going to break.
Let's just go ahead and try it out and see what we get.
Let's import CBS then.
That's our.
We need to make sure we talk about forms of sodomy to the right to out.
So let's see our rock list.
So let's see what the East looks like the name for the post is serious that's all.
So let's go ahead and make sure that this points to sou'west that strong squad routs series that's tall
and will provide a token our case so let's try this out and see what we get with fresh new series of
Lauda found description and creature.
And we have an integrity constraint volition under SLOC.
And I think that's my forte because we're trying to create a series without Potsie and those SLOC.
Right.
So we have to make sure we pass in a slog right here.
But looks like the image of Lord was utterly successful.
We're going to check that out in a moment.
So request title strength's law that squarehead and check disk to see if we actually had an email that
says store each public we have a series directory and we have new series right here.
But we don't have the extension right so that's what I was talking about right here.
But looks like it blows pretty well and we're going to take care of the extension very soon.
So let's make sure this works and then we'll take care of these little new series again.
FLATOW Lord description great series.
OK so we're redirected back to the speech.
Seems like everything worked perfectly.
So now why don't we take care of all the image off in the next video.