OK let's work a little we don't follow us.
Now I want to get the class extension and make sure I Possy into this name concatenated so requests
M.H. get a regional extension.
Squeege give us an extension but rather than making two calls to our request last we can just naturally
see these into available.
So we're just going to see that image Igor's request M.H. then we can reference this right here and
do.
Right.
So we get to that image so it publicly.
Another option for us is to use us.
So my thought and Mitchellville story into the public disk but we'll look at this little one between
the just fleeting images.
And then it starts into a series directory on the name of the fire east the strings long for the title
and it attaches the click and regional extension rights and forms of PNU is going to such that if it's
GBG then you're going to touch that.
OK so once that is saved we now know the name of the file.
So this is the name of the father it's going to be saved for us.
Right.
So what we could do such really see a name right here because this and then pass in finding and rather
than saving the e-meter or a sergeant making a saving us service because we know that it's going to
be in the service directory then concatenates will probably.
OK.
So we have the file which is that far loaded in each instance we get the found him by attaching title
street SLOC version to the original Klann extension.
And then we loaded the file into a directory and passed the filename and then we created the series
and why quitting the series.
We make sure we specify the image or a series concatenated with defining and we redirect the user back.
So let's try this out in the browser and see what we get.
Another series below the file and I see another series description which you wish I were redirected
back.
Now let's talk about food.
So in our story each up there actually we have this and JP G which isn't.
So what we should make sure we do is actually have a full stop.
MITCHELL That's an extension and that's going to fix that error then let's use CT to check out our database.
We are Sun Shingo and we're going to get that cost series and I'm just going to get our Okay so it looks
like we're all actually was successfully possed but without the points right here that's as simple as
what we made or finding changes.
Right here we are in this extension and then looks like everything is going to work out.
So try this all more time and then they're going to write a feature to us to make sure it works.
So final series in our series description of the fire great series where we directed back checkouts
in car and looks like we have a Jeep that is Miss height for imagery.
Check out the file extension.
And sure enough we have an image that was on Lol that looks perfect.
So was actually quitting a series is walking.
Why don't we write some features as to make sure we never break anything in future.