Give it some thoughts and I'm going to quit Neuter's.
Catch me areason make just.
And this is simply going to be crazy test.
OK.
So let's head the rather creates the mistrust and what do we want to do.
We want to make sure that our store method works perfectly right.
So public functions as a user can create a series.
OK so what we want to do.
Let's Checkout our series control and looks like we already know how it's going to walk.
So we want to make sure that we actually upload a photo of that Gladys.
And we want to make sure that we actually have a series that is a blend and we want to make sure that
we will debate the use of particular needs.
So let's go ahead and try that functionality.
So first of all we need to make a post request to an endpoint.
We all know the end point which is it means passing a rate of the time.
So we have a title.
So we're just going to see jurors for the best.
It's the title of our series description.
It's going to be best VGX cost ever.
And remember we are all building an image.
So why don't we get an ad for instance from novel rights with this fake metho that is actually going
to create an image for us.
So we could call fake M.H..
Let's just have to watch in a class so low that we need to know that we have a fake metho and this simply
cease testing fire factory on the fight for freedom agenda reads an image for us.
OK.
So did fire fake.
And then he's going to give us an instance of fire factory.
And if we had a box of five factory it's going to actually create an image for us.
So image is going to give us new file and it's going to college and wait image Mithal that's going to
get us back to our test our fake image.
We can't specify the dimensions and we can also satisfy the need.
So if we check out the MH mid-thought you know for archery he takes it in the name Neue on the hige
right.
So that's the name of the phone so he can be whatever name.
So we're just going to see EMH series that PMG then we need to import bit of that right.
So you think it's from the HGP of that file.
Let's check that out.
Yeah.
It's then let's just assert every direction to make sure everything was successful then what we could
do is actually assert our games our storage to make sure we have to really have something in our storage
right.
So that will price reduced each week and it's going to fake astore each.
And what the fix is going to do it for headbutts of storage that Ph.D. the fiqh method is going to give
us a clean directory to work with.
And if we don't know this is going to get the system's default Geske and this is simply going to help
us to clean the tree give us the fresh new juice to work with.
And a lot of other stuff.
So let's go ahead and work with that.
So we fixed the storage and now it gives us access to the start of each disk and we could specify the
dish that we want to check against.
And once we make sure that the disk which was fine here is the one we faked.
So let's just go ahead and walk with that for disk.
So config file systems that default.
So you know for systems that we actually have this default key right here that specifies the default
system is supposed to use that case local so-called feek file systems that default is going to give
us that.
And we could actually parse exactly the same thing right here.
OK.
Then we call a set exists method which level provides for us and I'm going to show you where that mid-thought
exist really fosterling a all now will illuminate a tree in our farm system.
We can see we have a file system up to try and find assert exist mid-thought.
There we go.
So assert that the fire exists in quiet osteopaths in a bar or the particular file that we try to find
and then it's simply going to use unit Asatru to check if they exist.
Right.
So let's go ahead and use not.
So right here we need to parse the path that we use to load the file.
And we already know we need to get the streets lock of the title.
So why don't we just copy this title right here and we need to also add such an extension.
Concatenate these two dots puji that's the extension we use and right here.
And then we have to also make sure we concatenate the directory to which we are good at that.
OK so we know we want to see which directory tree and we know we want the filename to be the stream
slot of the title.
And we also we want attached or regional extension of the overloaded farm.
Right.
So we are going to assert that it exists and we're also going to assert that we have some database entries
but for now let's go ahead and run this test and see where we are.
We have before.
I'm sorry about that.
This store is to be series obviously that's run that test.
We have 500 let's just emote exception handling to see that all this without exception handling.
Why not test again.
No such table series.
We need to use a fresh database so you use Refresh Eastridge one that says again.
OK.
And it successfully passes meaning that this test for the that far succeed in.
But we also check if we actually have the post on a CBC in each of these.
Right.
So this search the database has in the series table a SLOC war or a war where the SLOC is strings log
of view yes for the best.
OK.
So this is a title we want to make sure that if we check in to see researchable actually going to find
a field where the law is this exact same strange loan value.
Right.
That's one that's asked what I'm asking.
And that was successful.
So we are successfully testing our Lord and we also testing our database record store each.
That's if you factor in the very next video.