Like I mentioned a couple of years ago I'm not really comfortable with having a lot of lines in my control.
Actually most of my projects actually make show my controller has a maximum of three or four lines that
do a paragraphing.
So what I'm going to do is actually extract these image load into my Create Sui's request so creates
a least request that BHB is going to have a public function which says upload Seeley's image and I'm
going to cut out the functionality from my control up and pasted right to sue GET request image is going
to be this image because we have to request this title so upload that image use this image file image.
Is this title with the extension.
And then we stop publicly as Seely's and repassing the finding then what we could do is simply return
this then we're going to be able to actually change this method.
Right.
Then what I want to do is create a public method that says so.
Sui's OK.
So we have to upload series image.
So I'm gonna copy this functionality out of my class and I'm going to paste this in.
So upload the image right here.
And looks like we need access to this finding.
Right.
So why don't we just call this it in this class so that we can actually use it in this other method.
This filename because of this and we're going to assess this filename and right here we're also going
to assess this finding.
OK.
So great.
And then we are assessing this Farney.
So now what are we going to have will control our ease request or built image or what was the name of
that thought of little CBC M.H. And once that's done we want to start Sui's right.
That's the methodically right sort of blog Seuss image and the start a series and then return to use
our back and now that we have access to it.
We can actually run a test to see if it's still successful.
So let's run that on to find three more requests.
And that should be coming from our Creasey which request let's check that out.
Yeah.
So everywhere we have requests we have to switch that out with this this and I think that looks very
tough that's one that says one more time and we have a successful test.
So we've actually be factored on the functionality of saving a series into our request class then in
our control we just have a bloats image and store series.
I think that's neat.
Quick Joe.