I want to modify it a little bit and then we're going to write some new tests to introduce the concept
of validation into our series creation.
Therefore in my Cretu is test right here I want to assert that this session has something.
So I said session hahs are successfully and this should be equal to series creature successfully.
OK so let's run that test.
And I think you should feel right now.
OK so there's no sessions set for series.
So let's have a robot or a controller and we could actually set up the Session right here.
So session called a flush mid-thought on the session class and this is going to see success key should
be quarter exactly the same stream that we have right here.
Let's run that again.
And sure enough we have gui.
Now one thing I want to point out in our test is we're simply testing a strategy that makes right here.
You remember if that's what you feel you are still going to be debated of.
We have a mistake on error we'd might still be redirected.
So to make sure that you have a successful test or a successful test that actually makes sense.
Make sure you specify a direct path.
So for example if you want to make sure that they use that to mean slushed series after the farly successfully
upload it or after the series is successfully created then make sure you specify a path and then in
your control to make sure when you're redirecting to use or you specify that we debate path.
Right.
So that for now I'm not going to worry about that because I want to write test for the validation.
OK so let's jump straight into it.
It's a public function test.
A series must be created with Title.
OK.
So how do we want to test this validation.
We want to make a post request.
We doubt the title field and then see if we are actually going to be redirected back with some errors.
OK.
So let's just copy this and I'm going to plug the title meaning we didn't pass in the title in the inquest
we simply passed in description and found and then we're going to assert we direct and a pathway such
that it was redirected to.
I mean Sui's create and we actually can test if the session has errors by using the US-CERT session.
It was my thought and we can specify that we want to check if there's an ever fall title.
OK.
So I said if we were invited.
So I said that the session has errors.
So let's go ahead and try this out with one specific test.
Yeah we have a 500 Let's go ahead and see what we have.
We just able exception handling to have a better eval so based that in wonder again.
Ever see since integrity constraint violation for the field title.
So it means we're actually trying to create the series We the title meaning our foundation was are not
evil.
So let's head over to our controller and we see right here we are actually referencing a custom object
therefore we can reference some additional moves in our Carstone object.
So create serious request and what we could do is right here we have our wars array so we can see title
should be required.
OK let's run that test one more time.
And the arrow that given the time was involved.
So it was a validation exception.
Now what we can to do is head of about two hours SEST and plug this method.
And I think our tests actually succeed our Southern US field as such in lots of streams much and it's
telling us this is what we expected.
But this is what we have.
Can explain why he does that later but for now let's just pull out this assertion for redirects and
simply assert that the session house was run at.
Yeah and of course we get green.
Let's wait another test to make sure that it's created with a description.
So I'm just going to duplicate this on the Test series be created with a description and rather than
passing in a description here will pass in a title and make sure that the session has a process for
description.
OK.
So that's one that it fails but let's try to put you in addition for description so description must
be required.
If that run the test again.
And of course it passes.
Now let's just do one more for our image.
But I think the image is going to have to but let's just do one more duplicate dart and we're going
to pull out that image in this case I'm passing the description and show you see it's isoceles was created
with an image.
OK.
So I said assertion house was for image that's run a test it fails.
Let's make sure we have a variation we'll for image should be required to run that test.
Yeah.
And it is.
Now why don't we make sure that the image must be an image so let's duplicate this test and actually
pass in the image in this case.
So I'm going to copy this of that file.
But we're going to pass in streams stream in a valley.
MH OK then we're going to assert that you have arrows for image and you can also assert that the error
is actually of a particular type but we're just going to leave it as such then require is the only foundation.
So let's run that fast.
I'm sorry I didn't change the name.
So with an image which is actually an image run it fails.
But let's just try to put in an image validation to see what we get.
Run it one more time and we pass.
Now law also provides us with a way to test for the dimensions of the image but we're not going to worry
about that now.
I think this test would actually make sure that we upload a correct image and the user can create a
series with a title description and an image with a valid image also.
So great job in this video.
Let's make some progress in the next one.