This once in our project Lycos is that thinking about how we want to manage administrators and locks
and use us.
So before we jump students anything we got a quick acustom the weather this week to make sure that only
authenticated at ministry just can create a series visit the pages to view August.
The reason the backhand and Sanch stuff so let's go ahead and Jean who eats or work which we sent make
middleware at Main Street so you can call these whatever he wants or you want it.
OK that's what's up for us.
Buttons are cool if you head over to our administrates or class.
It's easy to sum up me to where we have.
So let's head over to our current on the beat which is for the SGP and we're going to reinstall a new
middleware.
So right on the bottom I'm going to save this as a green class and it's going to be in the broadcast
HTP media where the retreat and it's going to be up in streets of glass.
So that's when we just stop let's sit and watch over me to wait and see how we want to walk.
First of all I would like to create a cost from conflict for our for our project.
And this is the last talk project based conflagrations and we're going to do this now.
I don't want to create an administrator or team or unsafe or mistreat dozens in a day.
Therefore I think saving and us in that way will do.
And it's going to solve the policies for this lesson.
Right.
So we're going to save our administrators and an army and then this may be the way it is going to check
if the authenticated use or the calling of integrated user is actually in that way.
Right.
So let's go ahead and do this now for us to quit a conflagration fire.
We just need to call into our config directory and create us right config backcross.
But that's the name on the front.
OK.
So there it is.
So we just need to create the screens and return an array just like any of the other configurations.
Be a superscript of each scenario.
OK.
So this email is going to contain key administrates us and it's going to contain e-mails of administrators.
For example if I want Cutty for islands of calm to be in the streets or then I'm going to Puchi into
this key.
Ok then.
Anyway project we can actually access this using Loblaws can help our method.
Therefore right here what we want to do is first of all check if these sites authenticated.
Then we're going to check if they use Eyssen and Mean Streets.
If not then we're going to redirect these on to some beach or somewhere would start by saying if just
check that in either the use Eisin in the streets or.
So let's rephrase this Mithal on the use A-Class.
So we get the authenticated user.
In this case we call he's admin and this mythical tell us if they use such Yulian on this region.
So if he's an administrates or then suply then a return next request soon would allow the user to go
to the next stage of the application right or continue to where he was actually heading to.
Then if the user was not permitted then reason to return redirect to the home page.
OK.
And also in this case we also want to direct these parts to the beach.
You never want to allow your middleware hanging.
Right.
So if this clinician feels it should actually have something to run if not your meter is going to be
hanging really bad case.
OK.
So if they use a authenticates that you go back to the home page if the user is authenticated is not
in the streets or you are Sukumar homepage.
But if the user isn't on the streets then he's going to pass the state of the onion and go to the next.
OK.
So that's Chris that mid-thought use of Ph.
That's great and it's East administrates on it.
And this will simply return Inari.
And this in a real mess don't appear to be mid-thought and takes in and you don't.
And we're going to pass in this e-mail and the haystack is the army itself.
So we pass in the email and we pass him can feek back us up a ministry just acida Peyster.
Right.
So we have an army of a ministry to us which is right here in the broadcast configuration we have an
administrator key and it contains an army of all it contains the emails of all administrators.
Then in a Yusof class we have this it's a minimum thought simply checks if the common use are actually
useful in the army.
So if it's not on this Army this means it's going to return false.
OK.
So looks like our middleware was just fine checks if the uses then it just allows the user to go through.
If not then you choose the user.
OK.
So let's go ahead and implement this middleware in our Vauxhall.
So right here we have a group of I mean what we want to do is attach a middleware to this group and
this is going to be the admin made aware.
So this is coming from our cannot appear to be just like the registry.
OK.
So this was caught me but cost nothing exactly what with infringing on CROSSFIRE.
So not like that.
This is the route that comes from that route.
So who headbutts where this is when you stop in Iraq.
Try to refresh up each night and see where that's speech because the use us non-acting.
So quick refresh and we were directed it's the homepage.
But if you log in right now we don't have any use of Socky.
I'm just going to read just still want.
So my name is Cotty.
Emily Scace of the friends column and the post-war response to stock are direct That's a home and it
actually took a while because I think it's actually sending the e-mail.
We asked it to send.
Now let's try to recede at Mitsui secret beach and we actually visited the beach right.
Men who come to our broadcast configuration and actually pulled out the issues us email from the administrators
at least and tried to refresh the beach particularly with Democrats.
The home beach Minn. D'Souza Hasan mossies administrator privileges.
So I think for a project where we don't have our means the gist of many rules of administration.
This was just perfectly.
So now that up wouldn't that use a park as an industry.
I'm going to try Visi that vault again and sure enough I have.
So I mean a way it's working perfectly.
Why don't you write some tests for me the way in the next lesson.