Foster test that you were actually watched correctly it was simply going to pass in or try to visit
the route like this from our test and make sure that the use is reiterate that accordingly.
So you know are creating serious to us.
We just want to create a new test that sees test only administrators can create serious.
OK.
What we need to do here is generate a user second visit and point and then assert we are redirected.
So let's create that user user because factually for use our class and would create the use of a system
then this anti-Nazis up.
So let's slogging the up to make sure that it's actually I mean the streets are really off them.
The weather feels then we'll try to visit the end points.
So this last act means last series then we don't really need to pass in the data on right because we
and the data are going to be parsing.
We could actually duplicate the detail we have here.
So I'm just going to copy this army based that in and then I'm going to assert that we actually have
an Air Force session.
OK.
So I said stationhouse.
And they should match a message saying you are not authorized to perform this action.
We can also assert redirect to the home page.
But I think this one would do.
So let's go ahead and run this test singlehandedly.
OK.
So we get a field searching that no much is expected.
This means our session is not actually set.
Right.
So let's go ahead to our administrator me to wear and said that session.
So if they use ice and I don't agree on the streets or sesshin flush and the key is going to be narrow
and the volume is going to be exactly the stream that we have in our tests so I'm just gonna copy this
paste start writing and safe.
Why not ask one more time and there should be a difference.
We received the same thing and it looks like it's my fault.
This code is unreachable.
It should be before our return of course.
Run it one more time.
OK.
So we have a successful test.
That's it.
It's working.
Bert do we really need to actually pass in all of these dates are in our request.
Let's just pull this out and see if our test is going to work nonetheless.
OK so it works.
That makes our task look a little cleaner and we could actually in line this user and bring these streets
online and run the tests again to make sure we do not break anything.
And it looks like we're good.
If we run a test suit just to make sure we haven't broken any other parts of our application.
Yeah.
We have a couple of failures.
OK so let's go ahead and see what's going on.
Field asserting that no matches expected series quite successfully and another bunch of arrows.
So let's go ahead and handle this in the very next video.