We ended up having to deal with these aerostat wars as soon as we applied our admin middleware.
So let's go ahead and handle it in this video.
And it seems like all of our tests that have to do with our building on CBS are failing because we need
to actually log in and treat all before doing this right.
So why don't we actually log in the administrator right away before doing the test for us.
We need a user right so far we generate a warning for the use of force and would that second we need
this user to be an administrator but then we have that config array that actually does this so how can
we tell of all these years I should be an administrator.
Let's head over to our config class provided by Lovell to see if we can find a way to do this.
So it was a treat that Ph be.
And actually if you bought it office you know in the luminal configuration we would have this repository
that ph be where the config class itself exists.
OK.
So that class that implements the contract.
So let's browse the methods that we have here.
We have a husky or Hussman thought.
Get my folks get M.F. up a sudden thought a pre-planned method.
And I think what we are looking for is actually this method.
So push a value on one way configuration value and actually if you go through the Java documentation
you notice that it's highly recommended to actually push to the config or set to the config at runtime
rather than mocking the config class.
OK so let's go ahead and do this.
So we have our config Fasi and we can get to the push mid-thought and we're pushing to but cost that
ministry to us.
That's the reason we have you know buy cars of BHB.
Then we are pushing a value and that value should be the use that we just created.
And he's email right.
So creative use of course they use us email to the administrators are we.
And then finally what we want to do is allow the user or eat right.
So this acting us use on so before one is there let's just make sure we import our use config at the
top then let's run out the test.
Or you can add redounds for filling tests.
OK so this last one is actually succeeding because we are an administrator.
And we have the right to do this.
So we didn't duplicate in this solution every single place we want to on the streets or why don't we
create a cross.
Tom administrates all men thought that is going to help us logging in an administrator.
What I want to do is actually we're friends.
This logging I mean my thought and this is going to join with an administrator and lucky me.
OK.
So I'm just going to cut this out.
So where do we put this.
We have a case that BHB if we check out this extents desk or we can use test case and test cases and
or a test or a tree.
So let's head over to that directory test that case the Ph.D. and we can put that in a public function
plugging at mine and paste that functionality right there.
OK.
So we have a factory therefore we need to port our use our class so used by us use our then use config.
And I think that should do it.
All right.
So they use OUR make sure they use are created as an administrator and then not to use are in.
OK.
So that's what our logging admin thought does.
That's one that's a loan to make sure that it still passes and it does pass.
Therefore we just need to duplicate this solution to all our tests that we're feeling like this one
we need to be Latina's I mean streets before it works.
Same here same here same here.
And this one doesn't require that.
OK.
So let's run all our tests right now to see if we actually have a difference.
Great.
Looks like I should be successfully running.
And we finally fixed all errors.