Now let's jump into the car fabrication and that has to do with delayed with the lessons OK.
It's the fun part.
So I think I'm going to have a Lessons model so I can make model lesson and I need to my question with
this.
OK let's get that create lessons doable.
And how do I want this to be.
First of all I want the lesson to be long to a series.
So I'm just going to lean into each other and mops to squeeze ID but I want this to be optional.
So it means I can have stand and lessons if I'm going to meet this knowledge but then I'm also going
to see chaebol Stream.
And this is going to be the lesson title and I'm also going to have a lesson description which I'm going
to make a textfield So description and I should probably actually make sure the series description is
also text are you just going to be baseless then.
Another thing I want from my lesson is a place number.
So I'm going to create an airfield which is going to be the least number or we can actually name these
people that number.
Then finally I want a reference of the video on Vimeo.
So I'm going to see string and the string is going to be the video ID so video ID.
Now we're going to be serving our lessons or videos on Vimeo and then begin to saw a reference to a
video on the lessons table.
So for example if the idea on Vimeo was to do something whatever this is the number we can receive here
and then in our forms and we're going to grab a video with this ID and then present or use us then the
exact number is simply going to help us know how to arrange our suits.
Then in our lesson Gatsby just so we don't have any annoying ones we're going to make sure that this
is not protected from us assignment.
Now how do I want this to work.
Remember when we started working on our series controller the Shoma thought Walmsley use are truly Rife's
on this page to show page he's going to have a quick update and delete functionality for lessons for
that series.
And obviously for a better use I experienced this should actually be without refreshing pages or stuff
like that.
Right so we're going to use Vue just to make this really awesome.
So before we get to that let's just return of you from here.
So we turn to you and this is going to be a green or a tree and we have a starter in there an index.
So resources views mean Sui's index that blate Ph be.
OK so if we check out a directory structure Dessa index that late I'm just going to duplicate what they
have to create because I want almost the same header and the content is very similar but I'm just going
to pull out a form.
Yeah we should probably send the suicide data off from our controller.
So why don't we just pass in with series and pass in the C right here.
OK so now we're passing the series.
Therefore we can use a series title right here.
And this is going to be the page where we customize your series lessons and it's going to be a lot of
view just going on in here.
OK.
So that's what we see that beach.
So I mean seriously brush this course then do our experts here then we have the cost title then Carson
you serious lessons.
OK so we're going to actually switch to front and walk in the very next video and start customizing
our lessons right here.