All right let's get into a fun part.
This speech is going to have a quick update and the lead for our lessons.
Why don't we start with the read so before we start with the read.
Obviously we need to have some sort of coalescence into our database before we proceed.
So let's go ahead and create a class for our lesson ph meet our son make factory less factory and would
pass in the mother and all of all we are doing that for the lesson class.
OK.
So we have a lesson factory and we can customize it the way we want.
So first of all we need a title for the lesson.
So it's fake our sentence.
We need a shut description Ficarra a paragraph and suicide.
He also writes for series Id shoot up a series.
So why don't we do this.
An anonymous function that returns a suicide.
So we're going to call our factory and it's going to create one for us and give us the idea.
So what is the question for us your cretinous Kurus series class.
OK so suicide is going to call this serious Jenna itto generate a fake ID and then give us the ID.
Ok then what else do we want.
Episode number.
I'm just going to what could these two hundred maybe.
OK finally we have the video I.D. So let me go ahead and put that in the video ID.
I'll just head over to Vimeo and grab whatever I see.
So get this one.
And here's the I.D. OK.
So we set that's used to generate some fake lessons on Peachtree areason tinker and factory.
But cost less and class create.
And why don't we quit like five of them.
We need to migrate to our database.
Right.
So we understand my grid fresh aasan.
So Team car again and we did that yeah.
There we go.
We have five lessons in our database that's go ahead and see that and I'm going to get a slot for this
series right here.
How about this one.
And I can go and visit that series in my browser.
OK.
So there we are.
Now what I want to do is load all the lessons of that associated with this series into this page and
then automatically a view component is going to seek the detail and then do its thing with it right.
So how do we also load that data.
Let's head over to our series The HP and simply see any time you want to load this model make sure you
load this relationships.
So we want to load with the lessons relationship.
Yeah but we don't have this relationship yet right.
So let's go ahead and Queechy lessons return this mini lesson class.
Let's go ahead or index that bleed ph be for the series and actually try to co-opt something like service
lessons first title.
So let's see this in action refresh.
OK.
So there we go.
We are actually having access to that relationship.
But let's make sure this details actually autoload that by going to our series controller and using
a die dump series and quick refresh and check out the relations we have lessons collection right here.
Looks like that detail so that for us also.
Now what do we want to do when we have this page.
What I want to do is actually have a list of lessons but this list of lessons is going to be displayed
by huge s right here like maybe having the name and having us a Butson that opens a model to edit or
create a new lesson.
This is going to be controlled by Fujairah therefore we're going to have a component here that maybe
view lessons and then veejays is going to take it from here.
All the speech is going to do is pass the lessons into the veejays component.
So let's go ahead and start working on that in the next lesson.