Let's go to VGX component that's going to be in charge of lessons.
So right in my companions tree we're going to create a new lessons that you and best for it's going
to have a template and just to see what's in that.
I'm gonna have a Lessons header and I'm going to export an empty object down in my Abda.
I just need to pull in this component.
Now we just started this view.
Lessons are required now in our template index that need to be collaterally past this lessons into this
view component.
So that would be able to give the management of our lessons to view from there.
OK.
So let's first of all Mundus your lessons and looks like we need to pass a default lessons into this
component as soon as the component is mounted Austin has refreshed the page so we can see default lesson's
is the name of the product that we want to pass and we're going to sign these two serious lessons.
So this is automatically going to pass or the lessons for this series into the default lessons.
Then we need to set up that part right.
So props and we'd have a day for lessons.
But then this is actually going to be received in Jason format because remember we are trying to echo
objects right here because we have a collection of objects which equil them is automatically going to
cast that string or Jason and Parsee right here.
So what we're going to do is we're going to have a.
And one of them is going to be a lesson's property and it's going to be this dog for lessons.
OK.
So by default as soon as we receive the props we're going to have a property lessons that house these.
But then what about formatting that back into the proper object notation.
We're going to have a completed property for that.
So let's just see for months that in essence it's simply going to return.
Jason don't parse this that lessons.
So that's what we can actually use in our Simply And that's why I have a naturally equity's out of before
we do that let's make sure that we are truly passing that data and everything is working in our tools.
So we have a view that stores open to fresh and D'Errico.
We have our lessons and we check out a few lessons.
We have the pool up which is the default which is an for format like expected.
Then we have the data that is exactly this Propp But then we have this formatted license which is an
array of all the lessons for this series.
OK so we can actually look at these and display the lessons.
So what are we going to do.
We will pull out this title that we use for testing and in our lessons to the view we want to wrap this
in a container and then have at least.
And we're going to have less good items.
And each of this is going to represent a lesson.
Right.
So we have to simply say we fall and we have to decide what we are looping through and we really have
to formatted lessons here so we can see the lesson in adolescence and right here is we're going to acquire
that lesson title.
So let's see if that works.
Quick refresh.
And looks like it works right.
But there's no styling.
And I think that's because of this as why I'm going to pull it out quick refresh again are working exactly
as we expect.
So we have our lease items were displayed from our fermata lessons.
What about commuting lessons and automatically updating this least.