What I want to achieve in this video it's a way for us to quit lessons.
Therefore I'm going to have a button here that when the user clicks on it it's going to pop up.
And that creates a lesson.
Now let's get straight into it right at the top.
Why don't we will have an actual tech center and indeed we're going to embed a button that says Create
a new lesson.
OK.
So that looks great for me.
And we're going to eventually now which is going to simply call create new lesson my thought.
We need to create that math.
So we'll have my thoughts property on that.
We're going to have to create new Laursen method.
And now we have to think about how we want to create lessons.
This is a component that is going to be in charge of managing the lessons and they don't want to really
put in the functionality of quitting lessons right here.
OK.
What I want to do is actually create a chat component that is going to create lessons and it's actually
going to give us a great learning opportunity to see how to manage child components and parent communication
if you just components so let's go ahead and create that in the same directory.
I'm going to New up a new component and then I'm going to have children a tree created lesson that view.
There we go.
And this quick lesson that is going to be a child of the templates that we had before.
So we're just going to have an edge one that says Create lesson just for understanding purposes.
Squit export default empty object and we need to register these components either in our objects which
will already slide globally we view just instance or with our lessons that view which is simply going
to be just with this particular component which is actually a view in stone.
But it's going to be local only to this component so it's only available for some test component.
Therefore we have a component's property.
And what we you study is create a lesson and this is going to require from the directory to create a
lesson that you follow.
Now what we could do is actually meet an event this that Emmets events which you just provide to us
and the name of that event is going to be creating new lesson events and we could actually pass an optional
law.
But now we don't have any Pido So we're just emet you meet that event.
Therefore you know what component.
What we can do is have a mount up property and we're going to subscribe to the events coming from our
parent so we can see this that parents dot on Creedon your lesson events do something.
So right here we can actually receive any permits us to the past into this event but now we don't have
any so we're simply going to console that clock.
Hello parents.
We are creating the lesson OK.
We saved up.
Now what we need to do is actually mount this component somewhere right.
So for starters let's try to just mounted in the template for this component.
So create lesson and I think that's a good place to start.
Quick refresh and then let's click on that button.
Check out the console and right do we have help parents.
We actually in that lesson.
So it means a watch I can put any such Are you listening to events successfully from its parent.
OK.
So how do we want essentially to look.
I'm just going to head over to Doug component here I'm all beaches at the same place.
And I've got a copy or moved on from there to my Create lesson on page study.
And let's just change a little bit of defaults.
It's going to be create new lsen.
Nobody is going to have a couple of fun elements.
What we now need to do is actually trigger the opening of this model.
So I'm just going to change this idea to create lesson ID and we can actually use bootstrap with Jake
Querrey to open this so we can find that element using your course finder.
And the idea is create lesson and then we can call them with all my thought on this element because
it's a model.
OK so let's try this out.
Quick refresh check out the console click on that and we have this console the clock.
And then we also have our model open.
Great jump.
Let's start working on this in the next lesson.