That so can I quit lesson form copy some from books like here and my crit lesson rather than having
this body I'm going to have grps right.
So the first one here is going to be for the title.
So the model title placeholder is going to be lessons I don't looks like we need a voodoo ID.
So this is going to be the new video ID.
The model is going to be the joy.
Nate Wong for the episode number and we can change S-type to number and see episode number and we can
actually see how to use this in our application.
Finally a group with a text area that form controlling it.
OK so we don't need the name neither do we need the ID.
All we need is the V model which is going to map to description.
So looks like we actually need all of these form fields on our class.
Therefore we're going to have our data property or data which returns an object.
And here we're going to have title assigned to an empty string description an empty string a piece of
Number two an empty string and video ID to an empty string.
So we should actually have that in a form.
OK.
So let's go ahead and check it out.
Quick refresh to conduct and then we have less than V.M. video on the edges of number on the description.
OK so what do we want to happen when we click on the safe changes.
MARTIN Or we can actually change it to Seife lesson.
Then she validate the data here and then make that E-Tecs request will serve us receive the lesson.
Therefore we are going to need to pull the exhaust making requests for import XOs from examples and
we can now use it the way we want in our class.
Ok so I'm going to put a pause right here and we're going to walk on the back end on level so that we'll
be able to handle the requests for these components before we go for the view.
Jess.