Let's make the switch to live.
Now I will nobbled lessons controller.
And this is also going to be a resource.
Let's just go ahead and register our resource lessons control our route resource.
Looks like we want to receive the series and we want to receive lessons.
Right.
So we received a series of lessons then levels are too much going to attach the white cards right here.
And we wanted to map to license control.
Now look at this in our view component.
If we try to inspect a component actually has access only to the Swiss ID birds.
We had to find that if we typings series level automatically when we use dependency injection and vog
more then binding to past in the series.
But it's going to try to find that using the SLOC.
Right.
But we have the idea.
So what do we do.
We can actually load the slot into this class or while we are loading these we pass it as a probe into
the view components so that anytime we are making that request we simply pass it.
But why don't we do something more fun.
Right.
So we're going to review experts in modern banking.
We've seen implicit well takes care of everything.
But why don't we do explicit.
So what I mean by explicit we're going to define our own key or our own wild card and we are novel every
time you see CBS by buying something.
Therefore we're going to head over to a valet service provider and this is where we can actually define
our own vald model bindings.
OK.
So what do we want.
We once Lavoe to bind series by ID to the series class.
OK so let's import a switch class.
OK.
So bind this to this.
And what we wanted to obligate is how to resolve it.
Right because we're told this it seems like when you use the default get Radtke name that was specified
in this class which is the SLOC.
But then we have only the idea here.
So we want it all Lavoe when you see this white card reader find using the ID rather than the slot.
So what we can do is use the bind thought and we're going to be binding to see with my ID wildcat and
we're taking a closer right here and disclosure automatically receives the value of these work in the
route and what we do right here is how Lavoe how to resolve this.
OK so we're going to tol'able return series Find the value because we know when we see by you we are
going to be passing the ID.
OK.
So what we can do is really define or find of also the law which automatically rejects this using a
model not an exception.
And then we can catch that it or maybe handle it differently.
OK so first we define a new word credit.
We want to use an approach one.
And second we told her how to resolve this if we don't do this then it's automatically going to use
to get Waukee name to inject the superclass.
But then if we told her how to resolve it Guinta call these call back rather than doing the default.
Ok let's try this out.
You know what that BHB what we can do is before we actually start running out here let's just define
a get route.
And the wildcard is going to be this and we should actually wrap it disallowed on those parameter and
then we can pass you closure.
But if we want to automatically inject the Swiss class we need to type it right.
So vodcast series and will take in the instance right here then what we can do is just died on the series.
Okay.
So we are typing in a wildcat loveall is automatically going to search if we have a binding for this.
And that's exactly what what we saw.
It creates a bounding binding for series and in this case it's also going to create a body for lessons
but we have automatically created our own Fosi which my ideal level is going to check this out if we
haven't a in for that check if there's a resolution then you use the obligation to get us the series.
So let's go ahead and try this out in the browser.
So if we try to visit the route ampacity one receipt automatically Lovelle just gives us the series
last and Marci's with the ID of one.
If you try to have just does that mean the scene to see of Route 1 the bottom being my lover.
OK so now that we've done that every time we want to actually use the lessons what you know have to
pass in the series then.
Lessons control how we can actually get the service that matches my this idea.
So let's head over to our lessons Wauchula.
OK looks like we haven't created that let's go ahead and generate one which we understand make controller
lessons controller and we want this to be a resource.
OK that's generator.
OK.
So now we have this told me I thought and this is where we actually want to receive the series.
And then we want to start a new lesson.
So we're going to see a series and get that instance variable and then leverage systematically going
to inject that if we have the service by the wildcat.
Now what do we want to do in our method.
We just want to see if you're serious right.
And we actually might switch this out for a custom request but for now I think let's go ahead and see
how it works with this one.
And then if this is before we dropped all we might create a new request.
OK so what do we want to do.
Yes we're going to have some foundation and we're going to use testing to drive this out.
But for now let's just wait and see how this is going to work.
We can just get a lesson for the series.
So serious lessons relationship.
And we called yet mid-thought and we could actually pass in request or as a parameter.
OK.
So we have to.
And we have the lessons relationship defined in the series class and then we simply assess the yet met
and parsing the request or as a parameter.
OK so it's automatically going to fuel the series ID field.
And then since we have this form lots of data it's gonna up into that.
OK.
So let's go ahead and try this out.
But for that we need to take care of the Create lesson that view post request there for what we want
to do.
And eventually snorters.
Listen it's a safe lesson.
So CLIQ is going to call create lesson on this class and create Leser.
It's going to be a math facts and methods and we only have using it.
Therefore we want to see examples opposed to an endpoint and we need to make sure we pass the correct
end points let's go to a war where we have serious lessons and to quit we just need to revisit this
point right.
So what can we do.
We need the ID of the suits.
Why don't we pass that idea as a payload into this.
So we're going to see serious ID and then we're going to see this that serious ID requires serious ID.
OK.
And we can have a detail right here that is Sui's ID and it falls to an empty string.
Now what am I doing this is not eventually snow it's going to listen for events from the parent and
the parent has the possibility of passing a payload.
But we have the suicide available on the parents but not on the child.
So we're going to pass it as a pillow to this child let's head over to our parents.
What's the lesson that you.
Yeah.
And why we are triggering that image we can actually trigger or send this dog serious ID.
OK.
Now what am I doing this.
I'm going to be passing a series I.D. I.
And I'm going to be getting this from my index that blade Ph be.
And then I can pass it into the Create lesson that view component to use it to make post request.
I actually got some this from our lessons that we have right here.
But imagine a situation where we have no lessons that's going to break down really fast.
So let's just add a new prayer that is going to give us that therefore you know index that blade to
be we need to pass a serious ID which is going to be serious ID.
OK.
So we have a problem suicides.
We receive it then when we are getting a new lesson and we are imaging that event so our child component
we know Oh it's my turn to act.
It's going to see this as a parameter.
Then in our creedalism we can actually reference this when we want to define the you are all for exists
therefore we are going to use the tactics in Turks so that we can reference days a series ID lessons.
Right.
So if you check out our Web PH BE IT SUITS ID socialism's bird.
We also need to prefix dates with mean right.
So I mean slash Sui's ID slash lessons.
OK so let's try that so that they can get the response console that response to catch.
So you can so that not the error that we get from the seller or my god.
I just notice we actually didn't pass this data to our post requests.
So let's just parse this in as a second prompt or real fast and rather than empty strings we're going
to be friends.
This the title and days on description.
This is the opposite number.
Finally they say that video ID.
OK so now we are actually passing that detail like let's try this out in a browser and see what we get.
Ok looks like we actually successfully created that.
Now would look at the detail we received from the server.
It's the lesson object lesson object that we just created.
I'm just going to pause right here and there we're going to continue to find these in the very next
video.