OK let's pause for a second.
I think we've done a lot without writing any test.
Let's go ahead and actually make sure that application works do we want before we continue.
So I'm going to create a new test and this test is going to cover our quitting lessons.
So Peachtree arsenic test Crit. license test.
OK so create license test and what first do I want to test.
Let's just make sure when use of this is that in point you can create a lesson.
It's a public function.
A user can create lessons.
So how do we want to write our tests.
We want to make an Ajax request of an AJAX POST request to our endpoint that is in charge of creating
lessons and would assert that the database house where cards would also assert that the Jasen contains
the structure that we want and then would also US-CERT the start of school or something like that.
OK so what is the end point.
Remember we have admin then we pass in the ID of the series and then lesson's OK.
So looks like we need a series.
So lets create one.
So Sui's factory will persist that then looks like we need to make that post requests post Jason and
the End Point is I don't mean to post in the series Id like here and lessons.
OK.
So the data we are passing in is going to be on our way.
And I'm just going to see it in our lessons valuable.
OK so we won the title and wanted to be no less than we wanted that description and we wanted to be
near the description.
We wanted to episode number and we wanted to be maybe 2 and 5 or whatever and we wanted a Vimeo ID to
be maybe a your ID number.
OK so when we passed this thing as up we expect the lesson to be created.
And we also expect that it should be successful.
So let's check the status code.
First of all I said stutterers was 200 and then I searched the data that is returned to us right.
So I said Jason and what this method is going to do is it's going to take this lesson Parminter that
we pass in compared with the request or the response that we get from calling this post Jason methought.
And then the queen compared to make sure that this actually is a subset or actually matches the juice
that we received.
OK.
So we are certain strategy and we said Jason.
And one last thing we can also assert that the database has that lesson.
OK.
So I said database hahs and we can specify the less stable and passing and we can see the title should
be maybe the lesson title that we had.
Okay I think thats it.
We make that was request Michala status 200.
I said to Jason and I said that the database actually saved this record.
So let's run this test individually.
OK.
It is expected such as 200 but we see a three or two.
Now I think I know why we were seeing that we ought to is be direct and thats because we just locked
in our administration.
Methinks we have a helpful thoughts and logging that I mean the streets so.
So we simply have to see logging I mean I think thats how we caught the thought.
Let's check out our test case.
So so its luggin me.
Great.
We can just use it right here.
OK.
So let's run that test again.
We received the 500.
Let's just play ball.
Exception handling to see what that error was.
Days without exception handling.
OK.
And aerospace lesson has no call on ID.
So let's check that out.
Create less unstable.
OK.
It's called Video ID.
So sorry about that.
So Viaggio idea right here.
Run that one more time.
Yeah.
And you just posse's to actually have passed like that just the first time because we're locked in on
the street and we messed up this right here.
OK so it looks like it actually works the way we want it to work.
And you might actually have preferred to write this test before making the functionality.
But I think it's always a base to have this functionality.
And then we can go ahead and expand with our tests.
For example in the next lesson we are actually going to be trying to see how we can add value in most
to our one lesson creation process just by using a test driven development approach.