You want to verify that before creating a lesson we must actually passing a title.
So let's go ahead and create a test for that public option.
So first title is required.
Jacqui it's a lesson.
OK so how do we do this.
We need a series a lesson and we need to make that point requests.
OK so I'm just going to copy on the face and paste right here and I'm going to note the title from the
lesson so we don't need to parsing that title but we need to make an assertion that the title was required.
So right here Atsushi we're going to be making is simply a that the session has errors and this should
be validation for the title field.
OK so fair enough.
Longinus on Main Street or we might not need this would see through our test and then we Criddle series
in the series and then I said that the session has some errors.
So let's discuss specifically
Yeah.
And sure enough we have field as such and that force is true.
Now we need to make sure we have some validation right.
So head over to my lessons controller.
And I think this one line controllers are really the best.
Therefore I'm going to create a on request for this just so I don't have to include additional lines
like you.
So I'm not with this customer request.
Be sun make request quick lesson requests.
Hierarchy that's created.
Therefore we need to create the lesson request right here.
So Lavallee squinch you actually inject this one you need to encode that.
So use vodcast it's to be requests quick lesson request.
Let's head what's that class
OK so let's just say this is true and we're going to see how this applies meathook walks later on.
So we'll said that's true just really teach all egressed then for our test to Basri must make sure that
the title is required.
It's one that says one more time and we still get this error.
Now this is what I wanted to show you.
It still fails.
Why.
Because we're using the Jason method.
Now this post Jason mid-thought creates an environment and this environment is for testing.
Jason AP staff are nothing like sessions actually exist.
Therefore when we checked the session to conceive in the session.
But if we search this out actually to check the status of the response that we got would actually see
that it's a 4:22.
That's just the song.
Yeah.
On the process.
OK.
So we have a successful response as a 1:46 because Lavoe understands that this is a Jasen API in Vollmann
for the testing.
But let's switch this all back to session.
Was.
Jason right here and love is going to make and or did not read on normal post request including sessions
and all that then let's run this yeah.
And now posse's.
OK.
So you have to know when to use the post Jason or when you use to post depending on your situation.
In this case the post was just OK.
Now we need to also test that for the description.
Let's just get this math on test or title or test or description is required quick a quick lesson for
when lessons are really is going to be read about that description.
Right.
So be studying and pull all the description here.
So I assert that it was for description.
So let's run this specific test to make sure it fills in DOS box or quit lessons requests.
Or we could just add one additional move for the description to see each required one that tests one
more time and everything should be OK.
I'll give you this not one more test for the episode number and then B do ID and I'll test the discussion
is quite quick on this.
So test and it says of number is required to create a lesson.
So rather than these We're going to parse description.
OK.
So I assert that we have arrows for a bizarre number.
Let's run that again.
OK.
It fails.
This jackpot of addition will make sure it's required.
And it says Now I'm going to pause for a second for this video.
I'm going to call it a D and see you in the next one.
Thank you.