Let's make sure other vigilantes are truly required and then we'll move on to something else and get
this and make sure that the video ID is passed to quit the lesson.
So of this episode number in Boston and expects to be in a session was run this Singo test
to mission.
Let's fix that Rochester gang.
OK now it's fixed.
We might actually have to come back today to make sure that we verify that it's a valid ID or that the
number is unique.
But let's go ahead and move on.
And then we're going to come back to this later on.
Now what do we need to do.
We successfully verified that we can actually create or store licensed university.
But wait what are we going to do now is head of a create lesson that view and take it from there.
Now when we make that post request we actually create it.
We have the response detail right here from the server.
What we want to do is image of an event that a parent or we got a successful response do something about
this.
So we're going to be meeting an event called lessa created and then the data we're passing in is the
response to data.
Remember this is going to contain a lesson that was just created.
Now when we meet this event we need to listen to this event from our parent which is less instant view
therefore we need to hook into the Mount that Huq lifecycle.
And what we are going to be doing here is subscribing to that event.
So this is not on the lesson created which is the name of the event that is emitted from our child right
here same event with a callback that will be as Accu-Chek and we're taking the lesson.
So Parminter and what we want to do is actually update the data property.
I notice that we are actually parsing these Jason right here but it's fairly possible to actually it
in line right here which is going to give us a lot more flexibility.
So I'm just going to just in the past the study for lessons right here and I'm not going to need this
computer property anymore.
And right here I'm going to make sure we use the lessons in the loop.
OK that's a little bit of a Prato and it's going to give us the flexibility of doing these days and
lessons that Bush Leser.
Right.
So when we listen to the lesson create an event events let's push that new lesson into our own lessons
object and jazz as glass test.
It's going to automatically refresh that door.
OK.
So one thing we want to do actually in our quick lesson is to close the model.
So let's go ahead and do that.
And then the idea for that or worse create lesson and we'll call the model Mfat and passing a high parameter.
OK so that's going to.
Hold on for us.
Let's go ahead and see this in action.
Quick refresh and we have no arrows.
If we actually trench coat of your lessons we have the lessons object right here that is automatically
cast or passed into javascript array and we call on a quick lesson let's just see have a new lesson
parsing any ideas passing in episode number and then our description is going to be whatever.
So let's save the lesson.
And it looks like a cluster model but for some reason it didn't pick up on that event.
Right.
So let's see what's going on and make lesson yet when you actually listen into nests and create that.
And I think the error is coming because we really have to specify that we are emitting to the parent
of this child component.
So does the parent that I meet so emits particularly to the parents and the events should be lessened
created.
Let's try that one more time.
Create less than paste in the description in your ID please.
Id create and automatically we see that our home is refreshed.
OK so that's pretty great.
We actually successfully pushing this are we.