Let's straight into the reach of Zlitan a lesson from this dashboard.
Oh and by the way be on the scene I took the liberty of including an Edgerton's and Pazza.
OK so let's use the delete button to make this happen before we do that.
Let's just head to what some lessons can twirler and make sure that lateralis prepared to delete stuff.
So right here where have to destroy is expected on ID.
But we use an outmoded Banyon So we're going to get the lesson.
So lesson lesson remember we really just not a resource and automatically we can tap into these anomalies
can inject to us a lesson.
So that's important.
We just need to call.
Let's see.
OK.
So hopefully we don't run into any trouble.
Let's go ahead and make this happen with XOs.
So you know the lessons that you have this is the need boson therefore we cannot part an event is not
which is a clique which concedes you need that lesson.
OK.
So this and I thought we need to get right down in on my thoughts.
Object would create that thought.
And what we want to take up from today is that Mitchell he actually wants to debate so I'm simply going
to rubbish in a confirm.
So if confirmed Are you sure you want to do it and this is kind of using javascript's for API.
But I think it's going to stop the policies.
So you want it to lead.
And that's true.
This is a show he wants to delete.
Then we're going to make an egregious call so egregious that he needs which is a delete request.
Looks like we don't have access to use on this component yet so let's imported.
You bought yours is yours therefore exist to delete.
And we need to pass in the end point therefore with passing I mean this series ID slash them we need
to pass in the lesson ID right.
So why don't you get the ID from the loop.
So right here we can possi it as an argument therefore we have the lesson local variable and get the
ID.
OK so we passed a less than ideal to this method.
So once we get that we can in also as the Bonneton.
And this has to be fixed reconnoissance.
So I mean suicide the lessons lesson ID Justin's delete and point down we want to reach.
And if you're not sure about that.
Make sure you want.
We have seen Margolese and checkout zeolites routes we have.
So let me use my I.D. lessons and lesson and squinch go to destroy mid-thought of innocence.
OK.
So that's what we have done den.
If we have a successful response console that Lauck response just from now and Gutch it's also going
to do so.
OK.
So let's try this out.
Quick refresh.
Open up my console.
And that should delete this one.
So we have.
Are you sure you want to delete.
It's gone from and we have a good 500 Let's see what that is index a global is still not going to pass
to license.
That was supposed to be an instance of a lesson but received an instance of my class.
OK.
I thought that was going to be a problem.
That's headbutts NASA's controller and trying to see if the series.
And also we see them lesson then we do need the lesson.
OK.
I think this is going to fix it that Shrub did it again.
OK another error.
And Greg you actually deleted the response that must be a stream.
OK.
I knew this was also going about because we can't reach on the internet control us.
So what we can do is listen to meet and return a status of OK.
So response.
Jason sconces OK.
It's just a successful response.
OK.
So we found a series Find the lessons to lead the lesson and respond to this.
So I don't think a lot of long ago this was actually a problem we could actually typing this a novel
was automatically conject of the lesson acknowledging the series but that's how he wants to work now
then it's OK.
OK so let's delete this.
I think we already did.
Let's help refresh translate this one OK so it looks like we're successful and we have to delete a response
that.
OK so that was sucessful leagues in 18.
But what happens to.
When we actually have an elite where Spawn's.