Right now when we delete a lesson it doesn't naturally go away from the door right.
So let's handle that.
Now how do we pull out from an array we can use javascript's default splice mid-thought.
So for us to do that we need to know the index of that element.
So why don't we actually parse the index to just delete my thoughts so I'm going to pass in a key and
this key is going to be gotten from here.
So we could actually do this and get the key for the lesson and then pass it to this method.
And then what we can do is like here we could see this are lessons that splice in the key and we'll
pass in one to see we move just one image right.
So looks like we need to receive the key right here.
And I think that's going to work.
So after a successful Gillett's we'll move that.
Let's go ahead and try this to see if it works.
Quick refresh OK.
So let's move less than four.
So looks like less than four.
That's great.
That's from this one.
OK.
It's gone.
This one too.
OK great.
Looks like it's working perfectly.
Great Joe.