Let's that go for updates.
My thought for lessons now we're going to need to get the series the lesson that we try not dates and
also the request so we don't need the ID in this case quite so large that one article can undo what
you inject.
Then how do we want to update this lesson lesson updates request.
I think this will do then what we can do is return lesson fresh OK because naturally we just lost a
billion.
Then we researched a fresh copy of that response to our to our friends.
And so we can actually inject a custom request right here so we can define our addition horse all we
can actually also define the Venetian host in the control right here.
So let me just read and it's less than request.
So we are sent make requests updates lesson requests if I had about sort of dead lesson requests I'd
change the street to room to make sure we have access then I'll head over to my quit on request and
make sure I also have exactly the same validation what was a good lesson should actually have exactly
the same by the rules and that will give us a little bit of protection.
OK.
Then we need to all aval to inject rather than the default request.
So we need a bit less room.
QUEST I would use that at the top.
So all of the reasonable questions of dogma and then return a fresh copy of the lesson to our front
end.
OK.
So let's head over back to our So these are lessons that you know we have this added button right here
which is used to update.
And what we're going to do is add a click event.
And this is going to call added lesson and this is simply going to pass or taking the lesson that we
get into it.
OK so let's quit that method.
Added lesson we are taking the lesson now.
We have no choice here.
We can actually handle the editing of the lesson or we could pass it down to the child component which
has a form that we could use to edit the lesson.
OK.
So I'm just going to say this that image added less an event and the data was going to pass.
So payload is the lesson that we just received.
OK.
Then in our component we can actually listen to this show create lesson that you might actually think
of renaming this now that has two functionalities but it's OK by me based on parents not on the adolescent
request then begin to do something.
First of all that's received a lot which is the lesson that we are trying to educate and what do we
want to do now that art form actually has two functionalities what we want to do is actually manage
the state of the forms so we need to know if the form is actually in editing mode or in creation mode.
So let's just see editing and by default the form is going to be false.
Which means it's in question mode then what we want to do is as soon as we listen to this event we want
to make sure editing is true.
And we're going to do a little changes in our template that are going to help us know that the form
is editing and it's not creating yet our case so once we do that what we want to do we want to make
sure that the title is set to less than the title.
OK.
The description also is said to lessen that description.
Same thing with all the other attributes we have video ideation sets but UAD episode number 2 should
be set to a number.
So this piece of namah.
Great.
So another form is editing.
The first thing we can do is actually change the law for this matter so we can say if this film is editing
show us safe less on Butson.
But then if it's in creation mode we're going to change it to create Lassan.
OK.
So we can attach and VIF here.
So if he was not editing or we could actually attach the arrows just to we don't have to use or not.
And what are we going to do is duplicate this button and right here this is going to have the video.
So if it was editing and we're going to have to save less than what's on display to us and the most
important part we are going to call an update.
Lesson mid-thought on click.
Right.
So we have a bottleful gridlocks on one for a big lesson and it all depends on the state of our form.
So if the form is in editing mode then it's going to show the object lesson button.
Awesome.
So let's go ahead and quit that mid-thought lesson and for now let's simply say console that lock of
data.
OK.
So we listen to an event which is a good lesson and then we transform the form into an editing form
by setting this property editing and then we set the attributes of form should be equal to the lesson
attributes that we just got from our parents.
OK.
Which is going to proceed as a pillow.
So let's go ahead and try this out in the Parsa for quick refresh and then click on edit button.
Check out our CRID form which you score that it's automatically populated with the Ditto's for this
lesson right.
So what we want to do is actually open up the model right.
So let's head back to our quick lesson and we'll call this quick lesson.
Open wound up OK.
So refresh click on that and sure enough we have a model with the description ID title and everything.
So that's the care of the Ajax request in the next session.