OK let's get our fun.
We're going to use AJAX for that.
Now if we took off form we have the safe and Button and we click on the chin and say stop the team because
that's what we have for now let's switch this out with our correct implementation.
So Agios And the question we want to make is a push request.
So now we need to pass on the endpoint.
So we're going to be slash at mean slash the C C which we don't have yet because we might actually be
opening the lesson form when we don't see have this.
So why don't we have to be parsed in the society as a people and also therefore with head of cattle
and lessens that view and rather than passing one parameter would pass in the lesson and the serious
idea.
OK so serious idea should be passed in and we'll just see that serious ID because they this up serious
ID.
OK.
So we have this society that we could reference right here.
So we pass in lesson and see sides in an object then what we could do is receive these properties right
here.
So we'd have a lesson and a series ID.
We can now assign the series ID on this component.
Now we can make a request by passing in this that serious ID license and now we need access to the lessons.
So how do we do this.
So lets just default receiving saving the lesson ID on this class.
OK.
So lesson Id cause less than ID.
OK so we need to reference that onwards for that.
OK so now that we lucratively collaterally you just said the lesson or lesson from this that lesson
should be taught to lesson and that would actually remove the complexity of watching all of these properties
out.
Yeah but then we might actually Kombucha we frostily to but I'm going to go with this so we can reference
the ID by seeing the vase that lesson ID then its a regress.
We can listen to when the dentist fired on with just console that knock the response for now and would
catch and it was something we see from the server and console that know that response also.
So obviously we need to pass in the detail right.
So its going to look exactly like this.
So let's pass in title description a piece of number and your ID.
OK.
So let's try this out in the box and actually see if it walks and it click on the Save lesson button
and we have a successful response from our server.
So lets go ahead and try to edit something so edit it and save listen.
Check out the responses to see if the title was detat and looks like it works.
So updates is working perfectly.
Let's see if we could do a little refracts or in the very next video.