I want to automatically update that as soon as we receive a response from our server.
Therefore what we are going to be doing is meeting on events to the parents just like we did when we
were creating the lesson and our parents will automatically take care of the rest.
So before we do that let's close this model and immediate events the name of this event is going to
be lesson updated on the pillow that we're going to be sending to our parents.
The screen should be response to data then in our lessons that view which is the parents we can listen
to that event by subscribing to it and we can receive the payload in here in a verbal lesson.
And when we received this we want to find that lesson using its I.D. in this lessons are eight.
And then we to automatically replace it with this response that we got from the server.
So let's get the next and we'll be searching the lessons.
Ari on this parents will be using javascript's fine index method and if you don't know about this method
this is a simple method that Joske provide to us and what is going to do is it takes in a closed shop
and it's going to try to find an element in the current rate that matches the condition that is placed
in that closure.
And if he doesn't find any then he's going to return negative one.
But if he finds he's going to return to the index of that element.
So would look to all of them and we have the current object in that array in this variable area.
So return less than that ID equals all that ID.
So we are looking for a lesson where the IDs match.
OK.
Now if you get that index what are going to do is we're going to replace this lesson with the one that
we have in the lessons are we this that license dot splice and the splice method.
Checking the index the number of elements we want to move and what replaced at that position.
So the lesson OK that should do the trick.
Let's go ahead and see how this works in our Vasa.
And we simply cannot do said at the end of the title so we know it's actually added that safe lesson.
It's closed.
And there we go.
We have just that right there.
So it means it's correct defined in that lesson and replacing it.
Now just for a tip if you're trying to update your lesson by simply saying that lessons and parsing
in the lesson index and replacing it with the lesson.
This is not going to work very well.
Yes.
And the recommended way to do that is using the splice method.
OK.
So that's a little gotcha that you might be struggling with but that doesn't work out here.
Yes.
Now let us notice something when we click on the new lesson Butson Yeah we still have these dates are
in our model and we actually have a safe lesson watching here rather than the button we specified in
our code.
So let's handle that.
The reason is we are not telling the model that we are resetting editing to false.
Therefore what we're going to do when we listen to that lesson we're going to set this that editing
to false and we have to clear this data.
So I don't want to go through the cycle of this that scription equals empty string.
Let's start with your idea those days.
Therefore I'm going to take this as an opportunity to simply refactor this into a class.
OK.
So what I'm going to be doing is defining a lesson class and this lesson class is going to take in a
lesson and it's going to set properties on this class that match that lesson.
For example this title equals lesson the title and if no less than the title exists we are going to
assign it to an empty string.
Say that description.
Cost less than the description or empty string.
This dog Id cause less than the video ID or an empty string.
And finally this is of course lesson that of number or an empty string.
And that's a simple lesson class that will help us refactor our code.
Now how do I want to use this when I listen to a Creedon you less than event.
I'm going to set this.
That lesson equals new lesson.
OK.
And it means I need a lesson property or this class.
And lesson for potty is all of this title description episode and video ID.
Therefore I'm going to replace all of this lesson.
OK.
So when we listen to quit new this that lesson is going to be a new lesson.
Therefore it's going to be empty.
And we should actually pass on empty object right there.
OK.
So it's going to be empty with all of these empty strings then right here where I have title description
video ID.
I'm going to replace all of this with this.
That lesson equals new lesson and would pass in the lesson into the constructor.
OK.
And they also need to move the episode ID them with the series ID and lets them ID on this class.
Also when we are making a post request to quit a lesson we can now move all of this and pass in that
lesson.
And also when we are making that pooch request you can now replace all of this with this dog lesson.
OK so the only way to know if we've actually broken anything is to try it out right.
So let's go ahead and try.
Yeah.
And looks like we already have a bunch of Aristotle defined on that in science and that would be because
we have the model tied to the model vidual ID and all of that so we want to replace the lesson title
lesson that video ID lesson that episode number and finally lesson that description safe dog refresh
again and that clears up.
Let's check out of your tools and we have an empty lesson object right here right.
So let's click on average it populates that object with the data.
Let's get a lesson by adding a detat right here.
And reducing the description safe lesson and look at that nothing was broken.
So we actually had a successful refracts or not we were going to create new lesson Butson everything
is initialised back to an empty string.
So I think that actually works strangely perfectly.
Let's go ahead and create a lesson to make sure nothing is broken.
Great lesson.
OK.
So there we go.
We have a lesson here on the edge and we have the data and if you also hit on the Edit button it automatically
is parsed awesome.
So that looks like it's working perfectly.
I'm going to hit pause for a second and we're going to continue in the very next video.