Not want a lot of console that locks all about application and there that's not really going to be a
very helpful notification system in production.
So what are they going to be doing in this video.
It's actually creating our own custom detection system as you know just to be using notifications all
around application of different components.
And the best way to go about it is actually registering an events bus on in the object so we can access
it from anywhere at any time.
I'll show what I mean.
I'll head over to view and in my app the Jets right here we have the window objects and we can actually
registar different properties on this object.
And I'm just going to start with a naughty property which is going to be a function that takes in a
notification and let's just see if we start when you call this mid-thought.
It's simply a console that locks notification not message.
OK so because I'm thinking and this question should be made up of a message and a type so maybe it's
a success or a danger type or warning type we're just going to make that cost.
OK.
Now if you call this method anywhere we should actually see notification that message.
OK let's try this with head of what's our consul would call the new team effort and it's like setting
an object on one of those reports issued by mistake so I would say this is a new message.
It went up and there we go we have this is a new message on the console.
So it's actually picking up that message logging into the console.
Now this is not what we want to do right.
We want to actually meet an event and then we listen to that event from anywhere in application.
Now if you haven't noticed Yes it's so.
Actually an event bus which means we can admit events we view the view in stunts and actually also listen
to this event.
I'll show you what I mean.
So notice we have a window view right here.
Let's head over to our console and what we're going to do is see view should be close to new view.
So we have a new instance of view and what we're going to do is view that on Naughty fight.
So again a message and simply console that lock message and for us to know it's actually coming from
here.
That's concatenates from custom event boss.
And now we got an event listener on of your instance then what we could do is using View Available that
we start we could meet that event and that event is going to be notified and we'll pass in the payload
which is the message and we're going to see a custom message to events or bus he'd enter.
And we see it's actually lots of console custom message to even boss.
And then it's concatenated string from custom event bus so viewers can naturally artist custom even
box itself.
So rather than doing this in the console let's do it in our court so we could say window that events
for example is going to be called to new view instance then we can restart our global events.
Listen up.
But on notification checking the notification.
And for now just console that lock litigation.
Received.
OK.
So we have this event box just like we did in our console and it can actually listen to events.
So now that we've registered this event now we can actually Emmets that events from quantity function.
So we did have that clean window events and would emit notification and we can pass in a payload for
example new message.
OK.
So let's have a watch or a console call noti and we have notification received locked right here.
OK so why don't we actually wrap this in a custom component so that we can use it in any part of our
application.
I'm going to create a custom file and this is going to be naughty that view.
And we're going to have templates.
My scripts would export by default an empty object.
Let's just start this with.
Yes.
So the component and would use view naughty as Jim or template then quite an component's naughty that
view.
Not what I want to do is it may not see that view.
When we compare and is created it I'm going to see a window not events not on much kasian because that's
the event that we are broadcasting.
We're taking the payload.
And for now let's just say console that lock the notification received.
OK.
So in my of the Jest I'm no longer going to listen to this but I'm listening to it in the components.
So when they're called Norty it's going to emit that notification.
And if everything works well we actually see in the console.
There's not one last step we need to make sure we mnze this.
So maybe at the bottom we could mnze view naughty.
And I think that should walk.
Let's try it out how to refresh and would call Nuzzi again.
Yeah.
And we do have the education received.
Therefore we are truly listening to that event from our custom components.
Let's head over to our components now and actually try to make this work.
And first of all going to set up a data top in here I'm going to have notification such by default and
then right here when I receive that event or I listen to it I'm going to say this the notification equals
payload.
Then in my template I can see if we show a cause notification.
OK.
So it means if notification is not we are not going to see that template.
But if it's not no then we're going to see it in our template.
We may want to echo the notification message so we might have notification that MSH right up and we
should have a little bit styling for this.
So class of alerts maybe are less successful now.
And what about the positioning.
Where do we want to see it.
Let's just give this a class of Nazi lurch or naughty and what we're going to do is define our custom
sidewalks just what these components would define alert naughty class.
And let's just give this position of fixed.
And if you want it at the bottom right corner or at the bottom sense depending on what you want.
We can give it a right of 20 pleasaunce arm for pigs pixels maybe.
And just to make sure it's floating with give it that index of 1 and that would do it for the styling.
Pretty basic.
So we listen to that event and if the notification is not more then we are going to receive that message.
So that's just rubbish in the tech center.
So how do we trigger a notification event.
We do that by calling or Nuzzi function.
So our function is going to meet that event for us and we taking the notification rather than passing
a new message here we should pass the notification.
OK therefore let's head over to what lessons that you are gay and right here we're listening to.
When the lesson is created what we could do is see window the naughty.
I will pass in the notification.
We want to notify the users so we're passing the message like great great and this message is going
to be less than create it successfully and get passed in a type of success.
Right.
So we are calling Wiersma thought.
And when we call that mid-thought this method is going to taking the notification that we passed in
and admits that events and no one not see that view component we are listening to that event.
And we are going to automatically assign that event to one notification property or kink.
That makes sense.
Let's try this out.
Create lesson lesson sayto ID number description and click on a quick lesson button.
And here we have our mistakes lesson created successfully.
Bad looks like the message does not go off even after all we've fight saw what we can do is actually
have a time out for this to show.
So what we can do is this the notification equals payload.
And after that we can set a timeout which is going to take in a function and in this function we want
to set notification to be quote you know my game and we have to specify the amount of time.
So let's just see 2.5 seconds she's going to do.
So set the notification to be called the payload and after 2.5 seconds make showed an indication he
said but no.
OK.
So let's try this out one more time.
Quick new lesson new lesson number description.
OK we have that notification and after some time it goes away.
So the positioning is really off but I'm going to take that behind the scenes.
What I want to do right now is truly make this message dynamic.
So rather than having these alerts says I want this class to be dynamic.
Therefore what I'm gonna do is bind this class to be called to a computer property or a computer property
is going to is going to get the type of the notification.
So we need a computer property right here so we're going to see it and we have the type computer property
and this is simply going to return the class name that we want.
For example if we have success then we should have a lot success if we have a danger then we should
have that danger.
Same thing with a warning.
So would return the template string.
Words then concatenate that to this litigation type.
OK.
So if we ever have an interrogation by industry on the property type and this type is going to simply
return to us class name that matches the notification type.
OK.
So what we can do is would help reduce or lessen the view.
And just for demonstration purposes would change these to danger.
OK.
So when the user creates a new lesson make sure that what is I mean that is a danger and we should automatically
have a class of alert danger attached to this.
If so let's try that out and you lessen the number description OK.
So we see right here automatically we have a dean Jopp type of notification.
So that's great.
Aspected.