Let's do a little bit something about our handling of our topic issue right now for example when we
make that exist request to delete a lesson right here we just cancel that lock.
Let's make that better.
Now we need to know the person we are building for.
We are building for an administrator that's going to be adding series to a dashboard.
So probably is going to be a developer so I'm not going to stress much about displaying some sort of
error or to make him know what to do because it's not going to be a regular user it's going to be a
developer.
Yes.
Probably the owner off the site.
So what we want to do is to correct the error code so we're going to check if the statute is a 42 means
it's a validation error.
And then we are going to show the user.
But then if it's another form to then it's probably a problem of Beaufoy zation or an ex-pat CSR we
have to kill or 500 so we're just going to tell the user please there was an error on the server.
Please refresh your page so that you get fresh data and then you start making the correct API calls.
OK.
So how do we handle this.
So here we'll just see if response does the response and maybe we should change this into error so our
a response.
For starters because 4:22 then we're simply going to notify the user or he's validation was off.
So we'd have a window that note the method we created and the type is going to be danger and the message
screen to be had for Ed..
It's frustrating frocking.
And we actually might never hit this point because we are making sure that our validation is valid from
our front end.
So we are not sending any data from VGX but it just helps to know that we can do that then we're going
to see if this actually does not notify then that means we have a 500 here or for one then what we are
going to do is simply notify the user.
Something when you are on.
Please refresh please.
OK.
So this is going to be type of danger and we're going to move this console a lot right here.
So if there is just a school of watching to then you should try the user search.
And then if it wasn't a fortune E-2 means not validation error.
This is what we're going to tell the user.
OK.
So this is how we're going to be handling the airforce and we can actually build veejays front end in
such a way that it's never going to send wrong data to the server.
And probably the only areas that we're going to be getting are 500 million or so.
We just had a request for some reason but it's always good to handle for us and we have that's called
Reach on the back end to make sure that it actually works perfectly.
So what do we do.
Do we copy this exact thing.
Everywhere we have a console that lock like in the create lesson the view right here and paste this
in because this is what we want right.
So this is going to be everywhere.
And we'll get those forms and statues and do exactly the same thing and same thing right here.
Right.
So it gets in the air or after the EPA request checking if it's unfortunate too.
And if it's not performing to then we simply tell the user to refresh the speech.
So is this what we're going to be doing.
I think we should actually hide this functionality behind a blue bar method.
OK.
So ahead of what's in my app that jazz and I'm simply going to create a global error handler so window
door handle all the because function.
And this is what we want to do.
Therefore we want to parse into this My thought is the error that it's trying to handle.
OK.
So in the Arrow and then the method is going to take care of the rest.
Therefore now that we have this eval we can headbutts or quick lessons and rather than doing this we
can pool all of this out and right we know the tendu error us on passing the error and sure enough we
have to catch the roll right here.
OK.
So we simply handled or using that like Lubo error handler.
So pull all this and paste that handle or mid-thought right there.
But we should probably do exactly the same thing in our lessons to see if we catch an error or simply
call for her to undo the error.
So I think that safer error handling in the next video we're going to start actually doing a complete
refracts or cleaning up features before we actually move on to our next step.