A project is coming along good.
But let's just do some cleanup just to make sure everything is in place.
I'm going to start by creating a page where we can actually see all of our series.
OK.
Head over to my project my series control are you going to visit my index routes and I'm going to return
a view and I'm just going to college.
I mean that's series that are great that I mean there are trees series and create and all that blade
the pitch.
OK so I'm just going to copy the template Baystate as it.
And it's all serious then for the content section.
We're not going to have a form that would have something like a table which would have a class of table
that in which we can have a table had.
And now we can decide what we want to see on the table.
So what about the title and an edit button and a delete button.
OK.
Just follow them.
We need a table body which would have table was.
So looks like we're going to be looking through the table was to have all the civis display therefore
right here we should actually be passing the series.
So which series will pass and the switch variable.
Therefore we need to get all the series and pass it along so we can actually in line these just to make
sure that we stay in line as archaic weights.
Now in our view we have access to that therefore we can say for each.
Or we can actually use a 4 or else that will provide for us.
So for ours series as available as then we'd have our empty block and the and for hours.
BLOCK OK so if we have some serious loop through each of those and spits out a table but if we don't
we'll just have a tech center that says no series yet.
Then for this table would have table each hour that echoes all the series title that would of table
data.
Also with a Butson to the series and it's just going to say added.
So we'll have one for the elites and we'll talk about that later.
OK for us to see what we have to watch or what lay out fire and naturally creates a link so we can see
that.
So right here in the block let's add a link for weaving all the series and this we just see all series.
And if you want to know the exact route that actually leads to the Sui's control or index My thought
you can run ph we are somewhere at least.
And that will give us a list of routes and where we have.
I mean seriously it goes to series that index the index method.
OK.
So in our view of the blade ph we this should point to serious doubt index to view or series.
OK so let's try this out.
We're fresh.
We have to also reach spots on that.
Yeah.
So we have our switch right here.
The title edit button delete button.
So I should change this a little to something more visible which will be maybe a Butson info.
Yeah.
Great.
That looks better.
Now let's talk a little bit about editing and deleting our series.
And in the meantime we should start thinking about if we want some series to be published or not published.
And we're going to see how we'll manage that.