Let's think of what we need to update our series for example your credit series you want to edit the
title where you want to edit the image that was a blow that I think this is going to give us a little
bit of opportunity to learn something new.
So let's dive straight into it.
So obviously we're going to need a viewer for the edits.
So I'm going to create a new view in my scripts directory that I'm going to call edits that made me
and it's going to look exactly like the Crusades except that we're not going to be creating.
But we're going to be editing an existing series.
So looks are we going to be passing that series in to this view.
So it would just acquire the series.
Sayto So we know what we are doing then and the templates we're going to redirect this into puts requests.
Leave the CSR field and for us to actually make pooch's request we need to tell Lavoe that the methought
field is a portal.
So right here we are going to echo Methley field and Puss in Boots.
Then we have our title so we can assign the value of this title to be equal to the series title that
was passed into this view and we have our EMH and we have a description.
So let's call the correct description right here.
And the basic idea is when we submit this form it's going to update the title and the description.
But then if there is no fire fuel then it's not going to update that field.
OK.
So we need to direct this to the correct routes and pass the correct parameters.
If we check out our route list to update a series we put our patch request we submit that series pass
in the identifier and we are using our SLOC in this case and he has the point to see just the updates
and the screen to the update method.
Right.
So serious the updates is what we need.
We need to pass in the series log as a parameter.
So our automatic round model binding can take health.
And I think that's all we need to do in our funds.
Then we'll head over to our service controller and first will attack ads added my thought which should
we turn that view.
I mean serious as it is and it has to go with the series and we can automatically type in series right
here for a lot of water injected.
Great.
Then the update method which we're going to be taking care of that later that's just died down requests.
Okay.
So last off in our order blade the Peachtree where we have this table we need to pass in the correct
permits us.
So this should go to our routes which should be series that added.
And I think that's what we have.
That's what we have and U.K. as a parameter we should be a series SLOC.
Okay.
So let's try to sound refresh this page.
We have if we click on it it takes us to edit this series and then it gives us the title the field where
we can change everything and the update button and clicking on that makes a get request.
I think I know why that's because it's supposed to be a post request.
There's no such thing as a put request lovely automatically going to recognize it by the method field
right here.
OK.
So go back and then click on the updates.
There we go.
We have the data from our phones.
OK.
If we're actually to do or download or see a picture they're going to have an instance of upload that
fire right there.
OK.
So let's recap for updates.
First of all anti-Hindu is forced to have the series.
Now that we have the series.
We can update its properties now.
I would like to create a custom update service request where we can actually customize or take care
of everything in the background and validation and all of that stuff.
So I'll create a request.
He had to be sign make request or date Sui's request.
OK.
So if you had a Ratso update series request authorize or said that true.
Now the rules should have a title which must be required and a description which must also be required.
So we are not required to actually upload an email when we are dating but the title and the description
fields must be passed in the request.
Now I'd like to show you something we have some request right here.
We have our update series request and we have a quick request.
And if you check out our Queechy Richard Quest.
It has this long series.
MH mid-thought and what is this image mid-thought.
Is it loads the series on Sawston the name in this file named property on this class.
Now I want to use this exact same mid-thought so I'm going to copy it but I'm going to be all in the
new hour so I'm going to show you what I'm doing.
First of all copy this method to my update series and I'll paste in that thought.
So it's going to blow the series if we have image of that.
So in my control or what I can do is check each request house fire then would call request or bloats
series EMH.
OK.
So we have this image on the updates was the PH B.
So what are below the EMH.
And then once the image is below that we'll have this filename set and we could automatically do this
series.
MH You are all equals requests of us.
Imagine then will get the foreign name.
OK.
Because we actually set in defining property on this instance.
OK then we'll have to set the title because we know the title would be in the request.
I would also have to set the description.
And finally we need to update the series SLOC field.
So I would call the string SLUB method or we'll pass in the request Sithole and we'll just call series
Safe finally to posses that data.
And finally after we successfully see if the series will just return redirect to a route series that
index.
OK so first we check if there's an image if there is an image ablate the image you are fueled and we
are below the MH and then we update the title description slogs safe with the use up to the page where
he can view all the series.
OK.
So here we have all our series and I'm going to edit this one so I'm going to edit that title to maybe
best novel cost.
Change the description to maybe description of best novel cost and then upload a new series.
Maybe this one and then curricle ablate series and comments can be debated here we can see already that
this was at the top of the title.
So what do you want to check is if your image was actually as.
So I'm going to get all the secrets and if we cecal this one we have the slug of data or title of data
the image you are all also points to best level Casta PMG.
You check out the email in our story page there we have it.
So looks like everything is working as expected.
But in the very next video what I want us to do is go through this exact same process but when we go
into it using our test.
So we want to make sure that everything is walking like we wanted to work.