As East let's start having some fun week test.
But before we do that let's just make sure our whole process should is such really successful at this
point.
Yeah.
Looks like everything's walking.
So we're going to create a new test BHB percent make test.
And this is going to be update Sui's test.
OK.
So our first method we want to test is that the Beat actually works right.
So we can test a lot of different thoughts.
CAN I HELP US Reducto and help us clean up a little bit.
So public functions.
I use Arcanum beats a series.
OK.
So first of all we must love again.
I mean the story.
So before we go to see this Sekhon we would make pooch request to the specified endpoint and then we're
going to make some assertions.
So search storage has EMH for example also assert that the Tabby's hahs a particular view all of that.
OK so let's talk we want to log in as admin.
So we have our helpful this logging admin.
Thought OK this is actually going to look exactly like.
OK great series.
It says we have this logging at.
Or we can actually disable exception handling.
Why are we here so that we have clear us so we logging that into the streets or make a request.
So this is what we need it so we change this from post to boot's novel provides this for us.
So another being locked in us.
I mean what are we going to do is create a series so that we can update it.
So we create for the Sui's class.
So I'm just going to import this resource right here.
OK.
So now we have a series we can make a to quest to serve up to this series.
So I'm going to see this pooch request and end points that we used to or this series is Rauch's series
that dates and we Pasquin the series.
SLOC and then we need to passing on our way of the top.
We have a title and we'll just update each new series title.
We have a description just updated to new series description and we need a lot of fire because now we
are testing the complete update process so we are also doing this update.
So we have an image view which would be an instance of blue that fire.
But since we want to fix it we'll call our fake mid-thought and call the image metho up on the fake
below that fight and sunset behalf.
I we'll just call the EMH series the P and G.
OK.
So that's what we are applauding.
So our just imports of blue that are on the top so we don't have any horse then we'll make some assertions.
So let's just assert that the use ice redirects that after successful and let's assume that the session
costs something.
So I suspect that the session hahs session and this should be success really a beta series.
Now to make our test more reliable.
We can make sure that we are actually redirected to a particular route.
In this case see restudy index.
OK so we've asserts that that we have a redirect and we have a session.
Next we want to assert that the meet you saw.
So we have to fake the start h.
So with fixed all of each just like we did when we were creating a service.
So we used our h and then we can run an assertion for the storage.
So storage does this what's this be faked and then assert that you exist a serious image that peon G.
But the two should be this right here.
OK.
Because we are automatically gets into a string slot of the title and then we attach the end G.
And we're putting it in a series directory.
Then finally we want to assert that these are these Hosam what's called a value which is going to be
exactly the same like this.
So I said they are serious and the slots should actually be the string slot of the new title this.
OK.
Awesome.
So first we log in on the street so then we create a new series we fake the store which the config default
store each then we make a request on the server.
To this end point in a series slots lulav automatically knows what service we are of the end of the
title or description of late in the series.
Vaughan our assertions that we will glove Route 1 was a session that we have a session flash and then
we make sure that we have that story.
Then we finally make sure that we have that story in the database.
Ok so thats our test that's run that test individually and see what we get.
So picky in it with the fields of flock and trying with Futuna this test on the greats so we have our
first video for our search and not much is expected successfully of the Test series.
So it means this request was successful.
We successfully directed the use of the VCR and we have not saved this to the session so let's fix that.
And this is actually an obsession.
Let's give it a success.
OK.
Let me just run that test one more time oking gives us exactly the same.
Not what head of Butsu update series meathook right here at the box just fix this last session flourish
success and they should be equal to exactly the same string that we have here.
OK so successfully of detat series that's why not just one more time.
And now it's successful which means everything wharfs are specter.
But there's a little book in application that we didn't figure out a way in which we are going to actually
find out the very next Viji.