This a little bit of money will be behind the scenes that test does not cover.
So I want us to cover it right now.
Remember we are solving this and we are making sure that we actually store it in the correct path.
But we are not searching or making sure that we actually store exactly the same type of database.
So we're going to assert that the database has an image field which matches exactly the same way we
want to store it in a database.
So how serious slash new series sayto that P and G.
OK because we are looking to the series.
No actually we are street slugging the sites who are receiving a subpoena.
Right.
So this should exist in our database if everything actually walked correctly.
So let's run that yeah.
We have a failure because it doesn't fine that few because you've read notes or bouillotte C-rist mid-thought
right here when we are doing is simply assigning the MHRA to the filing.
But what we want to do is actually make sure that will be precise.
We want to see Vicini that's a serious directory.
Right.
So if we run that says Now one I'm Lougheed successful but we didn't speak this up.
OK so now that we've covered that point in our test like us to write some few thoughts asked just to
make sure everything was as expected.
So we're going on right now that says to make sure that if the image is not lead to other foods do just
fine.
So probably caution sayst and M.H. is not required to update Sui's.
Okay.
So how will this look pretty much exactly the same thing.
But we are not going to be building that image so will disable exception handling for better or for
all than lugging the user side streets or create a series Faktor store range.
Then we need to make that post request.
So make the push request but this time around we are not going to pass that image.
So pull out that image field and then with a certain date that assert that the session exists and now
about assessing for us so each what we agreed to do is we're going to assert that that fire does not
actually exist.
Now how do we check if this fire is actually missing.
We're going to see a certain missing method should be used rather than the assert exists.
Okay.
And law will actually provide this vehicle.
So we are going to assert that we are updating that series.
There is no major study of that.
And finally let's assert that the database does not have an update to that image but it hasn't of the
title obviously.
So right now here we're going to assert the Tabby's hahs for the series table a slot with the new title.
That's what we want.
So we don't want our MHRA fuel to change.
We want to be mean the same therefore we are going to assert or I said that the data base has a series
with this same image you are.
Okay.
Meaning it did not change at all.
We still have exactly the same image.
Yes.
So this field is not Abita because we don't want to overload an image.
And we want everything to succeed as usual without the image.
Okay that's honestest.
We will talk to this one rollout and it's successful because we are still creating still updating the
title description without the M.H. view on that.
And we actually already took care of this in a co-op.
Yes.
So one last test we can naturally write is make sure that the title is required to update a series.
So also make sure that the discussion is required but in the next video I want you are to lead a little
bit of reflux off because I have so many clients in my control which I'm not comfortable with and I'm
actually having duplicate methe thoughts in my requests classes for example we have this series M.H..
In this class I knew exactly the other class for create Seuss image so we're going to take care of that
and the very next Viju great up.