OK let's do a little bit of free FoxxHole.
Like I said I'm not comfortable with having this duplicate method.
It's not just cool.
OK.
So what I'm going to do is create a serious request and then the update service requests and the create
serious requests can inherits from this request.
OK so I'll see what I mean.
Let me create a request.
PH We sign make request and this is going to be serious request
OK.
So you know a serious request.
We have a blank credit right here.
But what happens is that if you want to make sure everything was in my test so that the Rifat saw stage
is when you actually make sure we didn't break anything like Saw the test run well no I would make sure
that there are these serious requests and the Christmas request inherit from this loss.
So I had a lot of dead serious request.
Now pulao this mid-thought cuts it out completely.
This seat my service request and pasted in.
OK.
So we have this mid-thought of the label.
Then in my obituaries requests are no longer winsby extending form requests from Larkhall but I'll be
extending series request so I know it is animal.
OK.
So our series of quest is not going to have an authorization Mithal because I want to take care of these
and the trout glossies and those are going to have Smith thought it's just going to have this method
that is common to both classes.
So which means in our quit serious requests we can also pre-loved this method completely and then it's
no longer going to extend for request but it's going to extend serious request not block this use.
And now everything should work as expected because this method now is common to both classes.
So let's run our tests again and see if we book anything.
Okay great.
We didn't break anything right.
But then we removed that to placation by also extending cost on request classes.
Now I'll have a watch through my series controller and I'll try to clean up these audio series.
So if Sourcefire we are overloading the series for a start let's just cut this out and just move it
into our service requests.
So I'm just going to call request of this series.
Okay then would I know what's in the update request.
Paste that then creates that mid-thought which was a serious case study.
So if request hausfrau will no longer be dealing with requests we'll be dealing with this.
So if this hausfrau updates us let's pause in the series into this method as a parameter or from our
current series
then this load suits you may get the file name and get this title get this description.
And finally also get this title then safe.
OK.
So right here we are data series plus the session with the user to the vault.
So if everything goes well we actually haven't broken anything and we can easily check that we are to
search.
Great.
We haven't broken anything but I think our controller looks cleaner when you come to our control or
you can we request updates serious and then you can visit Chris loss to see what series that is.
Great.
Great job.