Before we move on I'd like to make a very big and important Rifat so and it's going to give us a really
great opportunity to learn some stuff.
OK I'll head over to my web ph Ph.D. and you're going to notice that in most applications that you would
build your thoughts for is always going to be very very crowded.
And you don't want that because in future you want your outside to be clean so you can understand.
And that's kind of the main focus in this series.
We want every single file that we're dealing with to be as clean and understandable as possible.
So Lavoe provides us obviously with the possibility of creating our own Watchfire.
OK so we have with the Ph.D. and this is for routes that are in the web middleware group.
And we also have API Ph be.
And this is for a start and the API middleware group.
I'll see what I mean I can all the Ph be.
We have two middleware groups.
We have the web and we have the API and the web.
We just asked me the way that it uses like the cookies the session the very feisty SRF token Shehroz
from session and all that.
Now the API simply registers middleware that it uses like the bindings throttle.
And now since we have an administrator group like we see in our web PH BE we can have our own custom
middleware group and every single route that concerns administrators.
We go there and we would have really really caring about fires.
I'll show you how to do this to create a custom made aware group.
All we need to do is append this array so we can create an admin middleware group and like we said in
the middle weight group you just need to put in the middle where that are going to run for that particular
group of routes.
In this case I want all the middleware in this web to Ron because our users are assessing the application
using the web and therefore our simply see web here and he's going to register all the media we're in
this web group.
And also I want a customer the way that we critter's together which is the admin middleware to run.
Therefore I will cut this out and move it to my custom middleware group.
OK.
So this is for specific routes where we can reference avouch name the group name the middleware name
and actually use them on one route or many routes.
Meanwhile this is a completely grouped set of routes.
OK.
Just like we're seeing here now how do we use this group of robots if we want everything now.
It's going to work perfectly because Lovelle automatically understands if we're referencing a group
right here or a specific middleware.
OK but what we want to do is remove the need for this prefix and this automatically put everything in
an admin we found.
So let's quit that file.
I mean that should be and we can actually just move these files these routes like this to and place
them in that admin that we found and then we can clean up our CROSSFIRE.
But obviously obviously this is going to break the law.
We need to talk about the admin that Ph be.
And we need to register those laws.
How do we do this.
That's what's also ISKHANDAR and see how that stays for us.
First of all Lavoe actually really starts the web and API in the world service provider.
So for example it calls the map API routes and map out my thoughts right here.
And if you check out the map web WILESMITH thought it wraps all of the routes in the web the PH BE IN
of our group.
Right.
So first of all to me the way I thought and it's going to automatically come and pick up the middleware
web right here.
So all of the vaults in the web the Peachtree are wrapped in this middleware web group.
And then because the namespace method to set the namespace for control control stuff we want to use
this group and by default it's in the control directory just like we've been using.
And then it wraps them in a group from the web that we found right now for the API routes it prefixes
every single route there with an API stream and then it uses the Midwest API group just like in our
Canada the PH be this one.
And then it sets the namespace to the same namespace and then sets the path to API.
OK so we can actually create our own.
So we are going to call our own.
This map of main routes and then we're going to create that thought.
And in this method what we would do is call me to where I thought I would certainly that the middleware
group for this set of routes is the admin group like we created and then we're told that OK we won every
vouch for the administrators to be fixed with admin and then we also want to use a particular namespace.
This namespace.
And finally we want to group all of the routes together.
So I would say based path and we'll get them from routes slash.
I mean that be just like we created.
OK.
So everything should work as expected because we've really start all of the routes in admin the PSAP
with Lavoe using this method.
So we prefix all of them with admin just like we've been doing.
We protect all of them with the admin middleware and all of them are still in the controllers directory.
So if we head back to our application give this version of refresh we still have that we can visit our
series we can create series all of those vials us to register.
All right.
So now what I want to show you is what if we actually wanted to place all of this in an admin directory
all of the control that's the concern on the street is all we need to do is prefix the suite at me.
OK.
Because this namespace is actually a string that sits in a namespace that we want to save or control
us in.
So we have backups S2P control us and by default we've been just saving everything in the control as
directory.
But now that we have this method we can actually see them in the admin directory.
OK that's just going to make things a little bit clearer.
OK so if I refresh now sure enough it fails because it cannot find the Seuss controller in the admin
directory.
But what we are going to do is we're going to come to our controllers directory.
We're gonna create a new director called admin and then we're going to move the series controller into
that directory and things our admin the HP also has the lessons controller we are going to use also
move the lessons controller into that directory.
But now things are going to change when we are extending Cordula we need to import the controller.
Right.
So we're going to use but cost a.p control loss controller.
OK.
So referencing this fire right here and every single controller in sight should also imparts the controller.
Last thing is to update the namespace.
So we have to see we're in the admin namespace.
And finally here we also have to reference the admin namespace.
OK so let's try again refresh.
And there we are we are back to successful.
So all of those walls have been registar and we've successfully refactored into our admin directory
which makes things a little bit cleaner and understandable for us.
Okay so one last explanation of what we've been doing.
We have a web ph P for how we also have an API that ph be provided by default for us.
And what does Lavoe do in the World Service Provider Lovelle has methods that we just pass the routes
in these fires.
So for example the weap routes in the web the PSP have been namespace to the control us down a tree
and they have also been rapt with all the middleware in the middle where weap group.
Ok this group right here and we can find this group in our Canada Ph be.
So all of this middleware applied to all of the routes in the web that Ph be.
Now if we also check out the API group it also wraps all of the middleware in that fire which is the
API that should be in Middleware from the middleware group called API.
It also prefixes all of those boucherie API and then it also places them in a namespace by default with
use control us.
Now we can also create our own custom middleware group by simply append introduce our read like we did
right here.
Apply all of the away from the weather PSAP and also apply our custom administration me to whether we
create as a check if the user is an administrator or.
And finally we prefix all of those watching.
I mean and then we also live up to them in that me that were custom that we created.
And we were friends that far as admin the pitch we changed the namespace to admin namespace and that
said we've customized our system.
Every single one of our control our science and ministry of choice in this admin directory and also
I think everything looks cleaner.
OK.
So what we found was no longer going to be crowded.
We have only the assertion about essential was the concern what the Ph be.
And if we want to register watch for our administrator or we can do that in the admin ph be pretty cool
right.
OK so thank you see you in the next lesson.