I'd like us to start working on fun and a little bit.
Now I have important played right here which I'm going to use to display the featured screen screencast
when it gets in the featured series.
Yes but we want to actually just display a series from a database to the front end users.
How are we going to be doing that.
I have a template right here so we're going to get that data from the database.
And that's really displayed.
OK.
Now we're going to be talking more about images.
I like to start by creating a new controller that I'm going to call it free of.
Make the phones and.
And all of those little vaults like the welcome page are going to be accessed from this controller.
So if I head over to my web browser we have this Clozaril right here and I'm going to switch on right
now and I'm going to tell them to use the funds and controller and we use the welcome massage.
Ok for the welcome page.
So LA and the welcome and this Welcomer thought simply returns the view welcome like before but now
we want to actually display some series right here.
So what I want to do is I want to get all the Swiss on the database for now and then I'm going to meet
all of them on the front page.
So we'll just see this view with see race.
I would get serious or OK then on this view would now have access.
So if I visit my welcome to the Ph.D. We can now have access to that collection.
Therefore I would look to all of the connection using of or else be favorably and would see Sui's as
maybe available less than what my friends are empty blog.
And and files.
So in this foil spots we can paste up templates.
And now let's just start by customizing the cost side so so get the series get the title and right.
Yeah we can actually just get the Sui's description.
OK.
So let's see how this looks.
Refresh OK.
So we have to see recent Abita is the best Lavoe costs and advanced with just beginners course.
So this is the description of Yousif to each of his.
Now let's talk about the images.
I'm going to show you something right here.
If I simply echo out the series you match your own.
Now we see with fresh you just that we actually saved the name of the fire without actually saving the
path.
Remember we agreed we can put it in the series.
But then that's a little like an obligation that I'm going to show you later.
But the right says to fix it.
And that is when we're updating the see which we don't actually concatenate the response.
Right.
OK.
We're going to take care of that later.
So how do we display this image from our storage.
Now first of all remember if you want to actually display an image from your storage directory then
that image has to be in a public disk.
OK.
So you have to make sure it's in the public debate tree in your store each directory.
So we have our story directory and we have app which is the default look disk.
And if you wanted to be visible to the public you have to put it in the public directory right here.
OK.
So the first thing that we're going to be doing is making sure that we actually save our images in the
public directory.
We are going to be taking care of in the next lesson.
And the second thing we want to make sure is we actually see if the correct path into our database which
we're also going to be doing that in the next lesson with our tests.
But for now we want to see how we can actually display the images that we have right now.
So the first thing you have to know display images from your store which it must be in the store is
public actually.
So I'll just move my series directory into the public directory just for now and the next thing I'm
going to do is I'm going to run a command the law will provide for us which is BHB artist and Stone
Age leg.
OK.
And if you look at what these commandos he creates are stylish in public public the right here.
And most everything in that public directory to the public directory up here.
Now what happens now gives us the permission to display all of the files from the public directory as
easy as that.
So if you want that to display this image right here would head of what's where we have these assets
and would reference that fire.
Right.
So let's just see it will out.
I said my thought because the acid mid-thought assesses the assets from this public directory.
Right.
And we need to get into our storage in a treat and then we have a serious directory and that's where
we have the fire that has been seized.
So right here this is where we're going to concatenates with the Stone Age series.
You make your own.
OK.
So store each tree series than the series image you're on.
That's what we're going to have.
So let's refresh the page to see what we have.
Yeah it doesn't display anything.
Let's inspect to see what's going on.
And we have a series but cause this means we need a slush right here.
OK.
So let's refresh one more time.
There we go we have images display but this image is not just mean obviously because we don't have that
image in our system.
Right.
So we can actually display the images from our Stone Age but our system does not walk as a spectator.
We're actually just learning how to display from us each time a tree.
But we have to make sure that when we're saving the image into our storage the way we receive it into
the public now we're actually also so that we can access it using Petchey Alasan Strobridge link.
And we also have to make sure that we're be updating our series.
The image is actually updated on the correct path it's saved into the database.
OK.
So let's take of that the very next video.