One of the great advantages of having a message like we have is that when you want to be facts or life
gets very easy because all you need to do is write your test.
Keep running the test with factoring and making sure that the test to pass.
OK.
So right now we want to change the way we create series.
We want to test that the image such we receive in a particular direction.
Therefore we're going to update our test run the test and make the test pass.
OK.
So a user can create a series.
Let's start there.
What we want to do is make sure that it's received in the public directory.
So we are going to update our assertion and our storage facility here.
It's been asserted that exist in the public service directory and the file name is the same the way
we want.
OK.
And we can go ahead and run this to us now to see what we get.
So run this
yeah.
And we have a failure because it's unable to find a public series this right because it's not in the
public directory.
So remember we be factored into our series request the mid-thought that actually uploads the series
image.
So what we're going to do is come to this and stop publicly as thought within its early to see if in
the probably serious direction.
That's it.
Let's run our test right now and see if it changes anything.
And we're back.
GREENE So we have a successful test.
So we are successfully out of the team and serving our public directory so that every time we want Peachtree
or Sunstone which link is going to automatically link those fires.
OK.
And by default when we deposit or put out into the storage tree and the storage nature has been lying
labo is automatically going to sync with this each.
Probably no way to right.
OK.
So another thing we want to do is make sure that we are updating a series.
The fire is actually deposited in the correct tree after we update the Sui's.
OK.
So let's head over to our update series Test.
Right here we are checking to see if in the series a tree.
Let's make sure it's see in the public service directory.
OK.
Let's run that test loop.
So copy the name.
Run the test and now it passes.
OK.
Because remember how of series request is actually extend indescretion quest.
Therefore everything will change in this which of course also reflects on dishcloths.
OK.
So let's run our street now to check if we have anything successful.
We have it and we haven't broken anything.
Therefore every single wish we quits now since the killings are still reasonable.
We is going to automatically make it public so we can display it in our views.