This your rebuttal application actually using test right.
So we write to test making POS and then we see OK this feature WAPs But now we need to see the practical.
So let's create a new series and I'm going to call that yes we can this cause all of those.
A serious image.
And I'm going to put in just cause description right here is the description.
And in this series and everything works fine.
We should have a new image of loaded into our public service directory.
OK.
So great series and now we redirect that to this page.
Let's check out our storage directory in our snobbish directory.
Now we have a serious directory and we have the imagery of it.
But now in our public domain we we also have the storage and we have the series directory and we have
this image also.
So much can be synchronized.
The imagery uploaded right now we have that image publicly available for us.
So how do we deal with it.
Two displays either back to my home directory and we don't have that image displayed.
So what I would like to do is actually create a lot more access all of these assets is going to give
us the correct path to view this image.
OK.
How do we create this level so to create this level assets off.
We are going to be using a unique test.
So quite a unique to us.
PH We are sun make test and this is actually going to be in our series class so I'm going to make the
tax code series and I'm going to so level.
It's a unique test.
OK.
So if you head over to our test directory and you tell what you need we would have the seasonal Ph be.
Now what's the difference between the unit test and the feature test.
Remember our feature set is mostly going to make its DTP request.
So he is dealing with a lot of applications as a black box.
You putting in a request an aspect but love response out.
But then when you Nita's are going to be Methot for cost or class for cost.
So we want a method to function in a particular way and we want a media class to function but to allow
each one unit test at the unit level.
OK.
So the first one is I'm going to test series can get image path.
OK whatever name suits you.
So first of all we need to test that they use that image and get a C response.
And what we are going to be doing is creating a series series because factory and that will be for the
series KLOS will persist that through that data base.
Now I would like to overwrite that before that is creature in the series.
Now let just set my own M.H. you are.
I hope so I can passing on Judy's creator mid-thought and I'm going to see the MHRA all should be set
to series and I'm going to see civies small p and G because this is the format that we're using to save
into our database right now what we want to do is want to get in each BAAF to be able to squeeze M.H.
path.
Okay.
And we're going to run on a session so US-CERT equals and our expectation is that it should be store
H series series slot that P and G.
Okay.
Because remember we have published to our public directory and we start each series and then the EMH
path.
OK.
So we are asserting that this image is equal to the image that we have right here.
Okay.
So on I see wristlets we should be able to have an image of property that is automatically going to
get this from the database and actually give us this.
Okay let's run this to us.
PH BE IT FEEL talk to this to us.
No notes us executed it looks like we need to prefix this retest so that level knows this is one of
our testifiers and we mean these two series Sest.
Okay.
So let's run that.
And now we have a field test also so what does it say.
CS on able to look at facts you read name test unique Sui's.
So we need to specify our path.
So back to past series class one that says you say tests you need but Kassovitz I'm sorry.
So we have to ask to be checked from that region run again.
And now we have filled our search in that no matches.
Expect that study series three small puji.
Now how do we get this sort of syntax from Lovelle we simply use what we call access.
All right.
So what I said is we do get something from the database and before returning it to us each week to edit
it in some way or another.
So in our series the BHB we're going to create an accessible public function and formats for us Aussies
get and then M.H. POS.
So the case for how we want to use the assets and what that attributes at the end.
So let me ask you which is simply supposed to return to us a particular string.
Right.
So would return Stone Age concatenates with this.
MH You are.
OK.
So let's run that again.
And now the test passes.
But we're using some little magic behind the scenes.
So now we have an asset so that we can use by simply calling series M.H. boss and we'll get the correct
path to display that image in our views.
OK.
Now this is an option you might want to consider and that is you know a test rather than testing that
the path is correct.
We can test that that you are or is correct.
So we can see as I said this because we have a helper said mid-thought unlovable that is going to get
you are all for this resource and we can run our test using that.
Now we have a fitting test because this is what we expected when we use the asset in a thought.
And this is what is returned from our.
So we can now Rob all of this in our asset mid-thought run that again.
And now we have a successful test.
Great.
So remember when you're actually testing using the asset mid-thought you're that in the file contain
the correct credentials right here like the you're on.
If not love is going to try to get these you are in the testing environment and if it's not set correctly
you might have a feeling just okay.
So that's it we were able to write a new unit test that makes sure that when we call MH but it gives
us the correct path to the image now that we have that we can tell us all well that ph we are wellcome
and rather than a queen out asset and all of these Longstreet's we can just call Seabreeze get M.H.
path and that's it.
Let's refresh the.
Great.
And that's our image.
So looks like what's has successfully told us that we can get the image.
And now we can successfully get that image BAAF.