Let's take applications to the next level I want to start building or learning management system so
that we know which user and wardens will cost.
I've started watching a series.
We know what lessons a particular user has watched.
We know what the juice is washed and we can tell him OK you finish this lesson.
You haven't finished this one.
This one has been updated.
And none of that stat. OK.
So for that we are going to be using redis.
OK.
We want to store the ID for example of a series that the user is watching.
And then we also start the lessons for that particular series that the user is watching and we want
this to be for every individual user.
So redis is actually a very good place to start because we're going to be starting these in key value
pass and then for the use of it just going to get that key and where this is going to make this really
really fast.
We want to make API calls.
We want to check this and we're going to making hundreds of requests and Ready's is going to actually
make this fast enough for our needs.
We can use a database like Maskil but it's going to really be slow so we're going to use this database
server.
OK so before we actually dive into redis let's just have a quick refresh on what where this is how it
works.
So that will be able to start building the elements in the next video.
OK.
So if you haven't heard about where this race is simply a key value store but it's really advanced because
it exists in memory.
Therefore it's not storing It's information on the local harddrive but it's going to be married.
Then you can get it really fast.
OK.
Now before we use Reddy's in our vote we required pulling the Reddy's package so spearheads is it's
like the Holy Mother of Kuwaiti's in the Peachtree community.
So go ahead and put that in.
And once you put this in your set you use Reddy's for lovers so are required Pirelli spearheads should
get you that.
OK so now how do we communicate with redis.
First of all I'm going to show you a database that PSAP you should have Reddy's installed in your computer.
So if you have these installed then these are the configurations to connect to your various local server.
Now I'm using logging on my Windows computer therefore I automatically have this up and running and
I can connect to the localhost with mine with these credentials.
And this port and this password.
And I'm going to use by default the zero database.
OK so automatically I'm connected to when he's been if you're using a Mac then you can download various
and install really easy maybe with homebrew or something like that and you're already going to be up
and running once you install the package that we talked of.
OK.
So let's go straight to it.
How are we going to be using redis.
We're going to be studying keys and those keys we're going to keep values and then we're going to be
getting it later to maybe make some analogies or something like that.
I'm going to create a dummy route here which is a Getz and we're going to be walking with the browser
to see this in action.
OK.
So create a wildcard for this and I'm going to create my first video.
Come on before we go into that.
I'm going to show you the kind of these are types that we have for greatest the most basic the very
basic is a key and a value and this value ease of data type string.
OK.
The next we have is obviously key value but the value now will be of the least.
And the last we'll be talking about is key value pair and this will be of data type set.
There are about three or four more but we're going to talk about this ones.
OK.
Now let's start by testing out a key value for a string.
We'll call our Ready's fancied and the ready Seracini has a search command which actually gives us some
more thought and we can set a key.
And for example I'll give Diski friend and our set the value to him or whatever.
OK.
So it's the Reddy's Saudi ski.
And whenever we need the ski give us this value.
OK.
So this is what is going to be stored right here.
So it's kind of like objects in javascript or Jason if you want to see that.
OK.
So when we call these routes it's going to store that into our redis.
So.
So let's reset.
So this is read this ah that box is going to be my ready store for my locale so I'll just change it
up to the whole route command this one out then so that and this is the home route.
Now we have a blank page because we said this now to prove that we actually said that our command is
out and then we're going to learn how to get keys from redis.
OK.
So I'll call my accommodate them and see Ready's who gets mid-thought and we'll get the friend key.
So it's a level that we set in the last request.
Give it to us.
OK refresh.
There we go.
That's the key reset right here.
So we can saw a string in a key and we can get it using this method.
Now if you had a lot to try that where is that.
I know you're going to learn using this interactive console command how to use redis.
Now you're going to learn a lot of these commands and novel gives us and Lovelle gives us a really easy
way to use these commands by automatically getting the method that you are trying to call and Castanea
to read events command.
OK.
So if you want to use maybe an hour range command has a method for our range.
Now let's talk about our next data type and the data type we're going to be talking about is the least
not a strange simplest source a string right.
But this is going to give us the possibility of starting a list of values.
Let's just think of it as an array.
OK.
So if we see Reddy's we can call the elbow's command which is simply going to push a list item into
a list.
Think of it as pushing an item into an array and you have to pass in the name of the weights or we're
just going to maybe see teachers or framework's and we can pass in an array of values.
We can see the huge ass Lavoe and this command is going to check into this database.
Is there a key called framework's if there is none it's going to create a new one and then it's going
to take all of these values right here and it's going to push into that key.
So let's refresh that's a set that would commend this out and would learn how to get the least when
we saved them into the database so we're called a dummy again so we can see the value.
So we would call Reddy's and commom begin to call is the Elwin.
Come on.
And this command first of all takes in the least WCM.
We want to get.
And then it's going to take into more commands.
So this are range specifically for this.
All right.
So when we pushed our lease and we want to get the least we can pass in the name of the list and this
compartments are easy to offset.
We want to start.
Think of it as an RV.
So if once you start from offset zero to offset five then we can specify like this.
But if we want to get everything from said zero to the end of the list or our rate if you want to think
of it that way then we can possibly get one right here.
Okay.
So we died on the resort from this command mine.
Refresh There we go.
So we have Lavoe and we just in that list which reach into us us and we so our own comment this common.
And I'm going to refresh.
And now you see automatically the push is pushing to the frameworks list and we can see the results
by calling this method and not just how really fast redis is doing this for us.
OK.
So we've sort of at least we've talked about about strings but let's talk about sex.
Sex is simply a list but the difference between a set and a list is that a set is not going to let you
put in duplicate values.
OK.
So let's create Ready's ask.
We're going to be creating a set called France and frameworks and we're going to add some values so
maybe England are a member.
OK.
So if one of these women should quit a such court for infant walks which is just think of it as a list
and then saw Angola and Imber into its run the come on OK which shows nothing then of commend this out.
And then I'm going to use a Reddy's command to get that set.
So are they done Reddy's members is the commander we could be using.
I will post in the name of the key.
So the name of the key right there was front and Filmworks.
OK.
So let's run the command.
OK so we have Imber and and love right there.
It just looks exactly like a least.
But if we are calling this out and try to run that command multiple times we discover that the list
does not change no matter how many times we run it.
OK.
So it's a really good data structure that we can use to store unique values.
So for example if you want to count the number of visitors to our Web site you can store the IP addresses
of the visitors and we extol these values in a list so that if a V-Star visits twice the IP address
is automatically going to be rejected by Reddy's it's not going to save the IP address twice if you're
seven you know this.
OK.
So that's basically what we want to do with redis.
We want to maybe have a key that is called you and then we pass the ID of the user and then we also
pass the ID of the series so we can say use our 121 series to me.
And then this will be much to an array.
And this is going to contain the IDs of all the lessons that these use are hos was for this particular
series something like that.
OK.
So that's the idea I have We're going to talk about it.
Molly Barrett If you need a greater refresh of Ready's make sure you try out the race teacher right
here.
It's really easy.
Can be done it in five minutes.
And you're going to know pretty much all the Reddy's Comanche need to know.
OK.
So thank you so much for watching.
Let's see it in the next video.