Let's stop having some of your fun.
So we've already talked about how we're going to be using this now.
Well I want to do is create a couple of units that are going to help us drive all the functionality
that we want to have in our learning management system.
So we wanted a user to be able to complete a lesson.
We also want to use to be able to complete a series and we want to start a track record of the series
that the user has completed a number of lessons completed by the user and all of that.
So we're going to be using uniters because we want to test specific methods on the use of class that
stored the records of progress for our user.
So I'll start by creating a unit test.
Are sand makes us and our Codys use access on our specify that each unit.
So every single test I one to test the concerns the use of class we're going to put it in the issues
or tests.
OK.
So the first test I'm running is test.
A user can complete a lesson.
OK.
So what does this test really mean.
I want to have a user in my system and I want this use to click on the start series button which is
going to take him to the page where he can watch the episodes or lessons in this series.
And once he finishes to watch a lesson it should automatically save the ID of the lesson in the wretch's
database to tell us that this user has really watched this lesson.
OK so maybe we're going to have a key like use are.
And then passing they use us I.D. and then we're going to have series for that particular series I.D.
and then we're going to map this to an array that stores the IDs of all the lessons that the user has
watched in this particular series.
OK.
So instead we would have you use are you create a new use or create a new series then would perform
an action and we might call a complete lesson.
My thought on I use.
And and finally we can make some assertions we can assert that our Ready's database has a key user with
the ID of the user then the ID of the series and then assert that he actually has an array that concerns
that contains the ID of that lesson that the user completa.
OK so let's try this out.
So my question I use I use are equal Sfar tree creates.
And we're going to specify that we want for the use of class.
So we'll create a series also and will specify a sou'west class.
And if we want to complete a lesson we need to also create a lesson.
So I would say lesson factory and I would see for the lesson class and would create and for testing
purposes.
Let's make sure that this lesson actually belongs to the series by overwriting the series ID field from
our factory and making sure that we put in our own ID which would be the suicide we just created right
here.
OK.
Then would call or use our complete lesson mid-thought and for us for our session would say this our
search equals Radice and would use as members because we want to see it in a set.
Remember we use in a sense because we don't want duplicate values.
It's just like a list but it's not going to allow us to store duplicate values into that list.
Or are we.
OK.
So we want to assert that when we call Ready's to get a key which is user and the idea of that user
actually one and the series idea should be one.
This exact key should march and array which has ID 1.
OK.
So when we complete lesson one it should create this key which is for the series that this lesson belongs
to.
And we fully specify that it belongs to series one because remember we're going to be using a fresh
database right.
So this use all the idea of one series idea of one lesson of one also.
And we're trying to make sure that this key will exist in our ready store and it would automatically
be equal to the radius ID of one.
OK.
Now before we want this test I'll do a little creek of imports one for broadcast used for the lesson
and the sooks.
OK.
Let's run these tests individually.
One hit.
We have a culture on the find mid-thought complete lesson.
So ahead of us who may use our class and our credit my thought
OK run again.
And then we can find this.
So my test and our use ready to proceed run again expected that we had nothing.
But after all we're supposed to be an array.
OK.
So we want to walk in our complete lesson method.
Now looks like we really need to know the particular lesson that we are completing.
So this my thought let's pass in the lesson that we have here.
OK.
So we're going to accept that lesson into this thought and what we want to do here is save this and
we'll see as that is the method we want to call.
So it's adding to a set and the set has to be of a particular pattern.
Right.
Remember we said we need to use our car loan they use our ID.
So we going to call this I.D. and then we need the Sui's I.D. So we will cause serious car loan and
then we'll call the lesson I will get a serious relationship I will get the I.D. from there and the
value that we're going to be adding is the lesson ID.
OK.
Understand.
So for us to achieve this key we need the use of ID which is one right here.
We need a serious I.D. which is this one and then we need to put in the lesson I.D. which is this key
right here.
OK.
So we are actually building a unique key so that it would be unique for every Yousaf which takes a particular
series OK so let's run this test and see what we get.
Hope everything does not blow up.
OK.
But gas really is not fun.
We just need to import.
So use ready Swazey
one that again tried to get property of known object.
And I think that should be common because we don't have our relationship or lesson for lesson.
I'm serious.
OK.
So what are the what are lessons lost I will create a relationship for that so return this belongs to
the series class.
OK.
So let's run that.
And we still get a failure.
So why don't we do this with headbutts or I use OUR And I'm gonna copy the stream right here and I'm
going to use a day dump just to know the result of that stream operation right there just to make sure
we are truly saving the correct string to the database right.
So let's run that test.
We have use our 12 series 13.
So we actually are not refreshing our database which means we are not getting fresh data.
So let's use Refresh database traits right here.
OK.
So this is what I do most of the time.
If I don't understand why something is happening it's just like unsoldered locking javascript.
You can write them anywhere you projec to see what's going on at that particular point.
OK so let's run this.
And great.
We have a successful test.
OK.
So that's how we can actually complete a series.
And then later in our project we can get the series or lessons that a particular user has completed
by getting this key.
OK.
So for now let's Rifat So this lieto we have a user.
We don't need to create a series right here.
We're not using the series variable.
What we're going to do is simply place it as such.
OK.
Because this lesson automatically is going to generate a new series and we can use that series here.
So this is necessary complete the lesson.
And I said that what the array that the Ready's as members mid-thought returns to us is exactly this.
OK.
One that says one more time.
Michel we've not broken anything.
Great Red Green.