Let's talk about a little Ready's future Remember this is a persistent database that for every time
we said this key is automatically going to be persisted into the story.
OK.
But now when we want to run our test we want a fresh copy of the database just like we're doing right
here.
We are in my database right.
So we're going to actually create a command that would help us to clever ideas in any situation we want
to clarify so we can call this maybe flush with this.
Every time we want to flush our Reddy's database before actually performing our test on redis.
OK.
So our head of our true test case the Peachtree in my test directory and I'll quit that mid-thought
so probably function flush ready is and this would simply call redis.
And we have a flush or method and this is.
And this would delete all the key stuff we have in all of our databases in our ready store.
So you shred this year.
And every time we run our test it's going to automatically flush redis.
So if we want to clean up the database before running our test we just we just need to call that method.
OK.
Now one more thing I want to talk about is access right here is making sure that we can save the first
lesson and the first series into our database.
OK.
Meaning that in a User class we can relieve them of this and a 2 to 1.
And the sun also set it to one and this test will still pass.
But then that's not what we want.
OK.
We want to that this test should pass for all series and all lessons therefore what we're going to do
is just for our own security creates another missing
and this lesson will belong to another series because we're just used to create.
But what I want to do is pass and of our rights into this creates.
And I would say serious ID should be one.
OK.
Because you remember a series is going to be created with idea of one from this first call and would
avoid this one.
Also have one therefore this to see which belong to the series that is which I'd like you to see which
is the idea of one.
Now when we call use of complete lesson would also call use our complete lesson on the second lesson.
So we know that the user can actually complete a second lesson also then we're going to assert that
this equals one and also equals 1 and 2 OK.
So when we get this key for the user of ID 1 and the series Id want it should show us that we've completed
less than 1 and less than 2 and they should be in the area that is returned.
OK.
So if our method actually was as a specter we should have exactly a successful test.
Even after all the changes we've made.
So let's run that.
Okay great.
Looks like we're good therefore we can complete the number of lessons we want.
And it also can now walk out perfectly.
OK great job.