OK how about this.
We want to know the percentage complete for a particular series.
OK.
So we should be able to call our percentage completed on the series for a user and would know if this
use complete or 20 percent or 30 percent or 100 percent depending on the number of lessons that exist
in the series and a number of lessons that this user has already watched.
OK.
So let's start with a test test can get percentage complete for our series for our use Yeah crappy names
but they're going to work just fine.
OK.
So looks like we need a fresh ready States or maybe for this.
We need a new user.
We need some lessons like Lesson one lesson too.
We need to complete this on one complete lesson too and we might have a couple more lessons in that
particular series.
But we would only complete lesson 1 and 2 then we're going to make some our sessions.
OK.
So I'll just copy all of this paste and I will just create two more lessons and I'll make sure that
I specify that the series ID for these lessons should be serious ones so that they belong to each one.
OK.
So my lesson class for Archie right here.
So let me duplicate this so I have two lessons created.
So we have one two three four lessons belonging to this one series.
Now we complete only less than 1 and less than two.
Therefore the percentage completed should be 25 right.
So let's do this let's assert each course and would call use our percentage complete set for series.
So this is the name of the math thought and the past in the series.
And since we don't have the series in this case we'll just get lesson.
I will call serious.
OK.
So with puss in the series and we expect this math to return to us.
Twenty five right.
So that's good for a start.
Let's go ahead and run this one here.
So we have caught on defraying use our percentage computed for CBS mid-thought.
We don't have that.
So copy this to my User class and now we have that my.
And it's sticking in the suits run that.
So I said to not 25 machines expect that.
Right.
So now let's work on this my thoughts you see that it actually gives us 25.
The expected percentage completed.
OK.
So we've completed two lessons and two lessons in the series are left.
So what do we do.
That's a good number of lessons in series would be caught are you serious lessons.
I will call the count method because we have our collection.
Yes.
Then we'll get number of completed.
Lessons will be equal to.
And how do we get the number of completed lessons we just need to get as members and then get the number
of elements in there.
I read that we receive.
So why don't we do this.
We'll use our Get number of computer lessons for Sirius and we'll pass in the series right here.
OK.
So this we are in our User class we would call this so we have a method on this class that can actually
give us the number of computer lessons for our series.
Ok so now we have this what do we do we need to calculate a percentage therefore to do that we just
need to return a number of complete lessons divided by the number of lessons in the series and then
multiply that by 100.
OK.
So this is basic math and if I don't get it right we're going to search on the internet to have how
to do that with math OK.
But I think for us to get the percentage.
It's the Pashtun are divided by the total number and then much by about 100.
OK so in this case the number of completer lessons would be to the total number of lessons will be for.
So to do other by four should give us 0.5.
And then if we multiply by 100 It should give us 50 therefore that's what we should be expecting right
here right.
So we are having.
We are completing two lessons and then we are having four lessons.
Therefore the percentage computer should be 50 percent.
OK.
So in a lesson class we just get the number of lessons in the series get the number from teacher lessons
and we turn a percentage.
OK.
So let's run our test again.
And now we have this ever seen caught on to find mid-thought get number of completed lessons for series.
OK so we need to quit this method and this mathematics in the seeress that's run the test and he sees
fit asserting that 50 matches expect that zero.
OK because this mid-thought is returning obviously the wrong value.
So now to make sure that this method actually returns the correct value.
What are you going to do is therefore create a unit test to make sure that this method works correctly.
And then we're going to proceed to make sure that our existing tests that we are running right now succeeds.
OK.
So the next we do where we walk on the Get number of completed lessons for CBS test.