We already have an existing test to see that we can we can actually complete a lesson.
Right.
So rather than creating a unique test for our Get number of completed lessons we are going to really
test that functionality right here.
OK.
So we are asserting that this is an investment thought for this particular key is going to return this
array.
Right.
So we're going to do is create another assertion and this will be our search equals and would call our
method.
So I would say they use or let me copy the method name get them off computer lessons for series or pay
study.
And we need to pass in the series so we'll just get less on CBS.
And we want to make sure that this method returns true because these are it contains two lessons that
we completed.
OK.
So we want to said that this method returns too.
I think this is going to help us actually make sure that this method works as expected.
So we are back to running this test
and if we want it of course now it feels because too much is expected.
All.
So let's make that pass.
We're going to see this menthol should simply return this and will get as members.
And the key we are searching for is use our call on this ID card on Sirius.
CARLSON And Sirius ID.
OK.
So we get this Ari and we can now call Cowen's to get the counts of the elements in this area.
So if everything goes well this should actually pass right now because we are using Ready's automatically
to get that and then return the cons.
OK.
So let's run that are angry.
Meaning that this test actually successfully passes not we've actually verified that we can actually
get the number of completer lessons for series for a particular user.
Now we're going to continue on with this test.
So let's run it and see the next arrow we have and we're successful right because this method now successfully
calculates the percentage right here just like we doing.
Okay.
So for us to make sure that we're actually really successful why don't we place 10 right here to make
sure that this is not just passing for some reason behind the scenes.
So we have a figure now so we have 50 but it feels expected 5 1 0.
So we should have and if we run that we are green again.
So thanks so much for watching.
Let's continue in the very next video with some riffraff all.