At the moment we have a successful test suite like it's in C so we run tests and of them are successful
with successful sessions.
Now this is the advantage of having tests in your application.
For example you can use your test to make sure that everything is going fine in your application at
any point.
Now we want to do a little defacto and think of refactoring as making our code better writing better
code making things look better using the best of my thoughts on stuff like that.
OK so now that everything is successful at the end of every or everything should still be successful.
We didn't break anything we didn't write any new tests but everything too successful.
OK so I'll head over to my use of a patch and I'm going to show you something that Lavoe doors on lots
this use treats like here.
So what level D'Arcy's if it discovers that a lot of functionality can be hidden behind a tree it's
used to treat and it uses a concept of single trigger responsibilities.
For example right here we square that the notifiable tread Its responsibility is to contain my thoughts
that deal with notifications for users.
Therefore even though tweets can be used by multiple entities or multiple classes most of the time you're
going to see that Lavoe uses traits only in one class and it's a very Kooning way of compressing your
math thoughts behind classes.
So what we're going to be doing is move out all the functionality that has to do with completing lessons
getting lesson percentages and all of that stuff and with Heidi being a traitor.
And I'm going to call this creates a learning trait.
OK.
So in my Abdur tree I'm going to create an entity a tree and I'm gonna save that tree in there.
So I'm going to see learning the Ph be.
OK.
So this is going to be a Ph.
Before we did the namespace which is parked cars and teaches and this is going to be a trait called
learning.
OK.
So not only have these traits are the words my use of the B and I would use the stretch so use learning
and we need to import the streets at the top so use but broadcast entities and get into a PH BE GREAT.
But how does this help us all of this my thoughts that have to do with completing the lessons.
We're going to cut them out so from here Macken lesson completed for use are and right down to the bottom
we'll cut them out which will make our class look very clean.
And then in our reach we'll just paste them in right.
OK.
So this now is obviously going to be fed to the class or the stance that is using using this.
And for us to avoid having any errors.
We have to use the Ready's phosphate so that this treaty is going to have access to it.
OK.
Now that we've removed all the functionality from my User class and we've hidden behind attrit I want
use classes clean.
We need to run our test to make sure that we didn't break anything.
And great That's it.
We successfully created a trait put that functionality in it.
And our test is still passing.
So this is a really great advantage of having us.
You could change something in your application and check that everything still works.
I suspect that using your tests.