OK access to the queen.
Now what do we want to do is test a little bit more my thoughts that we're going to be using for our
learning process and then we're going to go to the next step.
Now the first thought I want to test is a thought that I'm going to start that series and this method
is going to help us know if you actually clicked on that starts with Martin and is actually watching
the series.
OK.
So this is going to be a unique test like this.
So you know I use that as we're going to create a new test so public function science can know if a
user has started a series.
OK.
So how do we want this test to work.
First we need a user right and then we need maybe to see race and then they use our watches or completes
a lesson in the first series.
And he does know which one in the second series.
Ok then we asserts that we turn into four has started a series for the first series and then has set
that series for the second series does not return true it returns false.
OK so let's go ahead and do it you'll understand more.
So first of all since we had to live with Reddy's we're going to flush with this.
So flush Reddy's will get to use our Krikalev son also create some from them lessons just like we're
doing here.
And I think we're going to need all of this.
So I'm going to copy that come right here to my instep and pasted it so use up and then we have a lesson
and we have two one on lessons right here.
So what I'm going to do is the son and this and two should belong to one series.
So two series one just like it is now and then I'm going to create lesson to see which should belong
to and not the series.
Therefore I'm going to remove this customizing right here.
So we have two lessons that belong to series one.
And then we have one lesson that belongs to Sui's 2 which is going to automatically be created by this
tree.
OK.
Now we want to complete a lesson in serious one.
So I would say use our complete lesson and let's say he completes Lesson 2 for example.
Ok then we can run our sessions.
We're going to see this.
I search through that use hostile and will pass in series one as a human right here.
OK.
So we get the lesson in this lesson right here and we'll get it serious.
Which is the same as Lesson two serious dent ones are so false that you are has starts at series for
less than three.
OK so over a haystack that she was mid-thought when we pass in series one into this methodic should
return true because we actually completed a lesson in that series meaning we started learning that series
and should return false because we have not completed and service for less than 3 Savi so we should
be checking for less than three right here.
OK.
Because we haven't completed any series in the series to which is from this series because this is really
going to generate a new series.
Then be some false but then this would be true because we have seen this one right here and we completed
our lesson and see which one.
OK.
So let's run this test.
The unit FUTA should this test great.
So we don't have that mid-thought he started serious.
Now we're just head of what are we learning.
PH be right on the bottom.
We can quit that method.
OK.
So this mathematics in a serious class one that again so feel asserting that no is true but they should
actually return a boolean right.
So what we're going to do is we're going to get the specific key for that use on that series.
Okay.
And then we can check if the number of elements in that army is greater than zero.
If it's greater than zero it means to use naturally completer one lesson in that series.
But then if it's zero it means the use or not complete anything.
Right.
So we have a good number of computer lessons for seeress so we can return this get number of completed
the lessons for a series we'll pass in the series right here.
So we have now a number which is the number of lessons that the user has completed for this particular
series.
Then we can compare to zero.
And if it's greater than zero it means the user has completed at least one of the lessons in this series
which means the user has started the series.
But then if it's not greater than zero zero it means the user has not yet started this series.
And our video store does not have any record of it.
OK.
So let's run our test one more time great.
And we have a successful test.
OK.
So we can now use that series in our views wherever we want to check if the user has started series.
So for example on the land each way for a series we can check has the user started the series or started
the series then rather than just plain starts reset button display a continuous series.
MARTIN OK.
So thank you so much for watching.
Let's continue with some fun thoughts in the next lesson.