OK welcome back.
Let's proceed.
The next method I want to implement it not a learning tool is a get completed lessons method.
OK.
So this mid-thought is going to help us get all the completed lessons for our series.
So that particular way this kid that we used to store we can get that are we of ideas and then we're
going to use our database to get the lessons that much use IDs and then return to us.
OK this might be really helpful in some cases when we want to show the use of the lessons that he's
already completed.
OK so let's go ahead and do this.
I think it's going to be fun.
So use our tests and we're going to create a new test so asked can get computer lessons for a series.
OK so how is this that's going to know.
We have a user up and we have a series and the user completes some lessons in the US and then we call
our get completed lessons thought then we assert that the lessons completed are a return value OK something
like that.
So we're going to run a bunch of assertions and we can actually learn a lot about Lavoe collection.
So let's get to it.
First we need a user and we need a series we need some lessons.
So I'm going to copy this.
OK.
So paste right here we flush Rhenish create a user create a new lesson which is actually going to create
a series.
Then we actually create another lesson in that same series.
OK.
And then I'm going to create a third lesson in the same series.
So we have three lessons in the same series serious one right then I'm going to complete lesson one.
So complete lesson and then use our complete lesson two.
And then we've not completed lesson three.
OK.
So get completer lessons mid-thought.
We're going to see set lessons a course use or get completer lesson and pass in the series so we can
get the series from any of the lessons by saying lesson series reference in the relationship.
Then we need to run a bunch of assertions.
Now remember when you're testing the more assertions you have the better are your tests OK because it
can actually increase your test coverage and you're going to make sure that every single point of your
application works I suspect it to work.
OK.
So first of all we want this to be a collection.
So I assert in stands off.
So this is a helpful method that that can help us check if a return or a resort is a particular instance
of a particular class.
OK.
So we want to check if the return that we have here is an instance of Lovell's collection class.
So I would say it supports Kollection class and we'll pass in complete license.
OK.
So we want to make sure that what ever this method returns to us it must be a collection.
So it must be an instance of this class.
The next thing we want to do is see a server instance off because we don't want a collection of series
or collection of users we want a collection of the lesson class.
So we're going to assert that anything that is inside there should be on stands and anything that is
inside this collection should be an instance of the lesson class.
So we'll get completer lessons and we'll just get a new one item from the collection and assert that
it's an instance of lesson class.
OK.
Then we can now assert true that this collection that we received which is completed license court day
in its lesson.
OK.
And since you also completed lesson 2 we should also assert to that completed lessons contains lesson
2.
OK.
And then we'll also assert false completed lessons contains Lesson 3.
Ok so I know this is a whole bunch of assertions but what we have is actually doing this.
We have three lessons in that series.
We completed two and then we caught our eye get completed lessons.
I thought this method returns to loss of value and we assert that that value must be an instance of
law was collection class therefore a collection and that we are so that everything in that collection
must be on the stands of lesson class and then we make sure that that collection actually contains the
lesson that was completed which one this one and then it also contains this one which was also completed
and we also said that it doesn't contain this one which is not a completed lesson.
OK.
So we're going to come back to this point because I think this is going to actually I think this is
not the best way to test this but I'm going to show you why in a moment.
So just keep an eye for this particular point of our test.
OK.
So let's run this test.
So you next few are pasting up this name.
OK so caught on the find method get complete lessons.
So we'll head over to name and cittie and we're going to create a function which is get completed lessons.
And it's expecting us to send in the series.
OK.
So let's run that sayst.
So filled are such and all is an instance of eliminate support collection.
Right now we want to get the computer lessons for us.
How do we do that.
Remember we have this key that we're using for a particular series on a particular user.
So what we're doing here we are actually getting the complete license in an array by using this particular
statement right here.
So what I'm going to do just right here I'm going to see public function get complete lessons for us
series.
And we're getting the series right here.
And what this is going to return is this segment right here so cut it out and I'll paste that in.
And right here this is going to reference the get completer lessons for our series.
I will pass in the series.
OK.
And this simply gives us the possibility of using this method wherever we want to.
Therefore Lagat that we have done meathook what we can do is get complete organisms you'll be called
to this get completed lessons for seeress I will pass in the series.
So now we have an array of maybe one two three.
OK.
And these three elements are the ideas of the lessons that have been completed for these series.
So what we can do is we need a collection right.
So I would say return collects and we'll collect completer lessons and now that we have a collection
it's simply going to be a collection of items.
This idea is one to four.
OK.
But now we don't want a collection of the ideas.
We want a collection of the lessons to whom these ideas belong to.
Therefore we're going to use our map function to look through each and every one of these elements and
transform them in some way.
That's what I remember from teaching DOS.
So we're passing the clues show which is going to look to each and every one of these elements and for
each of the lessons we have available lesson right here.
So I would say return lesson find lesson.
OK.
All we can fairly call this lesson idea.
So what's happening here.
First we have a collection that we just created but this is a collection of ideas.
But what we want is a collection of lessons.
But we have the ideas of the lessons.
So how do we transform these ideas into lessons.
We use a map method and this method is available on Lavoe collections and this map mid-thought would
help us go through each and every one of the collection items and transform them in any way we want.
So for example in this case we are going to each and every idea element and then we are finding the
lesson that matches that Id elements.
OK so before we run that let's just use and other top use but cost lesson.
OK.
So let's run our tests one more time.
So Field asserting that false is true.
Check out our test and look at what is happening.
We with this assertion meaning we return a collection that was successful and we asserted that any one
dumb lesson elements from that collection should be an instance of lesson class.
So that was successful.
And then when we reach this point where it's checking if the completed lessons contains this lesson
right here it failed.
And also this one also filled with apparently.
So I'm going to show you something right here we're going to date them completed lessons and I'm going
to show you what we have.
OK.
So look at this.
If we had them completed lessons we have an eye on items.
Army of Two.
The first is an intensive lesson obviously and which is I.D. one.
And the second is an instance of lesson.
Also on Friday too.
Right.
So we actually have the correct values but then this contains mid-thought is written into as follows.
OK.
So there's a simple reason for this.
The contains my thought is checking for exact values.
So we might not have exactly the same lesson like we have right here because we got one from our database
and got one from our factory and it might be a little bit different.
So the code things my thought my return follows.
So what we can to do is we're not going to run these Ossetians using collections.
What I want to do is I'm going to see computer lessons.
I this is going to be called a completed license or Plock called the IDs so we can use this method to
get only the IDs of these items in the collection and we can code all mid-thought to transform the collection
into an array.
So now that they have an array of the computer lessons which I'm getting from this computer lessons
that I got from this method then I can change my assertion so I search true and I'm going to call in
are we.
And the way we are using these computer license IDs and I'm going to see check for Lesson one so Lesson
1 easy.
And then I'm going to run exactly the same assertion.
For this lesson.
So we're going to check for lesson two.
So I assert that the idea of Lesson two is in this computer lessons.
IDs are ready and then a suit falls in ari for a lesson to be OK because we didn't complete lesson three
computer lesson one and two.
Therefore this should be returning false toss.
OK.
So let's run that again.
In our ear expects from attitude to be an integer given block.
OK I'm sorry about that so we should be parsing this as the second problem it's our not the other way
around.
So I'm just going to change that to be in a sense.
Ok so I'm done switching the position.
So in a way that takes a Nido and Haystack like that OK run the tests one more time and grade.
We have a successful test finally.
So what's happening.
I'm just going to go through this mid-thought step by step so we understand what was going on.
So we want to test that we can get the completer lessons for our series.
So we create other user lessons and these three lessons belong to series with ID one then we completed
lesson 1 and we completed lesson 2 but we did not complete lesson 3.
So the computer lessons mid-thought we got a collection of all the lessons for that series that we have
completed.
So we called use our get computer lessons and then we passed in the east and we got a collection of
all the lessons completed in that civics so that our sessions we where checking the return value was
actually a collection which it was.
And then we also checked if every member of the collection is a lesson which it was.
And then we got the IDs from the computer lessons collection and we did this because our contentment
thought was not really comparing like we wanted it to.
And this was a simple but easy work around for us which we might come back to later but not now.
Then we checked if the IDs of the computer lessons were actually in the completer lessons.
IDS our way.
OK.
So if you check out our computer lesson my thought what it does is it gets the computer lessons for
a series which returns to us on our way right here.
And then we change that array to our collection we map to each and every one of those elements.
We get the lesson with that idea and we return it as a collection.
OK.
So if you haven't done a stoolie just go through again.
It's not that difficult but thank you so much for watching.
Let's continue our having some fun in the next episode.