Come back we have a landing page we have a series on each.
But what about a single page to view our CBEST independency.
Let's go ahead and take care of this.
In my Front-End and control actually actually studied the for.
We're going to really start a new world where we can view a single series alone.
OK.
So watch.
It's going to be a gets and it's going to be serious and we're taking the series.
I remember I'm using series right here because I want to make use of Slavoj route model by then and
I'm going to see get to the front and control law and will get the series method.
OK.
So in our front end control would create a serious thought and to receive the series we're just going
to typings series and love automatically inject that into this method for us then we can just focus
on returning a view.
And in this case we tend to view quite serious and go past in the series that we just got is
awesome.
So now that we have that mid-thought in our resources views that actually we need a series that they
appear to be right and they just created want to save us a lot of time.
So I don't want us to go through the process of creating some ex-chairman and stuff like that.
OK.
So here it's simply a header and then some content very minimal and we're going to go for it.
So for the header I want to change the background styling that we have here to the Sui's image.
So rather than having these I'm going to call out series image path and I'm actually using the attribute
set.
So right down here I think we have an image path for me.
There we go.
OK.
So serious image is going to give us the background image.
The next thing we want is the title.
So with a quote Series title and we also do that here then now we have a start learning button.
So what we can do is check if
you zone.
So if the user has authenticated then we're going to check if the user has started that series so we
can see if the user has started serious on passing Sui's then we see House and with half and Eve.
OK.
So we checked if they use us authenticated and if it's authenticated then we can have the check for
if he has started the series.
So if he has started the series then we're going to have a continual engine box.
And rather than start nothing.
OK.
So continue on your learning and we can actually make this link two different pages.
We cannot talk about that later.
Then we're going to have start learning if he has not completed or he has not started the service.
OK then if the user is not authentic he said then we're simply going to see.
Show us start learning bottom.
OK so the use authenticated.
We're going to check if he has suffered the series and if they use it as another indicator we're simply
going it's me a start learning button.
Ok then finally we have the cause description which we can quote here.
And for the video lessons we are simply going to have an on that list which switching committee carefully
Tom.
OK.
So let's just squarehead and see what we get.
Now in our home page we want to link to that route so I'll head over to my Welkom that blade and right
down where we have I will read more.
I'm going to link this to all routes and this is going to be series I will pass in the series SLOC.
OK.
So in my web ph be I mean just give this a name of serious.
OK so looks like we get to go refresh rigmarole.
Undefined variable cost description that should be in our series that blate So in our description series.
I'm so sorry about that.
OK.
So refresh.
Great.
So we have the background image the title of the series and then Sing's This user has actually started
learning how behalf continual learning.
Barton now we have the series description OK great so we have a single page for a single service.