Let's do a little bit of clean up interviews and what I'm talking about is revisit our sou'west the
blade that we we have eve our fuse or if our user has started a series on of these kind of statements.
OK.
Now what I want to do is I don't want to have such but then I want to use the custom blade directives
that apply to us.
So label this as a possibility of quitting.
What we constantly debate shifts and we use them however we want.
So first of all I'm going to clean this up and I'm going to use ief Earth.
And this is a big if that law applies to us.
So and us and if we go ahead or Voser we still have the same thing.
So this looks a little bit cleaner.
Then how about cleaning this up.
If the user has started a series now they're going to create a custom bleet if Sigmon or blade directive
and we're going to use it in our views.
So our head of much of my apps service provider and this is where we can actually register some of your
stuff.
So after our level has finished registering all the service providers it's going to call this boot method
so we can actually create our own custom bleet if Stedman Rakia.
So how do we create this.
We have the blade Fassett we have an IV method.
So I'm gonna use the blade Fosi right here.
So on this if mid-thought it's 6 in the name of the directory if we want to use.
So I'm going to call it has started this and the Prometa it takes in like here is a function occlusal.
So that's the second Parminter and the pomander that is passed into disclosure or is the parameter that
we can pass into this blate the next year.
OK.
So for example if we have it has started seaways then we can pass in upon it right here.
For example the series itself the instance of the series.
So if we pass in that parameter for our views it's automatically getting passed into disclosure so we
can receive the series right here and right here we just need to return a boolean so we can return our
use on and then we can call the house started series marathon.
And sure enough into this mid-thought we need to pass in the series.
So that's all we need to create our own custom bleet directive.
Now let's go ahead and learn how to use this.
So rather than seeing if all news has started this we are simply going to see how US US.
I will pass in the U.S. and then else.
And then we're going to see and start as soon as.
That's it.
Okay.
So we don't at least no more Hostetter series display continue learning else just start learning and
has started sou'west looks very clean.
Okay.
So let's refresh and we get the exact same thing which means obliterates is working perfectly.