Get sick of this continue learning Motson first starts us we are going to have a page where you can
watch the lessons the page is going to take in the series.
SLOC lesson number.
And then when we read the use of that page the Coreg the Jews know that.
OK.
So I don't watch my web that BHB and I'm going to define a new routes.
This watch is going to be a get on it with good to watch series.
And we're taking the series SLOC.
OK.
And he's going to use or control or watch series controller.
And I'll just make it to the index Martha.
OK.
Let me create a controller.
He had assigned me control or watch series controller.
OK.
So our watch series controller should have an index method and the six in the series so type in series
right here for Lavell to automatically reject that instance.
So huge but costs squeeze.
And then once we have this my thought and the series and that's what we want to do is post starts us
redirect the user to the first lesson of the series.
OK but we're going to actually be setting up a way so that we can read the way they use us to the latest
computer lesson.
OK.
So like if you completed lesson two we don't seem to listen to the computer lesson five the last time
we do it in two lesson eight to Lesson 6.
Sorry.
So we're going to be setting up the system.
But for now let's just we like to use after the first lesson.
So return redirects and wait until we create our routes and we're going to call these routes series
that watch and this route is going to take keen to bomb us to see I will passing serious so.
OK.
Because Rob Mondo Bandi we need to pass this along.
And it's going to take a lesson.
Remember our old model mining permit so I will pass in serious lessons.
Chris I will get the idea.
OK.
So let me break this down for you.
It's just an array of departments that are going to be passed to this routes that we're going to create.
OK.
So these vultures expecting a serious lesson.
So the series we have easily but the lesson we have to make a query and what we do is we simply get
the first lesson from the relationship right.
OK.
So this relationship gives us the first lesson and then we can get the ID we pass each of our comments
on.
OK.
So we turn to redirect to this Ralph Byrd.
In future we're going to have to actually find the final find the latest lesson lessen the use a wash
and then return to the beach OK.
But for us this is good enough OK.
So what we need to do is create that vault that we just specified.
So we create a route and this will be Seabreeze permits us series then lesson on permits our lesson.
OK.
And this is also when you watch series control I'm sure lesson.
OK then we'll have to give it the name we specified so name is going to be serious that watch.
OK.
So like be precise repassing in the suit is the lesson and the name of the route and you see we and
watch like right here.
So serious lesson.
OK.
So let's go ahead and customize that button so it leads to this vault.
So would head of ops who are serious that laid the BHB and Querrey half hour consignor learning Motson
we're going to have to increase to include an aircraft.
OK.
So why don't we give the other vowels a name also.
So this Vought.
So let's just calling serious are and then OK then in this vault we could pass in all routes to Ceres
that learning will pass in the series slaughter house departments such that route.
OK.
So when the user clicks on to continue learning Motson it's going to invoke the index of my thumb and
index mid-thought is simply going to redirect the user to the first lesson of that series.
OK.
So let's go ahead and click on that button and see what we can refresh click on the Barzun OK it's a
strange property of known objects and online searching.
This line right here.
So maybe this lessons.
Let's check if we have adolescent's relationship.
So right.
So yes we do.
So the next thing should be this first mid-thought the first A thought is written in or and they we
are trying to get the IGY Parliament's off which means we are trying to get a property from a known
object.
So looks like we need to go over.
I mean and actually save a new lesson to this series.
Parcak like I thought this has no lessons so let's create a new lesson.
And this would be introduction to view just 2.0 or 2.5 and then we just pass in a fake video ID and
the episode number is going to be 100.
Dozens of asked in five V.M. ID this and then we're going to see that's true Jussieu.
So this awesome framework.
OK.
Then create a lesson and you have lesson created successfully.
There you go.
We have our first lesson Ladd's receipt.
Our home viscid dot series and click on the consonant learning Motson.
And now we have redirect that to series VGX lesson 1 and then we don't have the short lesson method.
So that's created now what series we're going to create a public function.
Sure lesson my thought and we need to receive the C race and we also need to receive the lesson now
or less.
And we just need to avoid that so we don't have any worse than what we do right here.
We turn of view so return view we should be watch and will pass in to permits us a civics lesson.
OK so we may not need to pass in the series lesson because the lesson we can get the series but we're
going to come back and be shocked in a little while.
OK.
So just to save us a lot of time I actually created a watch that made the Peachtree already in my home
my view woodstove tree.
And then right here we just have the stand that simply.
So here we need to equal the lessons itl.
So I'm just going to say lesson time to home.
And then here we have serious title SCMS and the speech arts of his title and right on the button.
This is where we're going to be putting our play and all that good stuff.
OK.
So let's refresh this link once again and grade.
We have these page introduction to you just 2.5 VGX beginner costs.