You guys will come back.
This is where we end up on this page and this is a page where the whole project is about we want to
be able to watch her series and learn something.
OK.
So we're going to be using Vimeo.
Now the reason why the reason Vimeo is it's really really hard to host your own videos because there
is a lot to take into consideration.
Streaming processing and taking care of hosting space port processing the video when the video is uploaded
and all of that stuff.
So it's better to use a video provider like video or YouTube.
OK.
So Vimeo provides the possibility of hosting your videos and once you host your videos you can make
the videos Private and specific to particular domains.
For example when we deploy these projects all the videos that are going to be on this website are only
going to be able to be embedded on this Web site.
OK.
So that's what V.M. provide to us and you need to be at least I think the premium plan or the preplan
don't know you have to check it out okay.
So the API is open if you are embedded with Windows it's open free.
OK.
So we're going to be using the video player and remember once a video is completed we need to mark that
the user has completed this video right.
So install the player and install that.
If you check out my history right here I have NPM installed see if Vimeo play up and it's installed.
Then once you install it let's go ahead and do some VHS magic to have that play out right here.
OK.
So let's create a video player or component.
So in my component's directory I'm going to create a play or that view and this is going to contain
my player.
So templates I'm gonna have a script.
And for now I'll just put in a D for a cure.
OK.
So let's register the component in my Abdur.
Jess right here I'm going to see view the component and this is going to be a view player and will require
components play clear that view.
OK so now we want our player to work that's the code of documentation for a bit.
And what do we see here.
You can install the product in many different ways.
But what we want is right here.
OK.
There are a lot of ways you can actually use an embed.
And they will pass in the ID.
Remember we have the ID stored in the database right.
For this particular video we have the ID stored in the database so we can pass it in into the component
and maybe concatenated to the I-frame and play it.
But the simplest way is right here automatically with SDMI attributes.
We can have a Z if.
And then we have a video id property or attribute.
And then we pass in the video ID into that play up and then specify the width and then we can give that
an ID.
And then in our code we simply create a new video player.
I'll show you how this works.
Let me copy that line and in our template I'll paste that in and what it simply does is remember VMO
ID that this is the pujo Id like we start in our database and then we have the ID which we can just
leave us one stake then in our code we need to import V.M..
So import player from Vimeo player.
Ok then we can reference our mounted hawk.
So as soon as this component is mounted in our code what is going to happen is we can we can see constant
player is a new player and we have options right here.
We can pass in the parameter which is going to be id of the element we want to mount our player on.
So were going to pass in hand steek right here and automatically we going to have a new player right
here.
OK.
So I'm going to go to my watch that played a b a b and right here we have column 12.
I'm going to mnze view player.
So this is just like I have in my Abda just right.
So you play.
And then I use that to match few players.
So I have my watch out with the one in behind the scenes.
It's watching everything.
And then I'm going to head over to my browser or inspect and then a hard refresh.
And there we go.
We actually have that video image that automatically because we have a player right.
So.
So the player is going to provide us with lots of options.
For example check out the documentation if you need any help.
But we can listen to the play events and then do something so we can also live in to listen to the end
events and also do something right.
So what we are going to do is let's just test out the events.
So we are just going to see a player that on play just like we have here and then we're going to pass
in a close call for what is supposed to happen once the play event is triggered.
We're just going to console glauca our video explain.
So let's refresh.
And then when we click on that automatically the video is playing.
And we have this locked right here.
OK.
So let's go ahead and continue working on our player in the very next video.