You guys let's actually get the ID from our of these.
So I'm going to have to watch you play and I'm going to get the idea of a you video for example.
This one right here.
OK.
So copy that ID and then I'm going to head back to our series.
This and this series as it does the job.
And I'm going to pasting that idea to see if and automatically we have some of the successfully awesome.
So now when I visit my home and I visit this series I can continue on.
And in and he takes me to the speech imbeds this video.
But now I want to pass in the Real I.D. from the server from the dates of these.
OK.
So what are we going to do.
We cannot accept props on the first and maybe only quote We are going to receive the lesson.
And then you may want to leave the pitch.
We just need to pass lesson because the lesson that we received.
So I mean these supplements you're going to cost the student Jason Parsons to the video player.
OK.
So let's just refresh these and check out if we have that data that's good or viewed to our view player.
And there we go.
We actually have the juice and structure of that particular lesson.
OK.
So what do you want to do is in our play let's just call the default and then I will need to change
these two defaults.
Lesson.
OK.
So now that we have default lesson in our props we are going to have a D.
So we're just going to return an object and we're going to have the lesson property right here.
And this is simply going to be Jason and postes.
This is the default lesson.
OK so keep refresh just to check that out check of the area.
And there we go.
We have props and then we have this lesson object right.
OK.
So we have the video I.D. right now in our template we can just see the lesson then we're going to buying
these dates of the new I.D. to lessen the Jew I.D..
OK.
So let's check this song fresh.
Check out our play now.
We have that object but looks like we don't have the play.
Let's check other council and it looks like we didn't load the video right.
So we go back to the video again.
Yeah.
The video has some right permissions so this is what I was talking about.
So the obvious Jihad set has said domain restrictions.
So let's just fetch for a free video that we cannot truly embed.
And if we check out this one yeah we can actually embed this with you.
Right.
So let's copy that ID one more time.
Head over to all series this the page for this.
But is serious at that pace that we join the safe lesson then the virtual home
visit this serious continual learning and there we go.
We have this exact video.
OK.
So this video right here that we embed that automatically we have the video of the ball on our war.
So we are actually actually displaying the video from the database.
That's great progress.
In the very next lesson.