Work on bad guys I want to see us drive to things real quick.
And the first thing is how to get the art that lessons.
OK.
Because he was joking or serious.
That we we don't have any thoughts to get the other lessons right here we just agin the lessons by the
ideas but we need a lot more thought that this other than by the episode numbers just like we precise
when we were creating them.
OK.
So let's go ahead to assist us.
Are we going to create a new test and get all that lessons for our series.
So how is this going to look.
First of all let's create a series and then create some lessons for that series about three of them
and then we are going to call the get or that lesson my thought.
And then we are going to run some assertions to make sure that the lessons are in the correct order.
OK.
So let's get to it.
First of all we need to create the series right.
So what I would do is just like what we've been doing or just create a lesson and then automatically
it's going to generate a new series so factory creates and I'll specify for the lesson class and not
forget your import less on the top so that we have no errors but class lesson and work here let's just
import civies so used by Sui's and I'm going to just pull out this right here.
OK.
So we have our first lesson what they want to do is take control of the episode number.
So I want to specify this opposite number in exactly the way I wanted to show up to my viewers.
So I want this to be the second lesson in my playlist so I'm going to use 200 and I'm going to create
another lesson.
So lesson two.
It cost exactly the same thing right here.
And rather than passing in 200 I'm going to pass in 100 which means this is going to be the first lesson
in my playlist because remember we are trying to test how it's going to be in real life in real life
we can create a lesson and then assigned a video idea and everything and then discover that that lesson
is supposed to come later.
So you added the episode number and you put it before the other one.
Right.
So if you do this everything might blow up.
OK so we have to test so much at this at the time.
So we're creating a second lesson but it's going to play before the first one because we are going to
be using the EPS number to know which one comes first and which one comes last.
OK.
So right here we need to specify our series ID to make sure that it's also for service one.
And finally we're going to have a search and I'm going to specify that this is place number three and
this is going to be lesson.
And that's what we need for our series on our lessons.
Okay.
So call to get that lessons.
My thought we're going to see lessons.
It's going to be courtroom lesson series because remember this should be on the series class then would
call get all that lessons.
OK.
Now for our sessions.
First of all let's just make sure that any random element from this result that we have which is a collection
should be an instance of the lesson class.
So we're going to see days assert Einstein's awful lesson class and we'll get the lessons and we'll
get around them.
OK then let's US-CERT equals and let's think about this if we have the lessons.
If we if other the lessons then the first lesson in this collection should actually be listened to.
Right.
Because if either A by episode number but this should come first and then the last lesson in this collection
should actually be lesson.
Right.
And listen listen one right here should be in the middle.
OK.
So let's assert that lessons first and we can just check across the ID is equal to lesson to ID.
And let's also US-CERT equals that lessons lasts we can get the last use in the last mid-thought and
then I said that it's lesson to be ID.
OK.
So those are the questions we're going to be running.
Now let's run this test individually to see what we get.
PH BE YOU filter by this test.
OK so on only get that lesson.
My thought yes we would have to watch or see which that BHP and right down here we going to create a
get that license method.
OK.
Run that test again.
And now each of us culture a member function or.
Because we're trying to get one done for our collection but we need not.
So what do we do to get the other lessons we just need to Aadhar all the lessons by the opposite number
field in ascending order.
Right.
So we just see if we turn this license or that by oh let's see something where here.
If I caught a guy like this he's going to give me an error.
Why.
Because this lessens colony as a property is going to return to us a collection of all the lessons.
But calling it as a method is going to return to us an instead of the query builder such that we can
call Marco Rubio the Methos like all the by and would order by the number few.
And then we're going to make sure that we specify that it isn't are sending other such that the smallest
is at the bottom is at the top and then it'll keep it keeps going down and then OK and then we're going
to use that gets mid-thought so that it returns to us a collection.
OK.
So we turn this lesson's order by a piece of Namok in ascending order and then get the collection working.
So let's run this again.
And that's great I test passes.
So we are successfully getting all the other lessons for the CBS.