Two very important Methos we're going to need a cigarette next lesson and get previous lesson.
So we should have this Methos on one lesson class and issue be really useful when we want to may be
automatically redirect the user to the next lesson he wants to watch.
All we want to display the next and previous buttons on the use on the washing page.
Ok maybe another play or something like that.
OK.
So let's go ahead and take off.
This would actually use a test to test drive this.
So I'm going to create a new test BHP areason make test and this would be the lesson I asked and specify
that it's unit.
OK.
So headbutts are lessons asked and who are first asked this would be a public function.
So I asked can get next and previous lessons from a lesson.
OK.
So how do we organize this.
Given that we have a series of lessons called Get next lesson and get previous lesson my thoughts and
then withdrawn some assertions.
So when we are creating these serious lessons we are going to organize them in a particular we call
these my thoughts on one day sessions.
OK.
So let's dive into this.
First I'm just going to use but cost series and that costs less than then here although although is
Azzi lesson or I'll just head over to my sisters attorney and then I'm just going to copy this.
OK.
Because this is exactly what we need.
Then back to my lessons.
Asked I'll just paste this in so I'm resizing the lesson has a piece about 200 lessons to a piece of
100 unpleasantry has the opposite number of 200.
Therefore actually less one less than two is the first to play.
Then there's this one place and then this one please.
That's how it's supposed to be.
OK.
So what we'll do is we'll call next lesson math art.
So next lesson because the lesson get next lesson.
OK.
So so we're calling get next lesson on this one.
And this is episode 200.
Therefore the next lesson should be episode 200.
Right here.
OK.
So let's on an assertion this cert equals next lesson ID.
And this is less than three ID.
Right.
Then we can say this a cert equals get previous lesson and we'll get the ID.
So looks like we don't even need this table right here.
I'll just pull it out.
OK.
So I was getting next lesson ID from us and.
And if we are calling less than three which is this one and we are getting the previous lesson that
it should be this right.
Right.
So he assert that the ID cause lesson ID.
OK.
So let's also call the lesson to show our set equals lesson to get the next lesson.
All righty.
So this is lesson in school.
Therefore if we get the next lesson it should be this one.
Right.
So if you get the next lesson and I said that because that's an idea.
And then we should also get assert equals lessons soon.
So what if so what if we get the previous lesson even though we know this one is actually the first
lesson.
Right.
It means we are expecting that lesson 2 which is the first.
If we get previous lesson we should expect more.
They're going to change this to suddenly all that get previous lesson.
We don't know.
And it's very important that you actually return.
No I'm not.
OK.
Because if your implementation breaks your code then it's really dangerous.
So if it we don't know what we can do in our view is check if this is not know then displayed a previous
lesson or if it's not know then play the next quarter or something like that.
OK.
So if your implementation actually breaks if it's it doesn't find a previous lesson or next lesson then
it's not a really cool implementation because you need to start handling errors and all that.
OK.
So let's also ask that when we get the last lesson we just listen to me and we try to get next lesson.
It also gives us all.
OK.
So I think we've won a bunch of assertions right here.
And I think it's really going to guide us in making this methodic pass our case.
So that's one hit PH BE field by this test grade course on the find method get the next lesson.
So we head over to our lesson of BHB and create that methodic redneck's lessons it again trying to get
property of object.
Why.
Because this fosters It's getting good next lesson which returns at the moment.
And we're trying to get the ID.
OK.
So let's just work on this method to make sure that it passes.
First we know the services that this lesson belongs to.
OK.
So what we can do is see this series and we'll get all the lessons for this series such that we know
that we have reduced all our database records to the lessons that concern this particular series.
And then we would search.
This is where the episode number is greater than this episode.
And once we get on the lessons where the episode number is greater than this episode number we are going
to order the results.
So order by episodes in ascending order.
And finally we get the first results.
OK.
So get the series so that you get all the lessons that are only in this series and then you search where
the opposite number is greater than this one.
And if it's greater than you or that in ascending order such that the next will be at the very top and
then you get the first.
OK so let's run this.
And we still get this train to get property of no object error.
Ok let's try to do both together.
We have this Sui's lessons and this is supposed to return to us a collection of all the lessons that
belong to the series that this lesson belongs to which is to me in this case.
Yeah.
And then we get where EPS number is greater than this opposite number.
And in this case it should return only this one because that's the only one that passes that condition
right.
And then we should order in ascending order just in case we have more than one.
And then he should return to us the first result.
OK.
It's supposed to succeed but for some reason it's not.
So I'll show you how I did back in these cases.
So right here I know it's written in knol.
Then what I'm going to do is for every single step of this I'm going to try to do Bach at a certain
point.
OK.
So for example this series of lessons I'm going to just died on the results of that operation to make
sure that it gives me what I expect.
OK.
So rather than calling these I'm just going to call the property.
So I get on and if I run that gives me an array of one element rather than three that we created.
And if we check how out the series ID it's giving us a series of 11 and I think I know why this is because
every time we run a test it's going to create a new series create new lessons because we are not refreshing
our database.
Ok found it.
So we need to refresh our database so that we have fresh data every time we run our test.
OK.
So this died don't break your run that fast one more time.
And we have caught on to find mid-thought get previous lesson great which means our next lesson was
suspected.
OK.
So let's quit this.
Get previous lesson mid-thought which is going to be a public function.
Get to this lesson and what do we do.
Let's return this series of lessons.
And remember we are skipping to only the lessons for this series because we can do something like solve
where but this is going to give us all lessons records in the database and then we can be comparing
the episode numbers because they're going to get mixed up.
Remember the episode numbers can be duplicated and they also belong to different service so we get only
for this service and we use the brackets right here because we need a KBO that in a sense.
And I'm not so sure if we need it because remember on collection's we have when methodes we have way
in my thoughts and in this case if we use this we actually have an instance of illuminate database eloquent
collection.
Well I'm going to leave that to you to find out.
But I'm just going to stick to the basics and then I'm going to call my where I thought the episode
number is less than this episode number and this is going to give us a list of all the lessons opposite
numbers are less than the one that we are check in.
And then and then we can order by episode number because nobody to for the other by the IDs so what
get out of my episodes and will put that in our star and we'll get the last.
OK.
So I'm not sure about that but let's walk through it together.
If we haven't gone for three five six and I walk in with idea of five.
Therefore when we run this query is going to give us we're going to be in the order in ascending order
we're going to have one and three.
And the previous is supposed to be three.
So I think getting the last is the reasonable choice.
OK.
So let's run this test is going to tell us if we are right or not.
It's called the find method on the query before the last.
OK.
So we're working with the Kraybill the here and not our collection.
Therefore we can call the last but what we can do is all the days in descending order and still call
our first method.
OK.
So let's run that says one more time.
And great.
We're going so we are successfully getting the next and previous lessons.
Now how are we going to use this.
And I watched that lead the Ph.D. We can now comfortably have next to button on the previous button
on the play so that the user can watch the next lesson or can also go back to the previous lesson.
We'll talk about that more in the next lesson.