In the last couple of lessons who creates a next and previous lessons math thought and then we also
quit a get or lessons method so we can get next boobish can also get all the lessons so let's go ahead
and use them on this page or head over to my watch that played the PH B and B can now have some buttons.
Awesome 8 arcs.
So I'll just give aid and box on the bottom in full and this is going to link to a page where we can
watch the next lesson.
So I'm going to see next lesson right here.
OK.
And we are also going to have a button that button in full and this is also going to link to where we
can watch the previous lesson.
So remember we can actually get the next lesson and previous lesson and also put the titles like here.
OK.
But we're not going to worry much about that.
Now let's have a watch on whether be.
And we have this watch Sui's show less and more thought and the name a series that watch which is expected
in the series and accepts in the lesson.
Therefore we can use that right here so we can see how it's a serious watch and would pass in the series
which should be lesson series snark.
Oh I think we actually passed a series from the controller must check the watch was controller.
And we actually passing passing the series and this is really going to help us.
So we don't have to make this query right here so we'll just have serious should be serious SLOC.
And the lesson should be lesson get the next lesson and get the idea.
Right now we only want to display these Matsen if we actually have a next lesson.
Right.
So I would say if lesson get next lesson.
And if they're all based in the method.
OK.
So if we have a good next lesson then place make sure you displayed the link so that user can view the
next lesson.
So we have like let's get next lesson that we pass the ID and the squinch automatically take us to the
same page but we can watch the next lesson.
So we're going to do exactly the same thing for the previous lesson.
So just copy this and paste it right here and read it and get next lesson we'll use GET previous lesson.
And this would point to get previous lesson would see previous lesson and I think it's all set to try
this out.
So at the moment let's visit that page refresh and there's aspects that we don't have in the next and
few years because we don't have any other lessons for the series.
So it's on my service visit this one and I'm going to add a new lesson the lessons Aitu is going to
be what this course called Vohs the lesson VDU idea.
I'm going to get from V.M. any one on video.
The EPS number would be 200.
Because I want this to be done next and the description of course description something like that.
OK.
Then on Vimeo that's just fine.
We do.
And looks like an embed.
It's all just copied I.D. basic right there.
And great.
We have a new lesson.
So I just quick lesson so that we can actually see this in action.
And I'm just going to get another video and then I'm going to paste it in right there on the screen
TV be view out or introduction or whatever.
And this is going to be a piece at 300.
And he's going to be using Virata are in your applications.
OK.
So create lesson and we have that creature for us.
Now let's reset our visit our course consignor learning and we have our next lesson button right because
this is the first lesson if you click on this it takes us to lessons you and we have our next and previous
lesson buttons.
OK.
Because this is the second lesson.
But if you go to the next lesson we have only the previous lesson button because we are on Lesson three
and we can go to the previous and using this button and we can go to the previous and it works as expected.
OK.
And notice that once we actually visit those lessons we have the correct video monitored.
So if I this next lesson we have automatically the video that we just embedded.
OK.
So looks like everything is working great.
See the very next episode.