We also had our get out lessons.
So we're going to use that method now to display all the lessons and display them in the correct order.
OK.
So I'm just going to create a column two of them.
And this really bootstrapped for stylings and I'll create an on that list with list book class and I'm
going to use my four each right here.
So for each and for each remember we passed in the series into this view.
So for each series get all the adolescents this current lesson.
OK.
So we're just going to use a different variable names such that we don't have any conflicts that will
create a list item with the ID of list group item and for each of this would simply first of all call
it the name.
OK.
So what's the current lesson title.
So that sounds strange.
I'm just going to use how to present.
So arrow title.
Great.
So let's go ahead and check this out.
I refresh.
We have the introduction to VGX.
What is Kostikov us view into view out the introduction.
Now if I were to head over to all my civis and added This is my maybe since I WANT MY seen.
I want to talk about this first.
So maybe I did this to 200.
So that this place first and then added this to 300 so that this place next and I read trash automatically
You see we have that order right here.
OK.
One more thing I want to talk about is we can also check which one is plain and display and I can here
as you see this is the current And we can also have links right here so we can actually change all of
these two links.
And the title is actually going to be able to visit that particular course lesson.
OK.
So we can Ecorse the page or the route to watch this particular lesson which is going to be this route.
So while it's serious that watch remember repassing passing in the series which is serious
SLOC repassing in lesson which is now ID.
OK.
So when the user clicks on that you should actually visit that page to watch that lesson.
Refresh and have those links.
So if I click on this it takes me to and three click on this it takes me to lesson too.
And this one also takes me to Lesson one.
So everything seems to be working.
Thank you so much.
See you in the very next episode.