OK guys let's do some javascript.
We have our API we have our suites our love which we saw just to have some useful notifications.
And we have our player now when they use a finishes just watch a video we want to alert something to
they use or like a notification message and then maybe we'd like to use to the next lesson or something
like that.
So let's go ahead and take off that in this.
If you haven't installed tweak alert just go ahead and put that in the sausage.
And then for our video player we need to listen when the video completes or when the video is and then
and we check all the events we have on that event right there.
Therefore we had to clear that view and said look we are going to see play that on and then call a method
which is going to be does not display video and then I launch.
OK.
So therefore we need to create that mid-thought.
So I'm going to create my methods object right here and I need a display region in that search.
Now how would this be.
We need to display an alert therefore let's fill in the street.
And that might be that we just installed.
So in Port street alert from each I lurch.
Ok then here we can see sweet alerts and we're going to see Yea you completed this video or this lesson
or whatever.
Ok then we can listen to what happens as soon as the user clicks on the confirm button and once that
happens we're going to see window that location across the whole page for now.
OK.
So what is happening is when we have this confirmation you need to check out on that documentation is
really easy.
OK.
For example using pharmacy's we can keep track of how the U.S. are actually done.
So click on each other button.
Although if you click on these Cobar you scored right here.
So that's what we are doing when the user clicks on the confirm.
We're simply going to redirect that user to the next lesson.
Now we don't have the next lesson.
So let's get to it.
And the easiest way is to get it from our program.
So next lesson you're out.
OK.
Then in our What's that let that be.
Let's pass this pop in.
So here we need next mess your all and it's going to be Buju.
We already have the Roxmouth thought that you are soliciting.
So I'll just copy it.
So for the next lesson and then I'm going to paste it right here.
OK.
So don't worry.
I know we have a lot of queries going on right here but regular facts are to move all of those.
But for now let's just make this work.
OK.
So to make sure everything is working.
So to make sure everything works as aspects that Windows that location is supposed to be equal to this
dot next lesson.
Oh OK.
So automatically when we click on that button it's going to rediagnosed the next lesson.
OK so let's go ahead and see if everything works as expected.
Let's inspect the refresh right now.
And then let's see you play to see if we have the next lesson on how we do.
So I'm going to play this video and then I'm going to ask for it a little to the end.
So instead we see that notification and ones that we just completed our play are automatically files
that events and we just play honestly.
Let's now click on this button and everything works perfectly.
This speech should be refresh to the next lesson grades.
It's refreshed but we have a problem right because in our pop the way a right here we are trying to
say and get the next lesson.
But this is actually the last lesson of the series.
OK.
And remember we didn't have that error earlier because we rabbits.
In an if statement.
So if lessons get this lesson on if lesson get next lesson.
So but at least we're redirecting to the next lesson successfully.
Now what we need to do is only call this last thought if we have a next lesson.
OK.
So we're going to be solving a lot in the very next video.
Clean up a lot of these and avoiding such errors.
OK.
Thanks so much for watching.
See you in the very next video.