A really cool Lavoe package that is going to help us debug applications or cool make applications better
a Lavazza What about go ahead and install it.
And if you use 5.5 like I am all you need to do is you want to compose or require Lavoe debug by as
modified by here and that's if you're ready to use it.
So I've installed that.
And if you can see in all my views I have this bar right here.
Now check out this page where we are actually viewing the lesson and we have our player up check out
for example what we have here.
We have analysis for everything the view routes queries and if you check right here it gives us information
about the queries you see we have to have statements executed on my skill database and several of them
were to be catered.
And that's really really powerful performance right because we can't make a query and then make it several
times OK.
It really slows down our server as a complication.
So now why we have that is.
Look at this quavery right here to get the next and previous with creating that query once twice twice
up to seven times.
Therefore to that application we're going to be using DEBUG by Chris.
We have the facts or check if everything has changed.
So we actually have no duplications.
OK.
So let's go ahead and take care of that.
Now the idea I have our head of it's my watch that let that be is we can either pass that get previous
lesson and get that lesson from our control.
But I don't want our controllers to be bloated.
So what we can do is actually get it right here so we can open up here and BHB and we can assign next
lesson.
They want to be go to a lesson get next lesson right here.
OK.
And this is totally OK.
We can also get previous lesson because the lesson get previous lesson right here.
OK.
So just assigning those variables and right here we can see the next lesson.
So rather than calling the math out again and making the query we see if next lesson and right here
we can see if previous lesson.
Okay.
And then this right here where we have that everyone forgets and the next lesson you all remember if
we don't have a next lesson it's going to actually break.
So what are we going to do is we're also going to rub it in an IF statement.
So if there is the next lesson then we're going to pass that prop to VGX.
So right here I'm going to see if next a lesson and if and if right here then we're going to pass this
problem.
OK then where we have our methods rather than calling next lesson we can just see next lesson ideas.
So we're using exactly the same vailable.
Therefore no queries.
OK so right you also get the next lesson will change this too.
Next lesson I will get the idea get this lesson what changed at your previous lesson.
I will get the idea.
OK so I think we touched everything.
Let's just refresh now to see if our number of course has reduced refresh and we have unsurvivable.
The lesson.
All right here.
I'm sorry that's because I'm in the Capitol.
It's supposed to be a small.
I'm sorry about that.
Refresh our case so let's look at what we have line statements executed only to where duplicator and
7 way unique.
OK.
But I think what we actually did fix the Evreux about Vista in the next speech.
Let's try this next lesson.
And this is actually the last lesson and we don't have that error because the problem is pastur veejays
now is not.
So if we checkout view and check out our play our next lesson is undefined.
OK.
Now let's head over to us to Hopley and Reaganites how sweet a lot what to do.
So here is not just play video in that other thread we're going to see if there's not next lesson your
all then what we going to do is display this.
Right.
And then if we don't have that then we simply cannot just play this right here.
You complete that this series because that's the last lesson.
Right.
So he's completed this series and then nothing happens.
But then if we have a next lesson then he's going to redirect to the next lesson.
OK so let's try this out.
Hard refresh.
Let's start with the previous lesson and I'm just going to ask for my plea to the end.
And yeah we have the alerts.
If I click on OK it redirect that me to the next lesson automatically if I played this one and just
phosphide to the end are so great we have the ACA you completed this series.
OK.
That's great.
Yeah.
So you might want to maybe redirect the use outside the home page after he completes the series.
Or you might want to do nothing at all like we're doing right now.
It's all OK and it depends on you but we are not tracking the success of the use of we are not yet knowing
if he has complete other series or something like that.
So what we need to do right now is play that and then when the vision has and that we need to fire an
Ajax request to the server.
Complete the lesson for the user.
And then when we receive a confirmation from our server then we want to display video and that alerts.
OK.
Try to figure that out.
Are we're going to do it together in the next lesson.