Before you round up with what Shuey speech I want to stick two things.
First of all remember that we need to fire the air jocks requests wants to use a completely what piece
of video.
And next we want to display a watching.
I can work here to make sure that we know that this is the lesson we are watching.
And finally I want us to hootz a teacher right here or check to show that this user has watched the
series or not and forced to do that when the user completely watches the series we need to find just
a request to us.
Are you opposed to quest to complete the series.
No we don't yet have a test for the feature but we already have a test for the units.
OK.
Because in our unit test we are testing the user can complete a series which is successful.
Bert we need to create a feature to us so that we test how the Ajax requests are fire or something.
OK so let's quit Anyuta us.
PH We areason make tests and this is going to be what shoosh to us.
We are great.
This is a feature Cockey so we head over to what suits us and the first issue with when you are writing
these tests.
A user complete series just use or can complete a series.
OK so how do we want this to work.
We need a user right and then we need a suits and that's the you have like maybe 2 lessons I suppose.
And then we're going to fire a post request for a server to complete the lesson.
OK maybe the first lesson.
OK then we reach Rumson assertions may asserted that the lesson has been complete.
Read this and then maybe assert that we have a possible response from our server and then maybe assert
the status of the response.
OK so let's start with our use or use our equals.
Create a user with our treat.
So use aquanauts code.
Create my thoughts of post-Easter.
Next we need a series on two lessons.
So create a lesson persist that will create another lesson which will be listened to for the lesson
Clauss.
I will make sure that be precise that the series ideally should be one.
OK so it belongs to the first series.
Ok now we need to make the post request a push request is going to be this post and we have to decide
the end points.
So can I say let's go through a series complete lesson and point.
I want you to keep the identifier for the lesson which will be less than ideal.
So in this case you are completing this lesson so passing its ID in this string.
OK and then we are not going to be passing any data to the server.
We just want to complete this lesson and that's all we need.
OK and we will have the authenticated use of we can get the Sui's with this lesson in the controller.
OK then what we want to do is first of all run our assertions.
Naturally if you don't love running your assertions in line as such and you want to keep the order all
the way we planned out you can save this in a variable so response it causes and then assert that the
use was two 200.
And then you can also assert Jason to assert that we see a possible structure of response from a server
and would see the stutterers should be ok.
And then finally make sure that this lesson has received saw the stall.
So why don't we do this this a search and then call a user.
I will call a has completed methodic has completed lesson method which takes the lesson and we are going
to check if it's true.
And then for security.
Let's call exactly the same or false to assert that it's false.
OK so everything was like we think it does.
OK so we've called a complete lesson for the first lesson but the second lesson is not complete.
So I said that is false.
Now we don't top this math.
But don't worry we're going to go step by step and actually make that happen at the end.
OK now let's run this test.
First of all before I want the let me use the use class and find the lead lesson and actually flush
Rhenish because we interviewed and read this and finally use my refresh on the streets.
OK let's go.
Let me run that P-H you need no filter on to this test cookie.
That's a first.
So it's a 200 but received or fall for unhopeful means this you are or does not exist right.
So let's head over to the Web the BHB and create new routes with several routes.
And remember we want to be a published and we want it to be series computer lessons and we wanted to
keep identify our lesson right here and we use them because automatically lovely's we inject the lesson
class into a controller right.
Then we match this to what suits control.
That's completely awesome.
OK that's one that has to be OK.
You see the 500.
If you want to see what the error is your test you just need to disable exception handling so this without
exception handling.
Run it again.
Now we have clean the error method complete lesson does not exist the whole good service to his country.
And we're going to create a complete lesson metho.
So a public function compeer lesson and we are taking a lesson right here.
OK so let's run days one more time and we have invalid Jason was written from the OP because we know
each any anything.
Not so much.
Actually this was a successful response.
Why this was skipped.
OK so what do we want to do we all want to complete the lesson so we'll just call authenticated user
on we'll call the complete lesson methode on posts in lesson and we will study some thought using our
units.
US too we know it works.
So for us to pass the test we need to return a response with a J sign and we need to pass in a particular
reason which is such use OK.
Right that's all I'm going to do.
Let's run that one more time.
And now we haven't we're talking a complete lesson on model.
So of course member complete lesson on all which means we authenticated user.
Right.
So what we should do is make sure that we logging this user and we do that by calling this thing us
user.
OK Rhonda.
And we have called on the find method has completed the lesson.
Now this is the part of our application that is breaking because this successful this was successful
and now we're using a Hoskuld Peter unless we use some method which is not different.
Let's pause for a moment.
Scale this error in the very next.