Guys let's have done with this we need to unit test the highest completed lesson method.
And then we're going to create it.
OK.
So head over to my user test.
So test can check if user has completed the lesson.
So we want to pass a lesson to the complete lesson thought and that should be done to us true or false.
If the US computer the lesson.
True if the user has not completed the lesson false.
So how are we going to make this test.
We need to use up and then we need a series which has lessons and then for action we're going to complete
a lesson.
And then for sessions would assert that they had completed lesson method returns true for the complete
lesson and maybe falls for an uncompleted lesson.
OK.
So quite a user we can copy that from here.
And by the way raising red is right so we're going to flush with these.
So this flush Radice create a user quit or less than quit.
Another lesson in that series.
So copy that and this will take care of this both steps.
So we flush this quit use our quit or less and create another lesson in that series which is lesson
two.
And then for us to complete that lesson we'll just call use our complete lesson and we're only going
to be in less than one then four assertions would see this as search that user has completed lesson.
I will pass in Lesson one and would say this should be true right and then we'll do exactly the same
assertion but false.
So for Lesson Two would say assert false.
So this research and return true or false.
If this user has not completed the lesson and we turn to the use ask completely OK that's our test let's
run it ph be in it and filtered through to this test.
OK we have our Eyrecourt on the fight has completed lesson Mithal.
We have our learning traits or Anstee and we are going to work with it.
So our create public function has completed lesson and this method is expecting lesson run it again
game and we have a search that know it's true because this is expecting that we return a boolean but
now it will turn in lower.
So how do we want to check if a user has completed a lesson.
We have a list of all the lessons that have been completed.
For our particular series right here there's a method that does that for us right here get completed
lessons for us.
So we have the computer lessons for series and we have that lesson.
That we are trying to construct.
So what are we going to do is return Inari.
Because the method that gives us all the computer lessons actually we just source on how we write.
So return in three and the first thing we pass is the lesson ID which is the door and then we need to
pass the haystack we just days get complete adolescence for a series.
OK.
And we need to pass in the series.
So what's the lesson I would call series right here to get the series that that lesson belongs to.
OK.
So that's how we check if a user has completed a lesson.
So remember this method is returning to us on our way of adolescence and it's actually holding the IDs
of those lessons and we can now check if the idea of the lesson that we would pass is in that area.
OK.
So let's run not just get going.
So it's successful.
But now remember that we are truly creating this test right here because we were testing our watch serious
thought and we're trying to make sure that when we automatically receive a response from the server
they should return true and they should return false.
OK.
So let's run this test right now to see if anything changes.
PH be unique I will filter to that test.
Great.
Now we have a successful test.
Everything seems to be working OK.