OK let's talk about you before we move on we want to make sure that we know which lesson we are watching
presently.
And we also want to make sure we know which lessons have been completed or not.
So let's take of that in I watch that later the.
And what we are going to do is actually work in this for each loop.
First of all we want to attach a class of active on the active lesson.
So in this for each loop we have the lesson the current lesson stored in a variable.
And on this ph file we have the lesson that has been passed on to this view in the Vaibhav lesson.
So what are we going to do is right here we're going to please an estate man.
So doing the loop if no ID is required to lessen ID.
And if then we are simply going to quote aktif.
So right here I'm just going to see actually.
OK.
So this is only going to be generated if the lesson in the current loop is because the lesson that was
fastened to this fire.
Next I want to display maybe an icon to show that this lesson has been completed.
Maybe a check or something like that.
But now we're going to start simply.
So if our user has completed lesson and will pass in L into that method and then we're going to see
and if right here so we can do a couple of things we can have a tick tick box or whatever I can we want
to have.
But for now just to keep things simple I'm just going to say we should have a small text that says completer.
OK then you can modify this however you want.
So we check if the authenticated user has completed this lesson.
Now we're going to decide in future if we want the user to be able to watch a lesson without being authenticated
but that will come later.
And in case we want to use that to watch us with our been authenticated we're going to have to wrap
this to check if there is any authenticated user.
OK because if there is no authenticated use or we don't want to do this it's going to break down.
But now we're sure that the user is authenticated.
So let's just hope with this for now.
OK.
Let's refresh and there we go.
One of them has been selected as such but then none of them have been completed.
Therefore we don't see this block let's walk on for having that Ajax request for us to actually complete
a lesson.