This father we have four components that are components and alerts to the user that he's finished watching
the video.
But before that's what we want to do is actually make an Ajax request to complete that NSN for the user
for that series.
And then we display this message to the user.
OK so that's quite a method called complete lesson on these components and this method is going to use
examples to fire that request.
So let's import exudes.
OK.
So just to review what the.
PH BE we have that post requests.
That completes the lesson and we need to pass in the lesson ID.
We already tested this so we know it's working.
So right here all we need to do is say XOs the post in the correct year.
I see this completely Assen and looks like we need to pass the lesson IDs so I'm going to change this
to back 6 so we can concatenate the lesson ID and then right here.
I'll just quote this.
That lesson that ID.
OK.
So that's the you know.
And then when you pass in the data for the spoors requests which is an empty object and Dan would say
that.
Then we receive a successful response from us.
What we want to do is now call our display video alert method.
OK.
So right here we're going to see this dot display video.
And then at the top in the wall mounted hook at the bottom when the player listens to and rather than
calling me already it's going to call this dot complete lesson.
OK.
So we listen to that event when the lesson is completed.
And once we hear that event we call a complete lesson mid-thought the complete lesson method as an Ajax
request to this point which is going to complete that lesson for I use.
And once that request is successful we call the display we do a lot more thought.
We just go into all the user you just completed the lesson or the Sui's.
OK.
So let's check this out in the browser.
I'm just going inspect right there.
Hard refresh.
And right now we haven't completed this lesson so I'm going to plate and phosphor that it's there and
so naturally fires that request and magically we see we have here you have completed this series.
So I click on OK and let's check out our network to see if any request was fire.
And right here we just call that the request was actually fired.
So I'm just going to expand this a little.
We have that request to the complete lesson for listen to and preview.
We have the status OK.
That was Sir responded to us.
OK.
So now I'm going to refresh this page and if you check out we have the complete set message right here
which means this lesson was completed.
OK.
So let's go ahead and also try to complete this video.
I'm going to play it fast for that and you see here we completed this lesson because he just of course
was fired.
That's the response if I click on OK it refreshes goes to the next.
But now all three have been completed.
OK.
So the completion starters for this series is 100 percent.
Great job.