OK guys welcome back.
Iraq's a little bit of walk on they use us so we can actually see something.
The concerns they use are OK.
So I just created a little template right here that we're going to be using because we're going to come
to the money parts.
We're going to need maybe a week for the use of the card and stuff like that.
So I decided to create you know our very top system right here.
OK.
So you cannot really just copy this on the template.
It's really easy.
OK.
So we can also be editing the users for free and stuff like that.
But first I want us to talk with this.
We can get the lessons completed for the user and we can get the series brainwashed.
OK.
So remember this is just a now that I'm just using.
So what we can do is actually drive out the number of lessons completed and see just been washed test.
So we can actually have those methods then we're just going to use them in our view.
OK.
So let's go ahead to our user test and we're going to create a test to make sure that we can get the
number of lessons completed or actually we should start with the series being watched.
OK.
So we're going to see test all series being watched by years.
So what we want is we want to create a user.
We want to create some lessons for CBS.
OK.
So let's say we need to flush out the tables because we will create a user create a lesson or two.
I mean just be studying right now.
So we have one series right.
So why don't we create a second series and this series is going to be having less than three.
And we also have less than four for this series.
So therefore four lessons lesson four to belong to see which two we just need to specify series ID right
here that you two.
OK.
So what we have now is two lessons belonging to series one and two lessons belong to Suvi to switch
to.
OK.
So that's our instep now for action would complete some lessons in series 1 and 2.
Remember this is how we used to know if the user has actually started the series if he has completed
at least one of the lessons in that series.
Then once we complete those lessons with one of my assertions we'll call our math to get the series
that this user is watching and then would assert that Tsui Swan is a man.
And also I said that's Zeus too is our mom.
OK.
So what we can do is let's just create another series for our own security.
So we're going to have five and six.
So five and six belong to series ID.
OK.
So we have to see which right now and then we're also going to assert at the end that series 3 is not
among the least of series that this user is watching.
OK now let's go ahead and complete lesson on Anderson twe.
So we use our complete lesson will pass in lesson and then use our complete lesson on past in Lesson
three.
OK so we've completed this for see.
We've committed this forces of Saussy wish to therefore with no completive and UFOs streaming into issues
into which one and two bodies are watching.
We therefore the next thing we need to do is get the satellite series.
OK.
So start that series or the series that this user is watching.
So we'll would say get this by calling use our series being watched method.
OK.
So this is the method that we call to get all the services that are being watched by these user then
we need to decide what type of detail this method should be returning to us.
OK.
So why don't we receive our current election of series and they think this is going to actually be helpful.
So now we need to run our sessions knowing that we want our collection of series.
So we're going to first of all see a surge in stands of eliminate support collection class and pass
in stuff that's serious and then the next assertion is to make sure that that collection is actually
a collection of series.
So I would call certain stands off but this time we'll be checking that it's an instance of a broadcast
series class and we'll get any random element from that collection.
And finally just like we did in the other test I want to get the ideas singlehandedly from this.
So I've discussed the ideas of such a series because you started a series Pulok only the ideas and then
I would just see all so it returns to me and I see the idea of all of this stuff that's serious.
OK then I'll say this search.
Who are we.
And we need to pass in the middle.
So I would say lesson which is lesson one and we'll get the series and we'll get the ID and we'll passing
the haystack which is IDs of stuff that's serious.
OK.
So we also have to do exactly the same thing for lesson here because this is lesson to be are complete
an age which means lesson series to also should be inside this ID.
So Lesson 3 series I should be here.
And then we're going to do the same thing for less than four but it's going to be false.
So actually for less than five or six anyone.
OK.
So I said force that lesson six ideas inside this series.
OK so this is a really long test.
So let's go ahead and go through it before we start one in our test.
First we want to get all the series being watched by this user.
So we are ready.
The trouble is then we get the use of a new user.
We create some serious.
So right here we've created one and we've added two lessons that's used here.
We've created two and we've added two lessons that we use and we've also created a third series and
we've added two lessons to that use.
Now we've made the use of stop watching series one by completing one lesson series one.
And we've also made the use of a stopwatch in Series 2 by completing one lesson in Series 2 right here.
OK then we get all the stuff that's serious series my watch Matt gets in this methode series being watched
and then we assert that what is returned to us is a collection.
And what is returned inside that collection our suits.
And then we get all the ideas from this collection and then we assert that the idea of see which one
is actually that very idea of Zeus is a story that I read but I also say it is not.
OK so let's go ahead and run this test to see what we get.
You know feuds are to this test.
OK so caught on the find mid-thought C-rist being watched so would Healthwatch are learning that.
Ph be.
And what creates that method is being watched.
OK so let's run that again.
And now Phil as such is an instance of eliminate support collection.
OK so this is all we have to talk about how we want this to work.
OK so first of all remember this is all we are saving our records in the database.
OK.
So we use our user id series and then Series ID.
And this is all we have in our Rennie's database.
What we can do is to get all the keys for a particular use or for any series then we can pass in a white
card to this database and then find any key that ends with this and that has the user's ID.
I'm going to show you what I mean.
Remember for this use or if you want to get maybe use of one serious one it means we are getting all
the completed lessons for use on one and see which one the same thing if they use those watching series
too.
OK so same thing if the user was watching so its true were going to have a one series too.
And if the user was watching series we were going to have a one and we're going to have Series 3.
OK.
So what he says is this is the only thing that changes the number right here.
So we can start the database to give us all the keys which half use a woman and which are serious and
they will put a wild right here to get all of these records.
OK so if we have all of these records in our database then we passed in Diski what is going to happen
is we are going to have all of these sent back to us.
Therefore when we receive all of this we know the user is watching we want to choose a history and we
can not extract this idea to get the series on the database and send in a collection.
OK so let's get to it.
We'll get the keys so key is because Reddy's and release has a key Smith thought and we can pass in
a word Katsu.
This is when you search in its store to see if we have keys that match this pattern.
So what we'll do is we'll call use our and then we'll call this right and then call on series and Kaalam
and then we'll pass in an asterix to show a white cut.
So we have gone through a rewrite here.
It's going to be returned to us.
OK then we can now extract or find a series on the database with this case.
So one is going to be returned to us is going to be an array of maybe use or once every few years or
once we see one.
OK.
Depending on the number of lessons or series that the user is watching.
Then when we have these this we can use a For Each loop to look to each and every one of these kids
because remember we have an hour we birds we need to reach our collection.
So for each.
And then I'll just call and for each right here and I'll say kids ask me and we be doing is right here
I'm just going to show you what would do would get serious ID by Colleen explode which is a natural
function.
I'm going to explain what it does.
I would say that the limiter is a Kahlon and would pass in key right there.
OK.
So if you read up see if you read out what I expect from those it returns an array of strings each of
which is a substring of string formed by splitting it into boundaries formed by the string delimiter.
OK.
So this is what it's going to do if we have use of one colon one colon series called twe then our explode
function is going to give us an array as such.
So you are then one then a series and then three.
OK.
So it's going to take this delimiter that we passed in.
So this column right here and it's going to use it to break the string into an array.
OK.
So for example if we had a string it can be maybe a string with cos if you want to break each and every
one of these parts into an array you just explode and use the comma.
OK so now we have an array of such.
And for us to get this element we can just get it right here.
So we would say get the element read the the key of tweak the index of tweak OK because it is 0 1 2
3.
So we can get the element of index of 3 which is the series ID.
Ok then now that we have that series ID we can actually store 8 in an array.
So let me just create a series IDs are we right here.
Okay.
And then after we have these we can just see how we push which is a pitch we thought and we can push
in to the series.
Ideas are.
And the value we're pushing is Series ID.
Once we have the ID of the series we'll push it into this avi and then remember we want our mid-thought
to get a collection and returns us.
OK.
So what we're going to do is get serious Kollection is going to be cost you collects series IDs.
OK so now we have a collection of IDs.
Then we'll just map over that collection pass in a close up and right here we're going to have access
to the ID.
OK.
So then we're going to return series find ID.
So this is our collection.
We simply get a collection.
My Christian collects on the series ID's Ari and then we can map to that collection.
And then for each of the elements in that collection we are simply going to find the series with that
ID and then return it.
OK.
So for us to actually USE the reason we have to report it at the top so use broadcast series and then
right down at the bottom we can actually return this.
OK.
So we turned the collection once we finished mapping over it.
OK so that is a lot.
OK we've done a lot on this method.
We're going to go for it.
But now let's just focus on trying to see if we're actually on track.
OK.
So let's watch that test again.
The test is successful.
All right.
So it just succeeds because we've gone through everything and I think we've done the right thing.
So in the very next video I'm going to go through each and every one of the steps that we've caught
and we're going every photo.
And if you have any ideas about how to make this better I don't hesitate.
Go ahead and share but we're going to go through what we did right here because there's a lot to learn.
OK.
So see you in the very next video.