That great let's go to the Swiss bean watch method once again so that everybody can be on track.
Our main aim is to get the series that the user has started watching so that we can maybe told a user
this or they've recently started series that you've been engaged into it's been updated.
You can watch it right now or something like that.
OK.
We've saved this series in the database which is the Ready's database with such keys.
OK so you use a one series one which means they use Isen wouldn't you see which one.
Same thing.
Same thing for the history.
So we have such keys in our database.
How do we get them from our database so that we can fetch all these ideas and that the user is not watching
this series we use already skees command and the rediscuss command and taking our parts on.
And there would Franke's that much this pattern.
So in this case we are getting the keys that match the pattern with these asterisks.
OK.
And it means get a key whatever key that has user and has the ID of the user.
And then he has a series and then he has whatever number and get all of his keys.
So in the case where we have all of these key safety in the database this is what is going to be returned
to us on our way.
We actually don't want these keys.
Right.
What we want is this last digit at the end which represents the society.
So what we do is we create a new army which is called suicides.
And then we look to all of those keys that we got from the trapeze.
We exploit them using the column and they will disappear supreme effort and then we get the last elements
of that array which is the idea of the series.
Now we simply push it to the sorry.
OK.
Now finally we need a collection of series.
So we create a new collection.
We map over that collection and simply return the series that we find from the database using that ID.
So now when we're talking about refactoring what we could do is actually make this method clear and
more useful.
So would create another thought I'm going to call series being watched IDs and this is certainly going
to get the IDs for us.
So we move out these comments and this part which returns to us the idea is I'm going to cut it out
and pasted right here so we get the keys.
Create a new R-E save all of those keys in there and then we can just return series ideas right here.
OK.
So we have serious ideas we return them.
So this is an avi of all the ideas of the series that this user has been engaged into.
Then right here what we can do is collect this series being watched IDs by clean method.
And if we want to make artifacts or rock or shots or what we can do is actually remove the need for
this variable and return right here and we'll just change the map function to this method like that.
OK.
So collect all of the ids and then map to them and get the suits.
And like we said when we refracts all or change our code we one that says to make sure that everything
works correctly.
So what's my user test and I'll copy the name of that of that test on or run it ph be it future to this
test and get your process.
It means you good to go.