Let's go one step further we want to talk about getting no math lessons completed for Pensacola use.
Let's head straight into it with credits to guide us and this would be test can get a number of completed
lessons for years.
OK.
So how do we want this to look let's just create or use or create a series with some lessons and then
would create maybe two series with two different lessons each and then complete one of the lessons on
each of the series then we count that the number of computer lessons should be I think two or four depending
on the situation.
OK so let's go ahead and dive into this.
So not to type out a lot of stuff we need.
Ready is to last we need to use our we need to serious like we agreed.
So I'm just going to copy all of this pasted in.
So we have a user we have one new series and this series has two lessons.
We have another new series and this one has two lessons.
OK.
So we don't need this last one right here.
So our actual step is going to be calling complete Glosson on lesson and also calling complete lesson
on Lesson 3.
Therefore the number of computer lessons for this user is two.
And why don't we make this on the list price here by completing another lesson.
So would have a lesson five which is going to be long to Siva's too.
And we're going to complete it.
So complete lesson lesson Phife.
OK.
So we're going to call this cert equals and we know that expectorate is to easy and we know that we
want to compare against user get the number of complete lessons.
OK.
Or we can call these get short on number.
So get total number of completer lessons is going to give us to turn on my computer lessons on in our
database for this particular user.
So I guess that's actually the only assertion we might want to run therefore let's run this math thought.
And yet we haven't ever seen a total of completer lessons is not found on this class.
So we're going to copy that headbutts all learning that BHP and create that run the test again.
And we are filled as much as six rocketry.
OK so how do we get the total number of completed lessons we already know how to get the older series.
So what we can do is we could get all the series for this particular user just like we did using the
wildcat.
And then for each of these keys we can add the number of elements in the value for this key and then
we'll get in the way of complete adolescence.
I'll see what I mean.
So I'm just going to see results equals zero and I'll quit a For Each loop.
So for each keys as key and for each I'm going to see results course results plus and now we need to
get the number of elements that are returned from this key.
What I mean is if we had use our won series who won for example and we also had use or won series 2
then in this for each loop when we have this one we are going to make a square which already store and
then get the value of this key.
So for example query our database or we're going to have maybe one to three which are the lessons that
have been completed in this lesson in this series and then we're going to count the number of elements
in that avi.
OK.
So I would say Ready's as members will pass in and this is an array.
So we'll call our Cowen's methought and it's going to give us the number of elements in that avi.
So for example if there were three completer lessons in between and then it's going to go to the next
step and if maybe there are two lessons completed then it's going to count and give us two elements
and then it's going to continue into these result in Georgia.
OK.
And then at the end of that oppression we can just return the result.
So I think that should do it.
Let's run a test and see what we get.
OK.
So it's great it's passing.
So to get that number of computer lessons we get all the keys for that use are.
And then we count the number of lessons that are in that are we.
When we queried that database on the set and then we add to the result and that's it.
So in the next lesson we should be able to use that data to display the number of completed lessons
for use or and also the series being watched for that particular user.