OK let's officially quit the speech.
How do we want this to function.
We want somebody who doesn't own the profile or will be able to see it.
OK.
For example you can see other users are therefore we have to maybe pass some way to identify the user.
You are out.
So we're going to be using the SLOC field for the user which saved us a username in our users table.
So let's just go ahead and set up a route in our web that it would be the profile and we can create
a profile on the Arts Index and we want this far out to actually accept a parameter.
OK so I'm going to call this varments I use art because I want to use Lovell's Rob model by name and.
And I need to create this Consolo saw created here.
Our son may control the first controller in our control.
We need an index and I thought and we are requesting that level automatically injects to use our swords
to use but curses are here.
And if love will just automatically inject the user.
It's going to try to inject the user by the ID of the user but then he wants Lavo to use their use on
the field on this class.
So we are told Lavoe get Keenum and would return use our name.
OK so lovingly squit you try to find the user are using the User Name column in the database.
OK.
So for now let's just return a view and would also pass in refusal which is the use of the record from
the wrong model binding.
OK so we know my username.
Let's just copy that and try to get this right.
We have a form for me to call up our database we can go and we'll just get all the users but CAS use
all and the user name is cutie.
OK great.
So we should actually pull that out fresh.
There we go.
We have to use a speech right there.
So what do we want to do we want to air quotes the number of completed lessons on the series being watched.
OK.
So I over to the profile view and right here the number of lessons is going to be user get.
So total number of lessons completed which is the methodology actually created in the last video OK.
So it's actually get total number of complete adolescence.
So we're going to replace that.
And that's what we have then for the series being watch.
Let's just make sure we haven't this one.
So we have to rewrite now because the series that we have in our database right now we actually completed
all of them in our watch beach.
OK.
So three lessons completed and series being watched what we can do is pass new series from our control.
So I'm going to get serious right here.
So with a series and it be user.
Get serious.
OK.
And this method is also coming from right here because we test that and we know it's working.
So therefore in our profile the blade ph B where we have been watched we can just Cluj or Welkom the
lead the PH P and recopied is the exact same four hours loop and in our profile we just be studying
for now safe refresh trends to get property of an object.
OK let's go to our recopied to see what we have we have for each series which we passed in the title
description or read more.
So where could the Arrow be coming from.
So when we died or in our control to see what we actually have.
So we use our series being watched or just died and fresh.
So we have an array.
And one of the elements is such Really.
That's why we're having some errors.
So this is not much of a big deal.
I think it's because we have a really messy database so values here and there and we actually don't
have the appropriate Ready's connection because we've been testing Whitted and we're using it now in
our view.
So that's why it took confusions but then for us to protect ourselves we can head over to what learning
that BHB and right here when we are mapping which we can fuel to eat to make sure that all know values
are rejected.
And we do that basically calling the full time method.
So the collection is going to move on and force values.
So let's refresh an artichoke or date them and now we have just one element in the tree which is the
one that was successfully found in the database.
OK.
So that should fix that.
Oh controller that died that we have refresh OK we're back.
So we have a list of series being watched by the user.
And then we have a list of lessons that the user has completed.
Now something I'd like us to talk about is how we want things to happen if the user is authenticated
or not and effectually locked out.
Right now I believe we're going to have a lot of errors everywhere because we've not been thinking about
that.
But we'll take that into very next video.