I'm going to start off by sharing you and every page and I achieved this page by logging out and visiting
the route to watch a series I'll be receiving this as well because in that while we are trying to get
the authenticated user.
And he obviously is going to fail because like I told you and locked up.
So this brings us to deciding if we want to permit users to watch series without been authenticated
or not.
Now if you want to use words to see which with all be authenticated then what are you going to do is
everywhere for your to and authenticated user you need to wrap this in an IF statement to make sure
that the user is authenticated before your Trenche you use that feature.
But if the user is not authenticated then you can skip that feature.
OK so what I'm going to do is actually simply take care of this route by securing it with a meter where
we just off.
OK.
So I'm going to create a mirror work up and put this group with the osme the where.
And every single water they want to use to be authenticated before assessing.
I'm going to put it in there.
OK.
So I want to make sure that the result is authenticated before watching a series.
So the watch series on the complete lesson would require an authenticated user.
So a piece that in so also this where the user can watch a Sui's requires an authenticated user.
So also pasted in and.
I think that's it.
So if you come back and refresh this page we discover that we automatically redirect that to the beach
where we have to log in.
OK so we haven't customized this view yet but nothing to worry about.
We can take care of that later.
So right now we can go ahead and again and everything should return to normal.
OK so notice how our status is returned to us when we try to log in use are we using the traditional
method.
Because remember we have an AJAX logging functionality in place we don't actually have to tackle this.
And we can use our task to make sure that the user is using a traditional method of authentication is
actually returned to a view and not a stutterers OK.
OK so now the user is locked in.
I just visited the home page and I'll try to visit that route and I can visit the page to watch a series
again.
OK.
Last thing I want to talk about is this navigation bar.
So I want to make sure that the user isn't on the street or before he sees them creates his rounds right
here.
And they also receive out OK.
So we have this is I mean my thought in know I use a class and what we're going to do is head of water
up the bleed Ph be.
And we have these navigation elements right here which we're going to edit.
So why don't we have a costume bleach statement that will help us to check if we use ice at me or not
I'll head over to my service provider and we're going to registar the lead if I will call this up me
and plus in this close call and see return off you.
He's mean because you know I use the last we have these is like I mean my father could help us know
if they use ice on administrators.
So with this key right here we can head about all of that lead.
And when we have this off check we can also have an admin check.
So by say I mean house then and I mean OK that looks real convenience then we can take the all serious
route and create Saraswat and paste them right there.
OK.
So let's refresh this page.
We see those swabs because issues us on and street all but we're going to go out and then visit our
registar page registar our new accounts and click on we just stop and it takes us to the home page.
Now receipts are our home page.
We have just called and then hey the name of the user because this user is not an administrator.
He cannot access the creates Sui's page and other pages that are protected for administrators only.
OK.
So remember we have or I mean that we where all the routes that can only be accessed by administrators
are registered.
Therefore even if the user tries to navigate through that speech using the you are out he's not going
to get it.
OK so I think that's a little clean up.
We have a little bit of cleanup patches to do now.
We're going to take care of that before we actually go into the money part of our application.