It like we said we're going to some kind of procedures.
So I want to tackle this when the use of the speech if he's not locked in he can be asked to log in
and if he doesn't have an account he can be asked to sign up.
Then if the user is already locked in.
Remember we talked about redirecting him to the CBC wash so that he can just continue but he hasn't
yet started the series then he can start from the beginning.
OK.
So what are we going to be doing is writing a little test.
So head towards or use that test and this test is simply going to help us to get the next lesson that
he's supposed to be watching.
OK.
So for example if in a particular series you use us finished use or wants you as one for example and
we have.
And we want to do the naturally that series has four lessons of life as such when the user clicks on
to concentrate on the bottle which ones will be used to lesson for another lesson one because it really
wants to Lesson one.
OK.
So you couldn't and method that we actually get the lead test which is this one.
And then it's going to get the next lesson in the database which is this one.
And then we use our two dots one.
OK.
So let's just go with this.
SAS can get next to each lesson.
So we watched by use on talking.
So what do we need.
Let's just say we need all of this sets up and we need just one sees.
I think in this case.
So we have to flush these Then we have Yousaf and then we have a new lesson.
We have another lesson that same series.
Why don't we create a third lesson in this series.
Ok then what are we going to do is we're complete let's move one and two.
And I would assert that when we try to visit the watch Seuss rug where we don't get to listen.
OK.
So we use our complete lesson or commit lesson on complete lesson two.
So actually this is a unit test.
So let's just test that the method works and that would create a future test to test the redirect.
OK.
So right now what you want to do is see next to last lesson because you all get.
Next lesson to watch for a series.
So we're passing this idea.
OK.
So get next lesson to watch is the method that we want to create and this is called taking the series.
Such are all of these deals are these the values or the lessons that have been completed and then screen
to get the next lesson or are these I suppose we are watching.
OK.
So you just assert equal holes.
And what we can do is compare the ID.
So we want this is less than one lesson to listen to me.
So we once listened to the ID should be called to the next lesson.
And this is something we have to think about because remember we haven't yet told our lessons.
What are they playing.
So let's go ahead and make sure we do that.
We want to be right the factory settings.
So in all the lesson actually we just check it out.
What they are doing is we're simply assigning the opposite much 100.
But in this case we want to make sure that we order all these episodes in the correct order.
So that's one should be 100 listened to would be to do it.
Lesson we would be very it.
OK.
So they're going to play in that or that such that when we complete lesson 1 and 2 the next to be less
than three.
OK.
So I certainly caused this.
I think I think this is one session we need to warn.
How about creating a fourth lesson on how exactly this bandish would be for the fourth.
And then what we can do to solidify sessions is to complete lesson write right here after we've run
the first assertion and then would call our session again.
OK.
So we remember more sessions.
You have the more difficult it is for your test oil assertions to be deceptive.
OK.
So we have our next lesson when we assert that it equals days.
What we'll do is call this method a game and you see a certain equals less for I will get the idea right.
OK.
So after searching listen to me is the next one to play.
What complete lesson to me.
And then I that lesson for the next one to play.
So I think that says this sets let's go ahead and run it at uni.
So we got this.
OK so we need to create the next lesson.
Watch it all the way to my learning the PH B and all that.
And the station the suit he's run that again and trying to get hoppity an object as expected.
OK so when do we want do we want to get all the lessons completed for that series and then we want to
just return the last one.
That's what we want to do right.
So we should have a method right here that returns to us all the lessons.
So getting them of completed lessons completed lessons for charades.
OK.
So all we can do is you can see less than ideal because and this would play Baichu methodology was the
last element of an array and we call this good complete lessons for a series of possible series.
OK.
So let's actually check out that method to make sure we are doing the correct thing.
We said get our way of computer lesson IDs for Shirish and this is helpful.
We can actually use blocks because right now I'm trying to verify this my fault at all times when I
want you to return and we can check all the.
Returns an array and the palm anti-SUV series of type by Cassy's.
And this is what it does.
Great.
So we can use it.
OK.
So once we get that idea all we want to do is we turn less and find a pass less than ideal.
So we can actually in laying this by not having to create this variable so we can cut this out and pasted
right here.
OK so next lesson to watch we squint to get the last element in the Get lesson get completed lessons
for CBS Arri and then he's going to use that to find the lesson.
OK.
So let's one that says one more time and you see only eboshi pass by reference.
This is something that should be us we can't call my thoughts in my thoughts in my thoughts.
Too many times and as such.
So let's just stick with the variable.
So lesson like the core to this Boston lesson.
OK.
Just so BHB doesn't worry us anymore.
So that's one that and it's still arcane.
So I'm going to do this I'm going to say lesson ID equals.
And assume it's ease and rather than getting the right here I'm going to see less of.
That's it.
So it's telling us only the table should be passed by reference that's a catch we think.
OK.
So we can actually pass a math thought into this metho so that it takes in available and stuff like
that too much in testing.
So I think it should be fine by now that's one other game.
OK so Phil asserting that too much is expected to read.
OK so let's check on that.
Yes.
Remember we want the next to lesson that we use I should be watching and not the last lesson these are
watched.
OK.
So what we should do is we want to find that lesson we should get the next lesson in the series that
you use or should watch.
OK.
Remember we have get the next lesson.
If you had one lesson that Ph.D. we get next lesson in the Sui's in the play list right.
So we can call this method up on this lesson.
OK.
And the thing that should give us the correct result.
OK so far less than expected type object.
Let's check out our tests 1 6 5 set a course lesson for greats who should actually be checking listen
for ID right.
So let's run that one more time.
Great.
We have a success with us finally.
So all we did was get all the lessons that this is are completed and then we get the idea of the last
one which means that's the leaders that these are completed and then we get that lesson and then we
get the next lesson in the play list.
OK.
So what we can do is actually write a little test to protect our souls because remember we are doing
a lot of assumptions like here in case there is no next lessons watch.
Are we possible into this.
My thought it's going to break for example you can break right here because this is Guinta we know and
then we're calling a method on all.
That's going to really be a big deal but I'm going to handle it in a couple of lessons for now I think
this is going to really help us in a few.
So let's work on this in the very next lesson.