OK guys welcome back.
This is where we left off in our projects and we are able to VCDs of course and be able to check if
to use ice cream.
Now what I want to focus on is actually when we redirect the user when he clicks on this button.
So remember if these users really started this series then we are going to see a continual learning
Butson the user has started this ritual.
When you see a startling Motson like we see right now remember this new reason we created.
So before we jumped into that I'm going to go to my lesson test and I did my test a little right here
that says that 6 sense can get next and lessons from a lesson.
One we to do is when this is such that the next lesson and previous lesson method should actually never
give us no.
So does it always give us a lesson.
So in case we are trying to get the next lesson for the last lesson in that series it should just give
us the lesson and this we are trying to get the lesson for the first lesson in that series.
It should also just give us that same lesson.
So how are they going to edit my assertions.
Right here in a certain or answer or more but I'm going to change this to a certain equals and lesson
to right here just to get you to ease naturally the first series.
The first lesson in that is lesson one is the second and this is the last.
Therefore get previous lessons.
Really was more like it was doing but nobody which updated by saying listen to which is this first.
When we tried to get when we tried to get the previous lesson you should actually give us a lesson too.
I'm going to show you what way I'm doing this right here.
OK.
So the same thing for the next.
So we're going to see it equals lesson.
We will get the I.D. and then we'll get Lesson 3 and get the idea.
OK.
So if one does test right now it's going to feel so good to be in the field so to this test and he try
to get property of object because obviously it's not so much a one lesson the PH be forced to actually
check if this isn't all we're simply going to see available.
So the next lesson equals this and right here what we'll do is simply have a check if next lesson return
next lesson.
OK.
But if that checks feels then we turn this OK.
So if there's no next lesson then simply return the correct lesson then we're to go exactly the same
thing like your previous lesson so previous lesson in all this.
And if we have a previous lesson which means it's not all fault you value will return.
Previous lesson OK else would simply return this which means this lesson.
That's more access.
And now we're back going now why am I doing this.
If we had the virtue of 30 that we we have some methods that are dependent on the next lesson.
OK.
For example this get the next lesson.
Watch.
Remember if we're trying to get the next lessons what a loser really completed that series.
We don't want our website to break and say OK we can find this lesson or we can get a bunch of them
all but we really wanted to give us the last lesson of that series.
OK.
So that said now how do we use this method.
Remember we agreed if we had to watch or watch series.
All right.
We're not index mid-thought when you use at least watch a series.
He certainly didn't make that to the first lesson of that Suze.
But we do want that.
We want to check if the user has started the series.
And if the user has started the series will redirect him to the next lesson that he has to watch.
For example even if he's watched less than one and listen to the lecture he should be watching this
lesson.
OK.
Therefore we'll just see if the authenticated user right here.
And what we're going to do is check if you are hostile to series or puzzling to see us then we're going
to redirect the user somewhere else.
And when we directly use our Mott's dyslexic which is the first lesson but we are going to get used
and the name of the method we can get it from are learning to be which is getting a license watch and
back.
Enjoy or watch SHOWBIZ on call or see next lesson watch on passing the series.
OK.
So the USALS really started the series will redirect the user to this lesson.
Alice is going to read the letter the first lesson.
OK.
So let's go ahead and check if this is working.
So refresh.
And by the way let me share my view right here.
So we have our series The beat the beat and right here we have a continual learning check.
I start learning.
So these are start at the series.
We have continual learning and neither has or has not yet started.
We have stopped learning.
So we are locked in.
That's why we see the Lenny freckly can start learning it redirects me to the first lesson.
So you see the currents in this and now is the first lesson.
I'm going to do is complete the series by simply playing that video.
And now it's at the end.
We're going to click OK you direct me to the second one but now I want to head back to that series and
we have Cancian you're learning.
But now click on this and you see that automatically redirects me to Lesson 2 and that I think my friend.
It's really really PERFEITO.
OK.
You don't always go and select the next lesson that you stopped the next time you log into our website.
So I think that's very convenient.
Let's just go ahead and complete this one for fun.
OK.
We've completed this series then the next one is this entry we haven't wasted.
Let's head back to that series and then we can continue learning automatically we are redirected to
the last lesson of the series because we've completed this one and this is all we have to watch next.
OK.
So great.
I think this works perfectly just like we expected to.