Like something imagine a situation where you're already enrolled into the series and you want to continue
learning but then the next lesson or the previous lesson you were you watched was last.
And then you're trying to get the next lesson after the last squinched if you know.
Right.
But then you redirect to that beach.
It's just pop up on occasion.
So what I want to do is customize our next and previous lesson mythos and we're going to be using our
test to do this.
So remember when we were running the assertions Check out this I thought I mean just walking you remember
who created a lesson and created a second creature the third and then this one was the first one to
play in the play list.
This is the second and this is the last one to play.
But at the end we actually asserted that if we are trying to get the previous lesson for the first series
it should give us more.
And if we are trying to get the next lesson for the last series give us all but I want to change this.
I want to say we should actually check our search equals ID and we get less too easy.
So if we are trying to get the previous lesson of the first series it doesn't give us the first series.
And if we are trying to get to the next lesson of the last series then you should naturally give us
the last lesson.
OK.
So the last lesson of this series then this year was the last lesson.
The first lesson of the submission was the first lesson because we don't want more.
OK.
And that's one test to see what happens at this point.
You know it's futile.
I started in and sure enough we ever feel the French get property of object because right here we're
trying to get idea of law at the moment.
So we're at the crux of this mid-thought and whether we do this is I'm going to see if next lesson available
for this query and then I'm going to check Wike here if the next lesson is no.
So if next lesson
so if we have a positive or two see value then simply return next lesson.
OK but then if we don't have a truly value Nietzsche was known then we would return this.
OK so when we send the lesson that we have to do exactly the same thing with our previous lesson method.
So previous lesson because this then what we do is we check if we have a previous lesson.
If we do then we simply return to this lesson.
And then if we don't we simply return this then let's run our test right now to see if it passes and
it does.
Therefore when we get the previous or next lesson we would never have know.
Now why do we do this.
I'll take to my learning controller.
I'm learning the PH BE traits and I'm going to show you that there are some that actually depend on
the next AMPAS less than my thoughts for example the last one at the bottom which is the get the next
lesson to watch.
See right here we get the next lesson.
So if this actually returns more and the way it gets in next lesson of now or this method actually returns
now and we're returning to the view it's really going to mess up our.
Therefore we always want to make sure we have something for the usal.