As a result of our little math or change in the last episode we have a little problem and we are just
in the last lesson right here.
As you can see but then you have the next button.
Why is this.
That's.
I watched Blade BHB.
And check this out.
Remember the way we know if it's the last series is simply by checking if the next lesson is null and
the same thing with the previous lesson.
We're just checking if it's not.
But this time on we refer refactored our methods.
And they would never return.
Therefore this method would always show the next buttons no matter the lesson that we are viewing.
So let's simply change this for us to know if this is truly the last lesson.
Remember when it's the last lesson we would return the exact same lesson we are seeing right now.
OK.
So what we are going to be doing is checking if the next lesson is not equal to lesson ID.
So if it's equal it means that this is not really the last lesson.
Same thing with the previous.
If it's equal it means this is the first lesson because remember if it's the last lesson where turn
in the same lesson and if it's the first lesson we're returning the same lesson which is the first.
OK.
So who refresh now.
And it's not going away.
OK.
So we should be comparing ID right.
So we should compare IDs.
We should also implement that right here and they should also see ID.
OK.
Refresh.
Very go.
Looks like it's back to normal.
We don't have that bottle.
If I visit the first we also don't have the button.
Now I've taken the liberty of doing a little bit of cleanup for an application like the all series we
have an awesome speech right now.
And recently display was all of the series.
OK.
So just a page where you can see all the series that are in the application and then for the video lessons.
Actually if you check out our whole series and we visit this series and we check out by starting we
actually have all the lessons displayed here.
So if you want to take this region it's naturally included on the page for the single series.
Feel free to do it.
It's all up to you.
But I want us to actually dive straight into our payments.
Doing stuff with money.
The very very next lesson.
Thank you so much and see you there.