All right guys.
Welcome back.
Let's talk about Lavoe cashier like we agreed we're going to try to set up subscription based payments
in our application so our SAS are working.
We can watch your videos we can watch courses because we want our users to be able to watch Pat's GLOBAL
LESSONS OF THE JEWS only when we permit.
OK.
So we're going to be integrating Lovelle cashier which uses Strype behind the scenes.
First steps we need to install because shit.
So the instructions on level 5 and 5 documentation says you should require a cache and then you need
to register the service provider.
But then if you are using Level 5:25 chromatically there composite that JSM file contains a string.
I'm going to go ahead.
I'm going to go ahead and show you that.
So I'm going to search with composer Jason.
And you see to my lover cashiered our tree and I will show you this law will provide us Jason Stream
right here.
So it's automatically going to register the provider.
The provider so you don't need to do any of that.
OK.
But what you need to do is update your migrations.
So for Lavoe cashiers who are perfectly Bennet's updates the feuds in all use are stable and we need
to have a new subscriptions table.
So for the use a stable copy these four columns and then ahead of us who create users and our peace.
And then for our subscriptions stable we need to set this now just for everything to be clean.
I'm going to create a new immigration EHRSSON make migration creates subscriptions table and I would
say to create Fluxion because two subscriptions great sunami have a success or subscriptions migration.
So create subscriptions to.
So it has to create for the subscriptions and we can also drop it.
So I'm going to copy the use and I'm going to paste them right in right there.
OK.
So now we have users on subscriptions updated like in the documentation.
Finally we just need to use billable Sashka will be able to view the user.
OK so I'm going to go to my user that BHB and then I'm going to use this trace and just notice how novel
is going to hide all the methods that have to do with building the user behind these traits just like
we're doing with our own.
OK.
Then remember to set up the type keys and the model.
So if you over to services that actually write down we should have Stryper and which we can simply send
those keys by setting and NVI key and secret and you can get that actually from your stripe dashboard.
So if you see your stripe dashboard you can head over to your API and then you're going to have your
keys.
Right.
OK so now we have to test keys.
You can get the publishable and the secret.
OK.
So that's what you need to set up for your configuration.
So that's basically all we need to set up Strype in our application.
We're going to continue our degree in Skype in the very next lesson.