Having a subscription based application with a cashier it's really easy level cashier takes care of
most of the work behind the scenes.
So for example let's go ahead and look and look at how we can subscribe a user to a new subscription.
All we need to do like in the documentation like your is find a user and then on the user we call the
new subscription mid-thought we pass in the name of the subscription and then we also pass in the name
of the subscription on our stripe dashboard and then we call that creates mid-thought and we pass in
the token.
That's all we need to create a subscription but then look at this talken right here.
Where is it coming from.
What is that token.
This brings us to understanding how strike works.
And this is what they're going to be covering in this lesson to understand how Strype works.
We're going to start by checking out our dashboard.
And before we are able to use subscriptions you need to come to your subscription stop.
And then we need to go to our plans and then you need to create some plans.
OK.
So when you quit discipline's that's when you'll be able to call or pass these ID right here all the
identifier of the plan and then automatically subscribe to use or to that plan.
OK.
So do you plan or you just need today's Can-Can plan right here.
And then you put in the GITTOES.
So for example right you have a new plan that they call monthly.
So the idea is monthly.
The name is just monthly what I want to see on my dashboard and I said the price to nine dollars and
there's no trial period.
I also have a yearly if you check out the yearly I have an ID.
I have a name on there and I have the price for $99 year.
OK.
So that said once you set up the plans what happens is Strype needs to take in the user credentials
charge the card and then automatically it's going to set up a recruitment payment charge on that card.
OK.
So if you passing a card and you told Strype subscribe the card to this monthly plan every month is
going to charge you use are mindless.
But then if you subscribe to the yearly every year you subscribe to ninety nine dollars.
OK.
So the question that still remains is how the reports in the Strype took in the strike took them so
representation of the use us.
Remember our data base is not going to contain any credit card numbers or any expiry dates for us credit
card numbers.
But it's going to contain an identifier for that particular use in our data in our database.
OK.
We're going to be looking at it but what happens is we pass the credit card information to Strype by
an API call and then Strype is going to return to us a striped token when we get a striped token passing
into this method and then Lovelle cashier is when you make another API calls the Strype to coo yeards
that subscription.
OK.
So how do we get the use of credit cards or Strypes with us Tricon returns was destroyed took in less
checkout Strype documentation.
So remember the procedure.
First we take our users credit card.
We send it to stripe.
She's going to convert this credit card encryption and all of that stuff into a token.
So a string so a string representation of the credit card so that it's very secure.
It's going to give us about that stream.
It would give the street level cashier level cashier would pass in the string back to Strype and then
it's going to pass in the name of the plan and make sure the name of the plan is also a plan that you
created right here.
And then third is going to subscribe to the plan and then charge the user.
OK.
So how do we get the credit card and then send it to right.
We need to use checkout.
So in your novel and your Strype Doc's visit payments and then visit checkout and then you can go to
reference and what reference when you do it's going to teach us how to integrate this tripe checkout.
So if I visit for example this link right here and I click on the page with card you see we have this
region that pops up.
We can put in the use ID then the credit card is the most important why are we passing the credit cards.
And they would say pay 20 dollars.
This is going to create.
So can this token right here and then it's going to return it to us.
And then once that is returned to us we can now send it to level cashier and allow lot cash is going
to subscribe that you are using that token which is a representation of these credit card details.
OK.
So now would be to get this functionality on our phones and to make it work.
That's right some of us in the very next episode.