OK guys like we agreed we're going to start working with VGX.
We just try API to tokenized our costs and then we finally subscribe our users to our plan.
So let's go ahead and get started.
Remember in the payments checkout we got the reference so that we can learn how to customize this model.
OK.
So first thing right down here you want to go to the on top and then we're going to see what we need.
Looks like we need to import the stripe library and then we create a custom button and then we'll go
on from that.
OK.
So first of all let's just create a view just component that is squeege be in charge of payments.
We tried.
OK.
Or create a new component.
And I'm just going to call each tribe the view then I'm going to reduce the other components in my OP.
The Japs done and now I can use this components in my template.
So just for starters I'm going to head right to my views right here.
I'm going to create or subscribe that blade Ph be.
And then I'm going to just duplicate my profile page page study and move out all the markup like the
contents that we have right here.
And Dan also right here we need to pull off some of these methods and we can just change this header
to see subscribe to our or some sites.
Ok so now we have this what we can do here now is Mullens our com partner and so we can see what is
going on.
So views tripe and what have you.
Strype But then look at the first step is for us to include this script right here.
So how do we conclude it.
Remember we don't want to put it in the obviously that BHB If not it's going to be included in all of
our HMO pages or all of the beaches on the site which we don't want because we aren't mounting this
component everywhere right.
So we're going to talk.
I wanna lay out for the rest of my of the believe that should be in right down but some or maybe preferably
at the top so it's low that first.
Can you add a new section and I'm going to call the section scripts.
Okay.
Then I'll head over to my subscribe.
I'm going to quit a new section here called scripts and section and right here I can include my CGM
link.
OK.
So this creep right here I'm going to copy it or I'm going to paste it here.
Then let's head over to our Web page and create a simple route so that we can view that beach so routes.
It's going to be a Gad's VCDs tribe to visit said that's this or simply return a view which is exactly
to view the creator called subscribe.
OK.
Maybe we should actually call the SUBSCRIBE quite okay.
Now we'll visit the SUBSCRIBE watch.
We're going to see this view and hopefully if everything goes well that should be brought in.
Which is the scripts it should be you that right here form this view.
OK.
That said I've also had a lot of occasion.
This is lots of Skype viewers subscribing to found what do they do.
OK.
That's my forte.
Supposed to be subscribe with a B.
OK.
Refresh everything.
What now.
We check out our page source.
There we go.
We have Dart's scripts know that for us.
OK.
So let's check other documentation.
So looks like we need a Butson sort of knowing the user clicks on that button.
It opens up the Modahl that we saw right here.
So we are customized in the normal way so that we understand how it works and then we know how to maybe
make any changes that we want to do.
OK.
So after including this link we need to create a button so I don't my strap that you on we need a template.
And sure enough we need a script.
And in this template I'll have a button and this is when you see subscribe to the $9 plan monthly.
OK.
So it is and much Butson success and looks like we have a bottom for the monthly plan.
Right.
So if I head back to this and refresh.
Looks like we have our Butson right there.
OK.
So remember we have jewelry plans.
So we need to set up two Botswana's So our change is too much on food for example.
And I would change this two things nine dollars yearly.
Okay.
So the user chooses what plan.
And remember we can have this so we're going to wrap this in a day so we have just one word elements
refresh.
Great.
We have the monthly We have a yearly.
Now the next thing we need to do are cut into our documentation is create a handle on the cost track
check out and we call the configure meathook we pass in the key we pass in the image that we want to
be displayed for example right here this image so we pass the link to the EMH and then we call look
how so much can determine the low cost of the use of a levy person or to Kobar code to come which is
going to contain the token one stripe changes they use our credentials into stripe token.
OK so let me copy this and we'll have virtue of our script in our stride that you will create or Monserrate
who walk and or piece that in.
OK.
So we need a handler.
So we're going to create Konstanz handler because Strype checkout can figure out which person that objects
so just copy this right here and paste it right here.
Delete this.
We're done with it.
And looks like this function I'm just going to change everything.
So will be consistent with ESX.
So we have this method that is called once Treb makes an API call and changes the critical information
into a token.
OK.
Now we have the handler.
The next thing what do we do we need to set the button that is going to be clicked and then the handler
is going to be opened.
OK.
So open the model right here what you're doing is getting to the aliments with ID custom button right
here.
And then we are in the on events list now which is the click events to open the handler and after opening
each we can putting the critical information and all of that.
So how do we register our Click event handler.
I'm going to see when we click this button it should call my thought on this class called such Qype
for example.
But remember we are dealing with two methods the one for the area and one for the monthly.
So let's just see if you click on the month the button or the yellow button should pass in a string
called me into this subscribe method.
OK.
And on the subscribe for month week we're going to read you start to click events.
We're going to see call the subscribe misthought but this time around the permits are going to pass
in the stream call monthly.
So we have subscribed Matho less created or my thoughts object we call subscribe and this takes in the
stream.
So we're going to call that string plan.
What are we going to do is check if the plan is monthly.
So if the plan is mostly the regular set this is the plan it calls monthly and else would set this up
plan to be quote you yearly.
OK.
So we were referring to is this the plan.
So where don't we set it as a dieter are on this component.
So we'll have to return an object and plan would be an empty string by default.
OK.
So we check the plan.
We see it on dishcloths and then we're going to proceed to opening the handload.
OK.
So how do we open the lock need each pass in the name description and the imams.
So looks like we also need to know the amounts for the monthly.
Therefore we're going to say this the Amman's is a quarter to nine and nine because remember we are
pricing it in sense.
And if it's the yearly plan we also need to say this that Amman's is of course 9 99 99.
Okay.
Because it really wants $99.
OK.
So let's just set up our margins on this should be zero.
And I'm actually saving this because we're going to be making an API a quarter or so that's how quick
the subscription.
And we need to pass in the plan which fits the monthly on the.
So we better have this on our global data right here.
Okay.
So once we said that we already know if it's the monthly or the we need to open O'Hanlon Okay.
So we need to be able to assess the hand-glass when we do this would see this doc had a lot.
It's a cultural structure.
Therefore we have a handler right here which is known by default.
So when the complaint is it we save the stripe chicle configuration and once we save that in the hard
luck we are able to call the subscribe mid-thought when these two buttons are clicked on.
My thought is going to know if it's the monthly or the yearly plan and if it's not it's going to happen.
The handler with the correct credentials.
So distant hard luck that open.
Are we passing an object just like the Drene right here and we need to pass the name description and
Amman's.
So I would say name is but cost description is maybe but cost subscription and the amounts is going
to be this are months.
Okay.
So when we click on the subscribe button that is what should happen.
Great.
Let's check this out also to see if it makes any sense.
Let's click on that and look at that.
We have a quote from nine dollars that's close this gets to go to the $99 plan.
And now we have ninety nine dollars right here to pay.
OK.
So that's our broadcast subscription and this is the image we poured in.
So I want us to put hold right here and continue in the very next video.
But just to recap on what we've been doing we have our soaps Qype.
We included the Cdn link for the Strype checkout GNAS and non-strike that you.
We registered this event Knysna which is a click it passes in monthly and passes in the yearly into
the subscriber mid-thought which is right here.
And also scrubland thought is simply making sure that the component is a way that it's on the monthly
plan on the yearly plan setting the correct amount on the correct plan name.
OK.
And then we just opened the Hadleigh as usual just like we have in the documentation right here.
So let's continue building on this in the very next episode.