Our next step is obviously to be able to get the user credentials and then pass it to our Strype API
which is going to return to us a token.
OK.
So we should click on this right now.
It looks like we need to fill in the email field.
OK.
But we already have an authenticated user and we collected his e-mail and we verify this e-mail right.
So why don't we preview this email for the user.
Our head of answers tribe and I'm going to show you why we are doing the custom rather than the simple
because the simple it's automatically just going to create this modem with the email feud and everything.
But we the customer like we are doing now we can profundo custom use our e-mail.
So let's go ahead or subscribe that let that be.
And indeed we're going to pass in a property called e-mail and this pope is going to simply read the
authenticated users e-mails.
So let's just say of us and then we'll get the e-mail.
OK then who are straight view components.
We need to restart that.
So right here I'm going to save props and this will be Himmelman right down at the bottom when we are
opening the handler what we can do is set an email property which is going to be Koetsu this the Himmelman.
OK.
So that's the sort of Vasa refresh.
Click on the yellow line.
And now we have the email automatically filled in right here.
So we just need to use US quilted card information and then we can pay.
Right.
So now if we fill in these credentials I naturally click on eBay it's going to get the talken for us
because what we want to do is transform this car and this field this field into our token and then we're
going to charge that so can actually use a of cash.
So this method right here is going to be in charge of the callback once the token is acquired from Strype
API.
OK.
So remember we need to get took on and then we get the idea.
So this is what are going to do right here.
We're going to make an API request Lovell.
But for now let's just console that lock.
So can I.
So you understand what we've been doing on the square.
So I'm gonna open up my console refresh this
get my console right there and then we're going to create a monthly subscription so that it's going
to open up more than we're going to put in a press conference try putting any date in the future and
then putting any CC number.
So it's going to make that IPO request to try get a token and then it's going to Peyster token right
here.
So that said we're getting toucans successfully from Strype this Treptow can actually represent a token
that is passed in here into almost lover Kashima.
So when we pass this token lovers are automatically going to call the strypes server again.
And then it's going to touch the user.
OK.
So looks like for us to charge a user or unsubscribe into a new subscription we need to pass in the
name of the subscription plan just like we're having it here right here.
So if it's monthly We need to Lavo it's one fee or if it's yearly When it's it's all over it's yearly
and that's it.
And then we need to pass in the striped sugar.
OK.
So why don't we do this let's just do this in a really fast way let's just import Agios from XOs.
Right.
And then we're going to make that excuse post request.
So exhausted post and would simply call and subscribe and point I wanted to pass in the data.
We're going to pass in Strypes or can and is going to be tokened of ID.
And we also note pass in the plan which is going to be destock plan y.
But then it's not going to work that way.
And I promise you that I'm just going to show you right here.
Okay.
So let's just we make this request like this.
I'll head over to my Web site.
Create that thought.
So it's a route and it's a post it subscribe.
I will just use a closure right here and just return request on.
OK.
So let's try Shrader as soon as we receive a token from Strype we're going to make that exist post a
question that end point and passed in the To.
And the plan.
OK.
So let's make that request refresh right here off and frustratedly see the results from the server let's
actually subscribe to that and get the response we can so that Lauck response.
OK.
Now let's refresh and make sure we make that request.
OK so Scratchie early plan pass in effect credit card pass in a future date and passing efficiency.
Okay be Strype creates that or can it makes that API request to our backend server and then we have
the dates of return.
Remember we have returning requests.
All right.
But look at what's happening.
We're just passing in the Strype took on what happened to the plan.
It means we are plan our plan is not truly reaching the server.
And this is simply of javascript right here because we are in this object.
And then we have a method inside a nested object and then we are trying to reference this.
And this can no longer refresh to view.
OK so we can't get into the instance if we code this right here.
So what we're going to do is we're going to make a little trick and that's this right here we're going
to see window that stripe line equals monthly All window the stripe plan accordingly.
OK so we're going to save it on the global when the objects are there we can access it from anywhere.
And then when we strip save it under global window what we're going to do right here is for the plan
we're going to see we know the straight line should be what is passed into this plan property.
Okay.
So this is simply a problem of accessibility we can assess the view instance from a nested mid-thought
inside the nested object.
OK.
So this should get us to Strype plan.
Let's reset our browser refresh and then let's get a new plan pass in a really current and future dates
and pay.
And there we have the dates are and our data now have the monthly plan because we quicken the monthly
right.
So let's walk back and remember how the resubscribed use us to our plan.
Easy as milk we simply call off user create a new subscription and this subscription will be called
the request plan.
So for us monthly plan then we're going to pass in my plan.
It was a yearly plan we are also going to pass in yearly plan and we're also going to pass in the same
request plan as a second parameter.
And we're going to call the crew yet Smith thought and we're going to pass in request Strype token.
OK.
So look at this.
We're just doing exactly what was in the Lavoe documentation nothing strange.
OK.
So we have this new subscription thought and the first parameter here is the name of the subscription
the way we want to see it in our database.
The second parameter here is the name of the subscription on our stripe dashboard.
So on our stripe dashboard we've named it as monthly or yearly and in our database we want to see it
as monthly or yearly.
So that's why we passed with BREASTPLATE-MAKER and we Crestline right here.
And then for Quitman thought we need to pass in the so can and just like we did with our XOs we are
passing in stride.
So can I say the key right here and that's how we assess in the choir here.
OK.
So once this is Dawn why don't we simply return it.
So return this.
And I think this is going to return to us the subscription that they use I was just subscribed to.
OK.
So let's go ahead and try this.
And actually this is going to create a new subscription in our database.
And it's also going to create a new subscription on our Strype dash board.
OK.
So I just thought of something right now.
Let me just repayed right here.
So PSP or Sun Cincom and I'm going to get all the users.
Yeah.
And thought so I'm using this e-mail as my test account.
But actually I already have a stripe plan on my dashboard where I was testing some stuff.
So all I want to do is actually change the e-mail.
So use of course but carriers use are for us and would simply update the e-mail to be something else.
So maybe klutzy friends.
My mail the com and save the e-mail.
OK.
So I think we're good to go for a refresh now.
And we click on subscribe.
OK we have that in your e-mail.
So if everything was well we should have a stripe subscription now or stripe dashboard how much of a
new subscription in our database so a spouse in a credit card plus under fake month of expiration.
Plus in the fake CVC and pay OK it's made that EPA request which made the request to Lovelle cashier
lover cache's making an EPA request to the back and Stripes.
And any time soon we should have a response.
Great.
We have a successful response.
OK.
So look at the data.
We have a response right here which contains the strypes subscription in our database.
So let's reset our stripe dashboard.
So if you check out our Strype dashboard right here in the Where We have a Pieman just now right here.
OK.
So we have a new payment right here of nine point nine dollars which is what we just did.
OK then if we check out on our database using thinka if you get used up and we get subscriptions we
just go that this user has a new subscription and the subscription is a monthly one that we just set
up right now.
And if you look at the data is actually just right now.
OK.
So we are actually successfully subscribing use us to plans in our application but then we don't want
to do it like this right.
It's kind of sapi having a wildfire fire with this methode and then making a request with view and waiting
for a long time before receiving a request response.
OK but we're going to tackle these in the very next video.
Thank you so much and see you then.