OK guys Soie come back.
So in the last week you were able to set up our ship and we know it's Walk-In but now I want to do one
little bit of subscriptions test because we're going to be introducing the concept of premium lessons
in our application.
Okay.
That's the whole point of having subscriptions right.
So I have a simple subscription sized class right here.
And I recently created that in my future so I have a new subscriptions.
And what are you going to do when he's running in a couple of test and before ads really start wanting
to us like us to talk about something.
First of all we want to have some premium lessons.
So if a lesson is premium then the user should not be able to watch it if he does not have a subscription.
OK.
That's the first thing.
The second thing is we want to run tests meaning we would have to subscribe or use and stripe or cashier
what it does is that it takes the users information then it makes an API call to stripe and then subsequently
use our plan and then it comes back.
And if anything more successful than in our subscribers to use or to plan on our database.
Okay.
So Strype knows he subscribed and then our database also knows the use of subscribers birds when we
get sustained what we want to do is we don't want to make an API call we do on level because we have
to communicate with our database.
So suply I want us to talk about how to fake the stripe subscription in the future.
Okay.
So for that I'm going to be switching my thought on this last called feek subscription.
All fixups quite.
And what is Smethurst going to do is it's going to get the authenticated use user or any use other we
pass in right here and then it's going to subscribe that user to our plan.
Okay but remember when it's scrunchies that we're playing on the strypes of I'm talking about level
Kashin when cashier subscribes on a user to a plan on the stripes of rock it will now see that the tools
that you use are on the plan for that user on our database.
So we have this subscriptions class and the user has a subscription relationship with the subscriptions
class or the model.
And when we want to create a subscription for Yousaf we could use that so we can see use our subscription
subscriptions and we can call the create method.
OK.
So remember I understand this because in our billable trades right here which I will use our classes
using we can search for subscription.
This has many subscription class so it has to be sufficient therefore to create a new subscription for
a user.
We just need to call these subscriptions creators and then we can pass in the details for that subscription
like the name which could be yearly and maybe the stripe Id know for us to know exactly what happens.
I would just open up.
Was on Team.
We have one user with a subscription so just get the user or just pack use for us.
And this first user has a subscription.
OK.
Because we subscribe to a subscription in the last week or saw just get on subscriptions.
So we should be using you.
OK.
And now if you out his subscription it has a name.
It has a stripe ID.
So right here we need to pass in a fake stripe ID.
So lets just see fake straight Reiji remember its just a string.
And then we need to pass in the straight line.
So remember we are just fixing this so that we dont need to communicate with our stripes or some striped
lawn.
And this is going to be the year plan.
Okay.
And then the quantity would be one.
And I think thats all we need.
OK so now let's create a basic test and this test is going to be for example public function and its
use without a plan can watch free lessons walking for example.
But what I want us to do here is together use on and we do this by saying factually creates and will
create for use of class and right here we just see this fake socks wipe and we pass in they use all.
So right here we are going to date them use our subscribed and the prompter here would be yearly.
OK.
So what they are doing is we are creating a new user.
This is our testing environment.
And then what software they use lots of these fake plan and then we are going to call the use or subscribe
to mid-thought and passing the little plan and this method will simply check the use I subscribe to
this plan.
OK.
So we get to exit's incorrect here.
B you need fuel to do this test.
Okay.
So let's run that and now we see true.
OK.
So Lavoe cashier is checking to see if they use I subscribe to the plan and it stays true.
So in our test we can now use this method to subscribe to use a terrific plan and then run our tests
to make sure that if you subscribe to can watch a video or he subscribed he can watch a video.
So that's what points again.
First we have to fake subscriptions so that we don't have to call Strype all the time.
So we have a fixed drive method fake subscriber method and this method takes in the user and then it
creates a subscription for the user.
And this is exactly what Lavoe cache does behind the scenes.
But first level caching is when you communicate with Strype which you don't want.
So not just in the moment we do want to get restrung So we have a fixups quite meathook and its subscribers
are used to a fixed line and we can now warn our test.
OK.
So thanks so much.
Let's it one some stats concerning fake and free lessons in the very next episode.