OK next step we want to be able to check if the Czar has a plan and then we won't be debating him to
the white page if he doesn't.
All we to permit him to watch here is if it's free.
OK.
So first of all we need to include the concept of having premium license therefore for this that will
not change to say something else.
So we'll be testing a use of we got a.
Cannot watch premium license.
OK.
So that's the test that we are going to be writing.
So first of all we need some lessons.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to help you use our test to include the concept of premium lessons.
So create a treat for the lesson class on your Christmas thought.
And in this methode I'm going to pass in a key called premium and I've said this to one.
OK.
So we're going to have a database full call premium.
And then if this field is one then the lesson is premium.
So next I'm going to pull this out for the moment then we're going to make a GET request to the end
point for the user to actually watch the video.
OK.
So basically what we want is if the user does not subscribe to our plan we were directing him to the
SUBSCRIBE page so he can subscribe to one.
But evidence do you use I subscribe to plan then we simply allow him watch the lesson.
OK.
So future cop outs are we have this get speech where we want to use or to watch the series.
So what are we going to do is we're going to visit this route right here and we're going to pass in
this lesson.
OK.
So this should be a lesson right here for descriptive purposes and we need to pass in less lesson series
Boston to SLOC and then for the lesson right here in Lassan ID.
So when we make it get requests to this lesson which is a premium one would assert something.
So I would assert that the use always redirects at that so that you use ours.
Actually we don't take that to the source quite beach.
OK.
So the by page remember is on gets and points where we see the subscription form.
So subscribe to some sites.
OK.
So that's what we want to happen.
Let's just try this out to see what we have not so far.
So let's run this.
We need to add to that last OK.
We haven't that sees or lessons has no on premium.
OK.
Obviously so would have the much or create lessons to a bow and we're going to create a premium color
so say so.
And I want this to be a boolean and I'll call this preview and I'll just set this by default to be zero.
OK.
So run these again and half expect that there is.
And this is actually what we got so we read the log in page.
So we need to lock the user in before we try to recede.
Lesson for this.
Right.
So we're going to see this seen us use on.
So would love this user name for this testing session.
OK let's run that again.
Now we have a video response that's good to read it's not reader.
I started school.
So in our control we are not with damage and to use lots of the SUBSCRIBE page.
So let's go on with that B and right here this is what she was controul at the show less than I thought.
So watch series controller at the show lesson method.
Simply read debates.
It returns that view.
So what are you going to do is check if the authenticated user has our current plan.
So we'll see if you use.
And we haven't subscribed to non-menthol at that level because she gives to us.
That's actually just check the billable trade to make sure.
So if research subscribed.
So it's called subscribe to plan.
OK.
So what series if the US use or subscribe to plan then we can let him watch the series.
So we could check here if they got use or not subscribe to our plan then we need to redirect him so
we turn redirect.
And this would be to the SUBSCRIBE page.
OK.
So we're just checking if the user has a plan if he doesn't have a plan.
We will direct him to the beach and we can maybe add a flush procedure or something like that.
But tonight let's run that test.
OK we have a 500.
Looks like we're having an error or let's just about exception handling to see that error.
OK.
Run that again.
And we are having the last two few arguments passed to frosh and use us to plan.
OK let's check out what the method needs to seized.
I mean if those tribal areas if they subscribe to one of the given lines we need to pass in all the
plans that we want to use or do we want to check if the user is subscribed to.
OK.
So basically we passing on the plan.
So for example in the southeast or you a method way here we can pass in an array and stop monthly and
yearly.
OK.
So we want to check the use I subscribe to either monthly or yearly plan.
So let's run this again.
And now we have a successful test meaning that user is not subscribed to any plan.
And then he said automatically we make that to the subsequent beach.
OK.
So that is working in the very nature we what we're trying to do what we are going to do is we're going
to subscribe the user to our plan using Orphic subscribe method and then we going to assert that these
days actually go the speech and he can watch it.
OK.
So thank you so much and see you then.