One math test before we move on I want us to assert that a user on the planet can actually watch any
sorts of video whether it's real or it's real.
So what can it create a new test for that and that test is going to see us use our on any plan kid watch
all lessons our kids.
So what do we need for the stress we need to use.
We need a lesson which is preview.
We also need a lesson which is free and we need to log in news or some just get a copy of this suit
right there.
And next we need to make a request to the premium lesson.
I would also make a request to the freelance so to get this.
But remember we want this user to actually have a subscription so we're going to fake the subscription.
So we're going to call this fake subscriber and pass in the user object.
OK.
So this week subtribe is such a this me thought that we created a couple of lessons ago which is going
to fake a subscription for our user.
OK.
So this is what we have.
We have a user and we have two lessons.
One is premium and one is free and it'll be lots of different series but it doesn't really matter.
Then we also locked in the zone and then we subscribe that user to plan which is the yearly plan and
then we actually try to visit the pre-meal lesson and what you do is assert that when we try to visit
a premium lesson with the use of our subscribers we should actually visit the watch that made the.
Meaning that the user can watch it.
And when we try to visit a free lesson the user should also be able to watch it make sense.
Let's go ahead and one that says between it foods or to the SEST OK great we have a direct pass because
we already took care of that in our control.
But right now we're very sure that no matter what plan a user is on he can watch Will lessons he can
watch free lessons as well but without a plan cannot watch him lessons he can only watch free lessons
and in case he wants to assess the lesson he's automatically redirected to the SUBSCRIBE beach so he
can get a subscription.