Next step we've included a Boolean field into this table so it only makes sense structurally updates
are a form for creating the lessons and updating lessons so that we can actually change a particular
lesson from free to premium.
OK.
So first of all head over to my lessons class and right here I'm going to set this to be called that
you are false because we want our lesson to be by default.
In case we don't want it to be a premium.
OK.
So next step looks like in our data we need premium we such a force by default.
We need a checkbox field so I'm going to head over to or from and have consistently duplicate this form
go pull this out.
And for now we're going to do with a simple checkbox I will bind the model to be of course to premium.
OK.
So automatically once you said that it's going to send the data to form which means an eye level site
would also be receiving that in this right here because we are in the complete lesson object.
OK so let's save that to a browser refresh.
Click on the Edit button and there we have our checkbox right there.
OK.
So we're going to actually set up a label right here and this is going to see premium and we'll call
it lesson that freemium right here.
OK.
So refresh click on click and edit lesson.
And when you click on these we have premium.
And automatically it's going to go that field in our database.
OK.
So this is what we want close this kid a new lesson.
Automatically such a premium for us.
OK.
So this looks like it works as expected.
The Shikata request when we make that Ajax request to create a lesson it's to past the lesson objects
which means nobody is receiving that field.
Also a good lesson does the same thing.
So we could go.
So next day is to checkout our lessons controller and look at what we have.
So let's head over to or create lesson.
So it's so surprising request all meaning it's going to persist that they are paid less.
And he's also passing in requests all OK.
Looks great.
Some lesson as a premium lesson and then see what we get because I have all of this see that top and
automatically offset the premium to false.
OK.
So I added this.
So this is true.
Cephalexin.
And then click on that.
And once we get the response from the server we see that is systematically set premium to 1.
Ok means this is a premium lesson.