Our current subscription process is working.
But this is not the best because our user has to wait and we don't even inform him that he's waiting.
Meanwhile there's a complete It's a long process of API calls going on behind the scenes.
So what we're going to do is we're going to change this implementation a little bit.
So that's the use of with no what he's waiting for.
And the user would naturally receive an indication that what he's waiting for was successful or something
like that.
OK.
So let's go ahead and poorly.
ST.
OLPHERTS.
From sweet arm hurt and right here where we are actually making the EPA request before the EPA request
would allow the use of something and the alert would simply have sex off police we weren't we subscribe
you to our plan.
OK.
And another option I want to ask here is Bateson's false.
So the usual no we don't expect him to perform any actions and immediately this is displayed the Jews
request is going to fire to complete the subscription process with our level back end and as soon as
that is complete I also want to notify the user of something.
So right here you're going to have this and the text is going to be successful not quite and I'm going
to move this Bateson's false option and I'm going to put in an icon which is going to be success.
OK.
And since our street looks like Regis we promise this we can see that then.
Meaning when the user clicks on the Confirm But so then we can do something.
So for example we want to refresh the page or maybe redirect the user to the less who was trying to
watch before he was redirected to this page.
OK.
So let's just start by saying window location equals here.
So basically how this is going to walk.
Yes.
When the user receives the token from Strype it's magically going to display this message to the user.
And it's going to be like a mood altering the user to wait and then it's going to fire the existing
requests and wants us to post request we're going to have this success this displayed.
And as soon as the user clicks on the button it refresh the page for him.
And while it's refreshing the page.
OK.
So the mirror on my end came on watch that we watched a genius next stop to subscribe and point in our
browser.
So I'm going to visit the luggin and then I'm going to subscribe putting cards e-tolls month of expiration
CBC number and click on the button and like we defined once that API requests or strike client is done
we have a token.
And we see this notification message and it actually tells the user to wait and now that the request
was successfully made to our server we have this successfully subscribed message back from our server.
And we can click on the OK button and automatically it refreshes the page.
OK.
So it looks like everything is working like we expect it to.
And this makes a lot more sense.
OK.
So why don't we do this when there is a is the page you should actually change that the other is shown
by here.
So why don't we use this page to show the subscription of the user.
And maybe he can change his subscription or cancel your subscription.
In case he wants to.