OK next step once you get the possibility of the use or to actually change his plan.
Yeah it's going to be really crappy if the user cannot wait for monthly plans.
The yearly plan done great if it's not interested.
OK.
So that's what we're going to be taking care of in this lesson.
And as usual caution makes this a real priest.
OK so for this lesson I behind the scenes prepared this form and this form is simply a soulmates which
is our select right here and we can either select the monthly or the yearly plan and we just click on
change plan and then we are going to send it our controller.
So for now it doesn't do anything we can empower it to actually communicate with the controller.
OK.
So we can look at the user ask Koreans Blunt let me take you right into the code in my poor father lead
that Ph.D. inside one of the top beams.
I have a form for now it doesn't stop me to anywhere.
It actually has a few four sets off detection.
And then right here we need to ECOs to use US Poulin.
OK.
So first of all since I'm going to be agreeno these US plan something I knew to take off is I want to
autoload the use of subscriptions.
OK.
So right here I'm going to set up a protected with property and this is going to autoload the subscriptions
relationship.
OK.
Save that.
And in my profile I can do stuff like this.
I think I can just Ecorse the authenticated user and I'll get subscriptions and I'll get the first and
I'll get the name of the subscription.
Now you need to understand something Lavoe cashier provides the possibility for users to have more cheaper
subscriptions because you can have an application where a user can be subscribed to maybe vigils and
subscribe to maybe music in stand so you can have multiple subscription so you use.
So in this case we are up about around the fact that the user can have just one subscription at a time.
That's why we keep saying first such that we know or we make sure that the user can subscribe to just
one subscription and we always get the first right to our king.
So in this case we get the first subscription and we get the name of the subscription or we just plead
to the user.
OK then right here we need to submit this to somewhere.
So I'm going to just set up a route and I'm going to call these subscriptions to change.
OK.
Which is going to be a post and that when we click on this is going to submit the form value.
So I'm going to head over to my web ph be and I'm going to quit this route.
So I'm going to change this to a post and it's going to go to subscription change and subscriptions
control or change my thought and I'll give this a name which is going to be exactly what I coded in
my profile that made that pitch be.
So I'm going to copy this idea save it and I'll paste it right here.
OK.
So that's our world.
We need to create this change method in a subscription schedule.
So that's what I'm going to do.
Function change and it's going to be a pause right.
So first of all the first thing we want to check to make sure that we actually bodging a controller
is if the request parm that was passed in here is actually a different one.
OK.
So first of all we have to use on.
So let's just use our equals of user and let's just say use up plan course user will get his subscriptions
will get the first call and you get the plan name.
Ok then what you want to do here is check if request plan which is the new plan that you use wants to
change to right here the name of this selects plan and we want to check if the request line is equal
to the use of plan.
OK.
So the current plan or the use is of course a question and then we'll just return they use our back.
We don't want him to change anything if it's the same.
OK.
So the next step we need to call our subscription change process.
This method requires us to get a subscription and then it also requires us to call or swap method.
And we're going to explain what this means.
So first of all they want to do is actually strip out this implementation with Strype plan.
OK.
Even though the name of our plan is the same as the Strype plan.
I want to use a stripe plan so that we actually know this is exactly what we have in our strategy but
so is the plan that you use is on the same plan that we are getting from our view that we are going
to win on ideas of.
Okay then the subscription.
Right here it's 6 in the the plan.
So we're passing use our plan and then we're going to swap it for the new plan that we are getting from
the request.
So if they use our strengths upgrade for months later yearly loveall is going to pass this plan to allow
a cashier and automatically level cashier with calculates what is Judy use our or how much they use
on these to be charged for that are going to succeed and it's going to automatically do that.
OK.
So we use our subscription.
But in the current use up plan.
In this case maybe monthly or yearly and then it's going to swap it out for this plan that was passed
in the request makes sense.
So after this operation let's just return a redirect back ok for now.
OK.
So we get the plan and then we swap out the current plan right here with the new plan that we have for
our funds.
OK so let's go ahead and try this out in Abrazo to see what we get.
So right here we'll just select the Yelp plan because it's safe I said the monthly plan and recoup and
change plan and then sticking a little bit of time because he's communicating with us tripes serve our
change of plan and now we have a response.
So it refreshes and goes back to the speech.
OK.
So it seems your current plan is still monthly.
So let's go ahead to think I get this use on naturally see what is going on.
I'm going to show you right here and I'm just going to get all my users and I'm going to look for the
patch I use only walking the earth right now.
So they use all its name.
So what is happening is if you look at the first subscription for this user.
First of all the name is monthly.
That's why we are seeing monthly right here.
But the plan is yearly.
So this trapline is the name of the plan that we use I subscribe to on our Strype dashboard.
So this is the plan that Strype notes.
And this is simply a name that we give to identify the users plan on our own database.
OK.
So something of a level cache's if we swap out the plan it's going to change the strike plan name right
here.
But the name of the plant itself does not change.
Okay.
So it's a choice if we want to manually upgrade the name of the plan right here or what we can actually
do is change the the way we are to explain this to the user so we can actually display the strike plan
right here which actually makes the name kind of useless birched if you will automatically updates the
name of the plan when they use a subsidy out.
Then you can do that in your control.
Okay.
So if I come back refresh and we check out the plan we see that the Strype plan is yearly.
And then we can switch back to the monthly and if I can change plan.
You say it's taking some time because it's complicated with the tripes service and then it comes back
with a response.
If you check that out it's switched to yearly.
Okay.
So just that simple math thought that actually helps us to actually switch the plan of the user whenever
they use our request.
And for one more thing let's just put a little bit of security for our service right here by saying
validates the request that is coming in.
And I would say the plan is required.
OK.
So that's it for this lesson in the very next one.