Something very important we have to think about is giving these are a possibility to cut teachers.
Right.
So we're going to take care of that in this lesson.
I'm going to head over to my Poffo to bleed the ATP and then the last.
I'm going to create a D so just to display the user are his current card.
Maybe the card brand and the last four digits.
Because that's what a cashier saves into a database when we subscribe to use to our plan.
OK.
So right here we just have an the tech sensor which is going to say your current card and it's going
to escort us to use our card brand.
And we also want to run for the car to last for.
So could have caught last fall.
Here.
OK.
It's just going to give us the last four digits of the cart.
Because separate this with a car loan and you could wrap all of this in a batch so spun that batch that
batch primary.
OK.
So that's what we have try to visit the profile page and refresh and check all the settings we have.
MasterCard 44 44 right here.
OK.
So I me change the settings to cut the tolls.
And we know what we want to have is such a view component.
Is just going to pop open a model for us to update to use our Skadi tools.
And basically the use cards those models is exactly what we use to collect the critical details.
And we're going to simply duplicate it and then edited to fit our needs.
So in our components we're going to open the Strype view component copy everything in it and then we're
going to create a new component that we're going to call up the card that few and I'm going to pay study
and then in my apt Yes I'm going to register new components.
And this is going to use the TAC view update card and require in the newly created components or date
card that view.
OK.
So in our profile the blade BHB we're going to mnze the component right here.
Maybe in the tech center we could have the view of the card and with a view of the card.
And also we want this to take in the image of the user.
So would pass in this program which simply echoes the authenticated users email.
OK.
And then one last thing in ablate head which I subscribe that bleed and I'm going to copy the script
right here because we're going to be using this exact same model.
So we're going to need Strype check out.
And then in the newly created component I'm going to pull out one of the buttons because we just need
one.
And the one we're going to be using is simply an A C or D the tools.
OK.
And this is no longer going to be a subscriber and I thought I'm going to create a new method called
updates.
So when the user clicks on that button it's going to call updates.
Then right here for a wall mounted PP-ASEL a public key local auto.
And we can actually change what we are doing like you're so right here.
Call is not going to be subscribing is going to be caught up that something like that.
OK.
So incrementally let's change this.
So here we have our pop e-mail which we are really passing in and wait on it.
But we no longer need mnze on a plan.
We also do not need the subscribed metho.
So all we need is an update to my thoughts so I'll change this to a page and I'll pull out the plan
and I'm going to remove all of these statements right here.
OK.
We no longer do no plans.
So does the candidate open.
We don't need to pass in the amounts and we can literally change the Pono label.
OK.
So what is displayed in the panel.
And this is going to be a date card GITTOES.
OK.
So for now let's just check out what we have in the question and then we're going to move on.
So I'll refresh this page.
This is the use of our page Vicent according to stop and there we have it.
We have MasterCard.
And we can click on the card details and it automatically opens.
These are all.
And you see the Pango info right here is on the cards.
OK.
So we can also turn off allow Remember me to force bypassing the allow remember me.
How can such a false and refresh update cards Ito's.
And we have just the form exacts form the to update these cards to make sense right.
So let's work on what happens when we get a token from Strype our post to be to card of the 8 which
we're going to create.
We don't need no plan.
So we just passing this tried to control my Lovell's server with the token and then we are going to
change this text to please read where we update you on your card details.
OK.
And then right here we're going to see success really update at card details.
So in our levels what we need to quit this end point so head over to my web ph be and I'm going to create
the endpoint just right here so round balls and it's going to be caught on the edge.
And for now I'm just going to put this in a close up for simplicity and what it's going to do is is
going to get that too.
Can we just request token or actually striped or can because this is what we are passing in from our
form.
So strato can and we get it and who just get the user which is the authenticated user.
Then some people writes us with an update card misthought which takes in the tokenized card from.
OK.
And once that's done we can return response which could be a J CRN and I can just say OK and automatically
there will be 200.
Which means successful.
OK.
So you know what component if it's successful they said see this message.
And I think everything is wired up to work as expected.
So let's try it out.
Head over to my form refresh cards details click on that up the model and I'm going to change these
two.
These are PESCHARDT and I'll click on ID cards Ito's.
OK so we have our updates message and successfully updates the card we have successfully updated card
details in a model that is displayed to us.
So if you click on OK it's going to refresh this page.
And if you check out our cards it shows it has been changed to Visa off 242 and that's exactly the same
thing that happened on our stripe dashboard.