Okay the next couple of years are just going to be some little clean up stuff we need to do in our application.
Nothing serious but little changes that are really going to help us optimize stuff like that.
So the first thing I want to do is head over to my notes see that view and I'm going to change the information
we have now.
It was a very good learning experience.
Bert I don't think it's the best if we want to use it in production.
So I'm going to move the template and we installed sweet alerts after he created this component.
So I'm just going to get Strega alert for him straight on Lerche OK.
And whenever this notification is triggered this event is triggered.
I'm simply going to see street alerts and the message is going to be payload the message therefore we
no longer need our computer properties.
We also do not need this data.
I'm not complaining just barged down to a subscription.
So once a component is created it subscribes to that event and everything events in its fight or the
event is triggered or fired.
We have our suit on the displacer message.
OK so my love makes is running compiled all the assets.
Let me refresh the page.
It a recipe.
And if I click on Save lesson we have street right here.
That's the lesson of the to successfully isolates the same lessons and each successfully.
So we just reached out on those actions implementation with street light which I think it's great.
OK so that's the first thing that we've cleaned up.
The next thing I want to clean is my web ph be in the last lesson for the card update.
We actually put it in occlusions So let's just go ahead and create our controller for this so we can
call it a big cock controller.
So here we are CRN make controller or actually we should we can put this in its own method in the peripherals
controller.
So why don't I cut this out and then I'm going to remove disclosure and see if you'd use the PUFAs controller.
It's a big card meathook.
OK.
So hello to my PUFAs controller and who create the OBD-II Cardman thought and I'll paste in what I had
from the occlusal exactly the same thing.
OK.
So far a little validation we can say this validates the request object and passing Strype token is
required like that.
OK so we've moved that mid-thought into our control or on our web the PSP looks clean right now.
And the one thing I want to clean up is in my profound lead that BHB I want to make sure that only the
authenticated user can view this in his profile.
So meaning every use I can receive and that they use a spoofer so they know the user's ID or they use
a user name right.
Bert the form for the team don't use those details which is this right here should only be displayed
if the authenticated users to one visit in his profile.
So I'm going to see if say orthe user ID equals user ID and I'm going to put it right here because this
profile we are posting to use up just like you or we would suspect for our work here.
Our country our first one then we have the authenticated user.
So we checked to make sure that the user is the one we will follow up and we can then display the details
for the use of two or bts details like that.
OK.
So there we go.
And I think that is going to actually clean up a lot of areas for example maybe a user visiting another
person's will cannot get it right and right in this form.
Another thing I want to update is the subscriptions for the use are so right though at the bottom if
these others will have a plan this is going to give us an error.
OK.
So what we could do is actually wrap this in an instrument that says if you use your subscription first
then and if now we can paste this in like this.
OK.
So this is OK.
And it's not going to make multiple queries to our database because we are already eagerly loading the
subscriptions for the user.
But what we could do is actually save all of this subscription in available and we just simply assess
it.
So I'm just going to put subscription right here and in my control right here when you're passing the
use on the series I'm going to pass with subscription and right at the top before the beginning of this
block where the user can view his Digital's.
I'm going to say open ph B and close BHB and subscription is going to be called to the authenticated
users first subscription.
OK.
So right down here I would check if the user has a subscription then display this.
So rather than all of these will just switch this out to subscription try plan.
OK then we can have an else and then and if and right here we'll just see span that barge.
That barge danger which is just going to say no plan.
Okay.
Makes sense.
This is following security such that the user would be able to see this message if there is no subscription
for him.
OK.
And we can do exactly the same thing write down here.
So if the user those have a cot we don't want to even display the form.
OK so I'll just cut this out and see if I can use.
And for example cardboard and which means it's not now.
I can base this in and we can do exactly the same check with the link right here.
So the link to see the cards Ito's we can see if Arthur use our card brand and if no paystub.
OK so would only see the card details being when the user has a card.
I would also see the details to of the card only if the user actually has a card makes sense.
So these are little things that are going to prevent an altercation.
And I think that's pretty good so far.
So thank you so much and see you in the next video.