The next clean up exercise we're going to Javie subtly cleaning up the way we send to confront emotively
use.
For now what happens is when they use a wrench registar it's going to send the email at the moment but
we want to switch out the source knowledge to use Lovell's queuing system.
OK.
So that this email is actually sent.
Behind the scenes and the user can navigate the Web site normally.
Have a great user experience rather than waiting for an email to be sent.
So head over to confirm your email which is on the label and the only thing we need to do to cure this
is to implemented the shoe Q interface so increments should queue and automatically every job that implements
this interface is going to be added to the queue by Lavoe But first we also need to go into all of that
in the file and updates the queue settings.
So for example now our queue drag racing which means it's going to process the queue in real time.
Boy you want to do is set up database as the queue driver and in case you want to know all the drivers
we have in a queue that BHB we have seen which is the default.
We have database beanstalks which are going to be using on our server.
We have obscurus ready.
And we also know which means you're just put off the queue.
OK so we set that up and the last thing we need to do such and it sets off a huge table.
Right.
So we resign.
Q table.
And what this will do is that it's just going to create a migration and this migration is going to create
a table called jobs.
So if you had to create jobs table which is the newly created migration it would simply put information
about the cube such that every time we put something to a queue it's going to save your job.
And then we can process it in real time.
OK.
So for now since we've already queued that email Let's go ahead and try to register a new user so slash
registar and then placing some dummy data dummy data that come in the password when you click on registar.
We have this error that sees this too of you know phone hacking.
So that's because we didn't migrate all our database so that we have the QS table right there but actually
it shows us that we are actually trying to put in something into the database rather than sending that
e-mail.
OK so I'm just going to go back to my told me no one ph be other than my great squinch my great chups
stable.
And then I'm going to log out and then I'm going to try to register a new user.
OK.
So I'm just going to see fake user fake user that comb passing a password.
Click on registar and we see in a second less than the second we received a response.
Welcome to dashboard.
OK.
So that's what we want.
But that email has not been sent.
Right.
So what you want to do right now is starts Ah-Q Walker.
So if I say get our son Q Walk it's not way to process every single job that is in our jobs table.
OK.
So right here you see it has processed and sent the Confirm your e-mail.
So we check out Milorad right now we can actually see that that e-mail was sent.
But as I said the moment M. Trop is down for maintenance but I promise you that Amy's husband said.
And by the time you're trying this out Shirley milksop will be out of Minturn's.
OK.
So that's how we can actually use QS in our application every single process that is going to take a
while before completing it can just implement should queue and automatically it's going to cure that
to the dieter is.