The next thing I want to clean up is my authentication.
For example if you visit the log in page right now we actually have the log form but and if we actually
log in we're going to receive the status or key response from our controller.
So that's actually clean up.
So in my log in the blade the Pietropoli I'm going to reload everything and I'm simply going to copy
everything in the register that let that be pasted right there and then I'm going to edit this form
such that it fits for luggin.
So right here whether that scene or you have an account we can see no accounts yet.
And we're going to see registar then the register button is going to see logging and then move onto
the top.
We don't need that great on going forward.
We have a password we have an e-mail.
We don't need a name and we need this form to submit to the logging post route.
And they should see luggin working.
So that's basically what we need to create a log in page refresh.
There we go that's trying to log in.
It's going to give us the stutterers.
OK.
So in log in control or in the authenticates at Mithal this is a method that is in charge of responding
to the user once he successfully logs in.
OK.
So whether than sending a response that starts with is we are going to check if the request is an AJAX.
So checking the question Ajax is very easy with love or because love will provide us with this.
Just my thought which allows us to check if the cost was an AJAX.
So if it was on Ajax would respond with this.
And if not we'll just return redirect home.
OK.
So let's head over to base and we click on the luggin and we see where we direct that to the home page
rather than the Ajax response.