Let's have a deep dive into lava's default authentication system and see how we can completely customize
it to our needs if need be Lavoe ships end with this son come on Peachtree or sun make off.
And what this is going to do is come for a complete authentication system for us.
It really comes with the default control us in our app controllers directory and we have an after a
tree that contains the controllers for these authentication system but that command is going to ship
in or publish some of views for authentication.
And it's also going to register the routes.
Let's run this command and if we check out what there are true right now we have a new home controller.
And then in our resources there actually we have a new off directory where we have the registar password
resets views.
Now interestingly you know a Watchfire who had a watch went to BHB.
We have a new route set that has been registered for us if we check this out and also to understand
what is going on we have a log in and just page and we can go ahead and we just start a new account.
And by the way behind the scenes are naturally sets up my database and my grid that we choose my data
tray I have this database all the skill lights and then my dad in Wi-Fi and referencing the secure light
connection.
OK.
So let's reach out on your accounts and once that process we redirect redirected to the home page let's
go ahead and divide into this system to understand exactly what level is doing for us behind the scenes.
First of all I'm going to start by checking out my loggin and registar buttons that are on the home
page now so resources will come the blade that should be closed down and right here we have an IF block
and this is checking if the route logging exists and if it exists then it's going to show us the home.
Now if the user has authenticated and it's going to show us logging in and we just type all if the user
is not authenticated and by the way this is a new blade directive that came in the late days of the
Apple iPhone 4.
How do we know this world is registar.
I mean why we don't have it.
Let's check out our Web the PSP.
So we have this new routes that was placed right here by our son C'mon.
And we also have this one that was released.
I'd love to know the routes that have been registered in application level provides us with pecera Arsen
route list and we can see the routes that we have in our web that HP is responsible for all of these
routes that we see right here.
And of course that includes the logging route right here.
That's why you know Welkom that lead ph be.
We now have this if block displaying because we registered with the US command now issue head back to
Boston viscid the home page.
Sure enough we have him here because right now this is the part of this of check that is successful.
That's the first spot.
Let's watch all of pitch be and let's dive a little bit into these routes metho the first place to start
is actually to check out the for sale right.
What about searching in phosphates off the pitch.
So here we're going to have the Fassett off the pitch that comes with Lovelle.
And check out that method.
We actually have the routes mid-thought on it as a static method.
And this is because the container and makes the routes I cross because that's the class that spans the
stream and it calls the off method.
Now vitiates going to return to us an instance of the router.
So let's head over to the router that BHB and that should be an illuminated routing you alter that ph.
And we can search if the reason off mid-thought there.
There you go.
That's an afterthought.
And this really starts the typical authentication Wild's for an application.
Now if you check out it registers a logging route and it points that to off logging controller sure
logging form and it gives it the name of logging.
Same with the post.
Same with a logo which is a.
It also we just asked for the registration process and for the password resets therefore behind the
scenes love is simply stream a bunch of rules for us.
And that's why we actually have them here when we try to display them.
If we actually try to do something you should never do any obligations like try to delete the rights
that have been registered in our vendor directory.
Give that a safe and notice that in our web the HP we still have this of are being called and we actually
get all the routes we discover that the routes that we register are just the four that we are truly
know when you start an application.
Now our head of back to my vendor directory and make sure I can do what I did and then if we run come
on again.
There we go.
I wrote back the falafel is simply registering this right behind the scenes for us and Lovelle will
automatically overwrite this routes in case we redefine them.
OK.
So if you want to actually change your application visit the register page.
You can do that.
Let's try one of those.
Let's say we wanted to change the register routes and we want our user to want to visit another page
for example the registrar that blade the HP in the authentication I mean directory or whatever however
you want to customize it you can get around and you redefine the slush registar.
And you just call back for now.
And this is automatically going to re write the register about that Lovegood defined in the vendor directory.
Therefore let's just say return a string registar user right here and we'll get about all of us so I'll
just log in so we can actually visit that page.
So we try to visit the register and point yeah we get that page and that's because we actually have
to make sure this is defined after all.
All right this is going to be different.
And then we write it.
OK.
So quick refresh again.
There we go we have just our user therefore for whatever reason in your application if you want to change
the view or whatever you do when the Vistar you reaches the register out you can go ahead and find it
just after this right here.
Or you can completely pull this out if you want and redefine all the methods.
So Lovelle gives us the possibility to customize that next thing.
What actually happens behind the scenes for our registration.
Let's check out the routes we have here.
We have Forget logging which points to logging control actually logging form.
We also have a post which points to logging control at logging my thought.
So let's go ahead and try to find those methods if we head over to our logging control which is in a
tree in our control directory.
Let's check if we have a show log in form and we don't.
We also do not have a log in my thought.
So what the hell is going on behind the scenes.
I'm going to hit pause for now and in the very next video we're going to deep dive into the logging
controller.