OK we almost went crazy in the last video when we actually try to find the show log in my thought and
the log in method and we couldn't find it.
So let's dive and see what it is doing for us.
Again behind the scenes we have a logging controller and labo uses this concept of Single Responsibility
traits which means defining traits and let me just have one responsibility.
You see this everywhere around Lavo.
So in this case level defiance and authenticates you use US traits and these traits is coming from the
foundation of authenticates years.
So it's coming from a vendor directory and we can actually go ahead and see what this Treach looks like.
So head over to the definition and if we try to check out our show log in for mid-thought.
There we have it.
And I will log in my thought.
We actually have it right here also.
So our show logging method simply returns to the view of that logging just like we like spec right.
Therefore if you want to overrides which you view is that when a user visits the logging route all you
can do is actually copy this my thought Head over to your logging controller base that mid-thought in
and override what you want.
Therefore if I want to actually return the string I can have return logging page as easy as that for
head of about my boss or try to visit the log in page.
Now I have log in page because I just overrode that method.
This is the power of customization that I will give to us.
So that's how we can actually change the view.
What about the logging process completely.
Let's go to it in authenticates use our let's find a log in my thought and Hatchet handle and log in
requests to the application.
Looks like we're calling a validates data log in my thought and you need to notice something.
Level is always going to be referencing math thoughts or our Kadhim hooks where we can actually completely
customize the functionality of our application.
So here we have logging and it's calling a valid data logging method on the streets.
Therefore let's find that validate lock in my thought and this validate logging method is actually in
charge of validating the data we receive from our front end.
And if you want to completely override the validate log in for your logging process maybe making sure
that the use of all writes the e-mail and the password two times or the e-mail and his name or whatever
you want to do during the logging process validation.
This is where you go to a game.
Another thing we need to notice is the value data logging method is calling this username method again
on the street.
So let's get to the username method and what this simply Dorsets returns a string.
Right.
So get the logging username to be used by the controller.
You might find yourself in situations where you want to actually log into use I use in the form or the
user name rather than the email therefore may be in your phone and you're receiving the name of the
user not necessarily the e-mail.
What do you do you need to do is override this username mid-thought and that's it you're done.
Love is going to automatically take care of every other thing.
That's why I and see this in action if I capitis had to watch my logging controller based that in and
let's say we want to actually log in the user using the user's name in the database would come here
and would return the name of that field and that its name in case it was foun then you're going to put
in phone when Casey was username you're going to put in username.
So laureate's every level to authenticate the user using the name.
So we need to pass in the name field from our front and I'll head over to my log in the late and right
down here where we have e-mail.
I'm going to change days to name.
So the type is going to be text.
The idea is going to be name name is going to be name and this is very important because if you check
out you authenticated users validate log in my thought it's passing in the username right here as the
validation.
Therefore it wants the name key and it should be a required stream.
Right.
In the case where was written in e-mail it was actually and that right here.
So we want to make sure we pass in the name.
And we also want to display validation for the name and name also also the name and all of that.
And and I think that sets up OK so we are passing the name and the password to loveall and we still
love all the user name to use.
It's not the email but the name field in the database.
So if you're not comfortable with it you can just go ahead and set up a name name also.
And finally your name right here.
OK.
So let's go ahead and try this out in a.
So your name.
I'm going to put in the username and password and click on the luggin button and we redirect that to
our home page it just walks as easy as that.
So in less than a few seconds we've been able to change our authentication system for email based to
name based just by overwriting one single method one single method.
And that is the method.
OK.
So username name we change that name.
That's it.
How cool is this.
Lovell gives us an extensive customization possibility once we know how everything works behind the
scenes.
OK so let's continue with our luggin method.
There is still a lot of customization that level provides for us in our authenticators our streets.
We have the validation for that username and this is going to validate our day.
Up next we have Lavoe trying to take care of too many logging attempts.
So if the password was wrong or the email was wrong more than three times or four times depending on
how you configure the loveliest automatically going to lock out the user and say oh no you can't log
in to you or maybe past AP or of one to two minutes.
Then where does the logging process actually happen.
Right here if this attempt to log in then send logging.
Response.
OK.
So attempt to log in is a method on the streets.
What does it do.
It cost the gov't which means you can actually customize the guard because we are referencing a method.
So right down here we have got the guts to be used to record indication levels to gives us the possibility
of overwriting this and it attempts to authenticate the user passing in these credentials and a boolean
whether they remember field was in the request or not.
OK.
So this credentials is another method.
And what it does is it gets the username.
So in case you were using an e-mail we get the e-mail.
And in case you are using a name field like we are doing now it's going to get the name field and then
it gets the password.
Now we tried to authenticate the user returns or true or false.
And then when log in my thought it checks if that operation was successful if we're successful we have
a send log in response Meffert that takes care of responding to this situation.
That's had a watch or send log in response.
And what does this do.
Generates a session for the user class or the log in or times in case they use or try to authenticate
himself more than once and then it calls and authenticated method or process requests and process and
authenticate a user or it redirects the user to the In turn the page or redirect the user to the redirect
path method.
So lovely simply calling methods on these traits and it's giving us an extensive possibility of cost
or my xine.
Now what if you want to maybe redirect the user to the welcome page after logging.
This is a method that level just calling and this is the method.
It's simply empty right here.
It means we can put in whatever we want to put in right there.
So let's copy this and try to rewrite it.
So what do we want.
Once you redirect the user to the home page right.
So return a redirect to the home page.
So rather than slash home we are going to redirect the user to to the main page of the Web site after
the user is locked in.
OK.
Now this is simply how we can customize.
In case you had an AJAX logging then Reicher you be returning and Ajax response in case you want to
fry the user or send an email.
This is where you're going to be doing it in this authenticates method.
And what happens in authenticates use ostrich.
I will send log in response is when to check if this method is null.
If it's not all it means you've actually customized didn't put something in it then it's going to code
and methods or if it's not it's simply going to return a reader to that and turn the page.
Ok so maybe you whether use I was going to before he was locked out and sent to the authentication page
all it's going to code is redirect part method and this way the record method actually gives us the
possibility of customizing what happens when the user is locked in.
So if you don't want to use this you can actually configure this.
So let's go ahead and see how this authenticated method operates in a logging controller.
We need to put in that request so let's go ahead and make sure nothing breaks by using the request at
the top and we expect that when we successfully log in we are redirect to the home page.
Right.
Let's go ahead and try to sort our lug out.
Go to the log in page and now we are no longer logging in with e-mail because we have our word that
mid-thought And now we are logging in with our name and the password.
So luggin There we go.
We'll redirect that to the home route rather than the home page.
OK.
So to the front of our website rather than the home page that's how easy it is to customize.
What happens when the user is locked in.
So this is the send log in response.
This is what happens when the user successfully locks in.
We can customize that by simply writing the authenticated method.
Now finally before we hit pause on this video are we close for the day.
Let's check out what happens when the user fails to authenticate himself.
It's going through incremental logging that terms that if this if statement feels right so that again
returned a boolean which is false it's going to incremental logging items.
And of course they're testing care by Lovaas Troxel floggings APHC which is also a trait that level
this by default and it's going to return what ever is in the Sinfield log in response method.
Let's visit the Sinfield logging response mid-thought and we can customize this method if we want to.
So if I want to control what happens when the user feels to log in I can simply override this mid-thought
in my Consuela the for my logging controller or paystub in and when the user fails to log in I'm going
to return a stream that says logging field let me log out and head to my log in page 14 the credentials
and I'm going to put in the fake password.
Click on the luggin button.
Yeah.
And there we go we have log in field as easy as that.
Just one Meffert lover gives us the possibility of overwriting the whole system.
Therefore anything you want to do you cannot do.
In case you want to control what happens when there's a field log in response you can simply define
a method in your logging controller in case you want to control what happens when you use ice authenticator.
You can also use a method in case you want to change what system or what database you want to use to
authenticate the user.
You can also do that.
So Lavoe gives us the possibility of completely customizing our system in whatever way we want.
OK so this must have been the longest video in the series.
We're going to hit pause for a moment and consignor and the very next video.