Let's talk a little bit about the Register's controller and our password resets controller and then
you'll be done with default controller customization.
So if I want my poetry or Sun Radley's C'mon we have this roster when you start to go to the controller
like the show registration form and the registar thoughts.
But then if we visit that control just like we had with our logging if research for the show registration
for Mithal we don't have it.
Same thing with the registar method.
So same thing.
This Mithal Sahid and BNR traits.
So let's visit that Treach retry to visit our show registration for my thought.
Sure enough it returns the expected view.
The view that we see when we try to register a new user.
And then if we also check out the registar thought he actually does everything behind the scenes concerning
registration.
Let's go ahead and talk a little bit about Avijit stomach phone.
For us it also validated my thought and this method received the request as an array and then validated.
And this way they are Mithal the search really in our registar controller right down at the bottom.
Therefore if you want to customize what is validated when you're registering a new user maybe you want
to customize and make sure that the height is a number of the hightest required under each and all of
that.
This is where you're going to do that.
OK.
So just simply putting a new radiation field and automatically going to call that as we see in our registar
method.
Next thing Lavoe utterly rigid starts to use right here.
I'm just going to break this down to a simple line so you actually understand what is happening.
So Lovell's firing an event and that event is the really start event and that event is actually coming
form eliminate of events we just start and it's passing a user into that event.
And this user is coming from calling the Creator thought on this class on the streets and that create
these receiving all of the request data.
Now discreate My thought is actually from our control.
If we visited D'Errico receives an array of all the requests they are and then it creates a new user.
Therefore if you want to customize what is passed into the database when they use ice created this is
where you're going to go to.
Right.
So I should create mid-thought and Lavallee optical going to call that behind the scenes.
Next thing it saves the user isn't available and it passes to these new registar events.
Right so an event is fire.
That's the first hook that we have if we want to customize our system.
Therefore if you want to do something like send a welcome email which we're going to be doing very soon
then we simply need to listen to this particular event and that's it.
Lovely is automatically going to fire that event.
And all of that event is not going to take action.
OK.
And most of the time in the community we actually listen to people saying I don't want my users to be
locked in.
As soon as they are registered.
Therefore this is where you actually want to come to right because this is a line of code the lover
uses to logging the user.
So it locks in the newly created user right here.
So if you don't want to log in the user simply override this.
We just thought that in this line you might not even wanted to get the event therefore you're just going
to validate the data and then call the Creator mid-thought and then pull out this line completely.
Therefore the use I said I'm going to be authenticates that all locked in automatically.
And then finally what level dosshouse Is it cause of which you stop mid-thought just like the authenticated
method that without logging controller if it doesn't find anything in the way you start mid-thought
which is the case right now it's simply going to redirect the user to mid-thought redirect path.
So you try to visit that redirect path.
My thought is actually in a redirect such rates what is simply going to do is check if redirector method
exists and then it's going to call that.
OK so you can actually create a redirect to metho it right in your register control.
Or you can actually find a way to pour putty in your registers controller.
OK.
So I think Lovelle already comes with that.
There you go.
So we already have this redirector property and you can actually make sure that the users without access
to the home page if you want that's the flexibility that level gives to worse Burts if you want to completely
overwrite what happens when a user asked registar.
Then you need to simply define this when you start method.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to copy this when you start my thought and I'm going to head over
to my registrar's controller and I'm going to override that method.
Therefore when the user is read you start what I want to do is decide on the use of data.
OK so this is what we are going to see when the user is registered and we need to import this request
last of the top.
Now another thing I want to do is actually listen to this event so you understand how it works.
So like I said loveall fires an event which is called a widget event and you can actually listen to
these events and send an e-mail when the user is registered.
Right.
So let's go ahead and just do that in our events.
All right.
We are going to listen to that event.
And how do we listen to that event.
We simply call the events right here.
Eliminate of events and this is the restart event and all we need to do is moppy to all of it's listeners
and we of all of its listeners maybe if you want to send an email and if you want to also upload the
user's avatar to Amazon then you can have different business for the same events.
So in this case we want to send an e-mail right.
So I'm going to set up listeners send welcome e-mail.
OK.
So we don't have this list in our class if we want to a recent event January is going to generate all
the listeners that do not exist yet.
OK.
So we are listening to illuminates of events we you start and I'm writing that because this registar
is coming from illuminate of events where you start and we are telling Lovell every time this event
is fired.
Make sure all of these listeners are caught.
OK so let's generate that in the Petri Aurizon events generate is what we need.
Ok I just one that if we check out our Abdur tree you should have little changes like this looseness
and we have a send welcome email listener.
So it has the Handleman 4.6 in the register event.
Now what we want to do in this which you start event like we said we want to send a mail to the user
who was just registered and we can get that from that event and we can call the send my thought.
And we simply need to know more about that.
We want to send.
We're going to see where you are SAS is going to be the mailable and we can also pass in the user into
this mailable class.
So send an e-mail to the newly created user and that mail should be welcome to our SAS application.
Now we need to use the mail for Slate and since we don't yet have that mailable Let's go ahead and created
Peachtree Arsen make mail.
Welcome to our source and we're going to make sure that we have a markdown view for this.
And it's going to be e-mails start.
Welcome.
OK so that minable husband creature for us therefore in our app directory we have this welcome to assassinate
B A B and it returns the emails that Welkom we Postino the user.
Therefore we can receive the user right here on our sign that are public property so we can have access
to that in our view.
So in our construct or we're going to set this user to the use of we received from our listener.
OK.
So let's viscid that you welcome that Bader Ph be.
And we can have welcome to our Soest up and we can get the user name to customize the e-mail.
And this is going to be the body of your message maybe whatever text welcome.
OK.
So what do we expect to happen.
We expect our registration to take place just as usual but then we expect these registar events to be
Fiat which is being fired right here and we expect all that smart for this event to be fired.
Also to be one note and the handling right here is going to send an e-mail to the newly registered user
which is the welcome to our SAS e-mail.
And we should receive that e-mail and see the contents.
Now if you have any it set up a trap I've set up my mail drop and I'm good to go.
So let's go ahead and we just a new user and see if everything works like we expect and obviously wants
to use naturally receives that e-mail.
This will just start mid-thought should be called in which the controller simply died on the user because
we are each and AMFA.
OK so visit our application visit the registar page registar news or click on the register button.
There we go.
We have we use our Didymos right here just like the specified number we just are on free checkout.
We see our Welcome to our SAS e-mail and if we check it out for an office customized exactly the same
way we wanted it.
Therefore we see how we can integrate completely into Lovell's default system.
Listening to the events calling the appropriate methods whenever we want to and level automatically
takes this takes care of this for us behind the scenes.
OK so before I actually stop this video I want to simply show you how you can also customize the password
resets process.
So if we had to asked to be control us we also have passwords resets control up and we also have up
forgot passwords control controller and we can see it also has a son passwords reset email traits and
we can visit that tree to see what is happening.
Shoaling request form is going to return off the passwords to email and we can customize the page that
they use of views when he wants to reset his password or put in his email by simply copying this my
thought and customizing it in this control or then send a link to the given user.
So send resending email is going to validate the e-mail and then send the reset e-mail.
Now Lavoe uses a book Behind the scenes.
But what this simply does is it has a send reset link and all of this is coming from password booka
that Ph be.
So it has a certain reset link meathook.
And if that option was successful the response we're going to get is a string and that string is equal
to this string right here.
OK.
So right here what level is doing this.
It's comparing the string that we received which is this response is equal to the string that is saved
in this constant.
And if that's true then it's going to call this methodes send reset link response.
And if that was not true it means it was failed then it's going to call the send we said Lingfield response.
Now this said said Link response just like any other method that we've been told that we we can customize
it however we want maybe you want to send an S M S or do whatever you want.
Once the reset link is send to the use of e-mail you can do that right here.
Burts if it's actually filled then this is the method you want to customize send resettling field response
and now by default Lavoe simply returns to use or back with the arrows.
OK.
But you can do whatever you want.
Use or anything.
This is why you can customize that.
OK.
And then lover also has this reset password controller.
And like you see it also uses a reset password.
Behind the scenes and you can customize this with like to property to redirect the user to maybe the
dashboard page as soon as the password was successfully reset.
And in this reset password street you can override whatever you need to reset.
So reset form is also going to return this view right.
You'll be the token and IMHO you can customize that if you want by simply copying it into the reset
password control lock.
And this is the reset process.
And the same thing Lovelle validates that we have the correct Ditto's to reset our password and then
he uses that verruca again cause the reset mid-thought which returns a string and is saved in a response.
So if that string is to password that resets if you receive discloser check it out passwords that reset
then this condition is going to be called.
Ok means we had a successful password reset.
Then we are going to call the send reset response my thought and if it was not successful then it's
going to call this field method.
And again if you want to customize this you can just copy this into your controller and that's it.
OK.
Very very easy.
And if you also want to customize what happens when they use or does it not correctly reset his password.
This is where you're going to do that.
So everything works very seamlessly with Flavell.
OK.
You can customize the system completely just like we have reviewed.
Thank you so much for watching this video up to this point I'm so grateful you did.
I hope you learned a lot.
Let's talk more about customization in Lavoe in the next video.