Let's talk about service providers.
No this is one of the coffee yourself Lavoe and I think its importance comes immediately after the importance
of the application that be in Lavoe Lamma provides a great deal of customization using service providers.
And this is truly a space Ostrum be able to do whatever we want to do.
As soon as the application is booter.
So let's have a watch or service provider.
Now also provide us access and phone support service provider and they might or might not implement
this boat and registar methods.
Now let's talk a little bit about the difference between these two during the boot process.
Loveall registar its service providers and the service providers are the ones that are registered in
the can be Abda.
So right here it's going to go to the provide the army and when you each and every one of these providers.
How does it do that.
It goes through each and every one of those service providers and he calls the Register method.
So for example if we choose any of the providers for example the precursory will light up we can see
each Register method and basically what it does is it stream the money Jayanta the content or the contract
into the container area the manager and the factory and all of that good stuff.
OK.
Lavoe doing its boot sequence is going to call only the registar method on each and every one of the
providers that I specified in the app that HP provide us away.
Next thing after the process has been completed its now when to call the boots method on each and every
one of those providers.
Therefore this broadcast service provider can have a book metod.
And this is going to be called by Lavoe after the application has been booted.
So after Illuminatus finished running.
So if you have a service provider like the US-Soviet provider that is empty and provided to us by Lavo
if you weren't buying anything of the container registar My thought is where you're going to do it.
OK.
So put things into the container in the register mid-thought but never try to get things out of the
container because remember the Register method is called when loveall is still in the process of registering
service providers.
Therefore you might be getting something out of the container or it's not yet been put into the onto
or by Lovelle.
OK.
So make sure you're only putting it into the container in the register provider.
So for you to see this revisit what ever provider by Lovelle for example the database server provider
it's only going to be doing registration.
OK that's all it's going to do.
It's never going to try to get something out of the container.
If you check out the first system service provider and you also go through each region stomack thought
it is putting things into the container.
OK.
Registering things into the container.
It's not getting anything out.
So if you have customer service providers or you want to use service providers like our service provider
make sure you're not getting things out of the container here but you're putting things in.
And then once lobert is completely set it's going to cost each and every Booch method of each and every
provider.
So for example this is where you can maybe get an out of the container or the database or whatever you
want to get out of the container.
OK so but my thought after Lavoe husband Richard thumb I thought during the registration process of
Lovelle registering the service providers.
OK.
Now how could we use a service provider.
Remember we have the odd vaults mid-thought.
I'm going to use this as an example.
So right here we have this odd thought and like we saw in our forsakes us it's calling to offer him
a thought in the vaults are the Ph be.
And what often thought is doing is simply registering some votes.
Right.
So this is one of the things we can do in our service provider.
We can register a new route.
For example if we dont want to dynamically or put those routes in the weather THP or if those regions
routes are supposed to be registered only after a condition is met then the service provider is a very
good place to go.
We also have a voucher provider that will provide for us.
So if it has anything to do with routes then you can do it in the boot method of the vaults of each
provider if it has anything to do with broadcasting.
Then maybe the podcast available writer is a good place to register.
For example the book Kasserine provider actually registers some routes in its Meffert.
OK just like we're talking about.
So why don't we have some form with service providers to see how we can actually generate our own and
customize it however we like.
I'm going to create a new provider.
Peachtree Arsen make provider and most of the time when you're creating a new provider it would be because
you want to handle a particular thing in your application.
So let's say we want to communicate with our medium API and we need to obviously pulling the tree clients.
So here it is squarehead and one composer require this and then looks like for us to use this we need
a new instance of the middle class and we need to pass in these conventions.
So where is the best place for us to put this.
The controller might be a first place to start but then every time you want to use medium you're going
to see a new medium which is not bad but then emerging.
Of this class of multiple times over and over and your application Meanwhile you can just all Lavoe
to give it to you.
So the best place to put this would be into a secret service provider or you can also put it in the
observational either but just so we learn how to create our own service providers.
We can create a medium service provider plus indiscreet and shelves all over any time we want an instance
of medium though this and give it to us.
OK.
Let's go ahead and do that make provide medium service provider.
Now that's great for us.
If we had a virtual app there to provide us we have these medium service provider that has been created
for us.
And remember our book mid-thought is after our registration and our register method is doing registration.
Therefore what we can do is buying something into the container.
So by is simply telling Lavoe take this on for us whenever we want it give it back to us OK.
We want to store an instance of medium in our container and we want Lavo to give it to us every time
we need it rather than creating a new instance like 10 times in our control.
So Ali dishcloths so use this glass right here and during the registration process and when I told.
OK since you are registering things and you're calling these registar methode for my medical service
provider please keep a major pitch be as DK and what you're going to be keeping is an instance of major.
And we need to pass in the credentials.
OK.
Because for instance this loss we need some credentials.
And naturally if you type Hynds this in any control of our dependency indiction Lovelle would understand
that.
But then if you're putting in some predations then you need to talk about how to bind this into the
container.
And what we are doing here with team level whenever we ask for these key Give us this.
And how do we get our credentials since we learned in the last lesson that we can actually have a lower
cost configuration files.
Let's create a new config file just for our medium API.
So fix Losh made you appear to be.
And right here we just need to return an array right.
So return and I'm going to copy these configurations away from this page and I'm going to be studying.
OK.
So this is the configuration.
And you can go ahead and use.
Ian wiitwd you get this form that the NV file if you wish.
And in your service provider you just need to call config right.
So config.
Get rid of them and that's it.
It's going to give us whatever is returned from that medium to we file.
OK.
So we are putting the configuration we are selling novel every time we need mid-June.
Just give us a new instance with this configuration.
Now during the boot process squinched rigid studies.
And every time an application where we need this level is going to give it to us let's go ahead and
request this in our web ph and see what we get.
That's died down.
I will call it a resolve help on my father level gives us.
And this is simply to enable that thing that we put into the container with this name.
We want it right now.
OK.
So we can see it in a very well.
Let me just show you right here so we can see in stands of medium equals resolve.
This from the county you know.
So this is the instance of major ones.
And then let's die down that stands right here.
So if I refresh my home page yeah we get an error.
And I think you should know why we get this error because we've created our service provider but we
haven't told Lavo to load this service provider right.
So for us it's all our vote.
This is one of the service providers we want you to load.
We need to have a watch or a configuration file until Lavo when you log in so people write us.
Make sure you load the medium service provider.
OK.
So quick refresh again.
There we go.
We have an instance of me do this.
It's also Lavoe to also boot or call the Register method and the register mid-thought binds that key
to our container.
And this is the instance that we are asking for in our web ph.
Now what can we do in the boot method.
Like I said the Bush method is after everything has happened.
Therefore we can't ask for anything from the container.
For example in this case let's call it a container and ask for Duvall's up.
And this actually is the currency in our application which extends to currency you know and it's actually
saved us on our property on our service provider.
OK.
So this album make lots of simply means to get the router or you can actually use the resolve method
that we're using in the web that we.
And since we have a router sure enough we have to get Mithal and we can define or get mid-thought to
define a new route and we can see this new is for me June and we can pass in a closure to be executed
when we visit that vault.
So let's just return made you home for example a stream.
OK.
So we just start a new route in a boot method.
Now let's reset that home.
So minge you and sure enough we have medium home therefore just in a nutshell we can see that level
provides us a really easy way to hook into the system by creating service providers.
So you can customize a lot of things.
For example you can even replace the router in a custom World Service it you can replace the podcasting
driver if you want to implement your own just by creating a service provider and binding a key and every
time Lavoe is requested for their kids to return whatever is in the closure so we can see how Lavoe
gives us really easy customization and service providers.
We have a bunch more thought of register mid-thought we can register whatever we want to register into
the container and in our boots thought whatever we want to do maybe send an email when the particular
wallet is visited or do whatever we want.
We can do that in the boot method.
OK so that's how we play along with service providers to customize Lavoe.