Let's to go out middleware and the extensive power it gives us for customization.
Now if you're not used to me the way in love with me the web is simply a really easy way for us to hook
into the request lifecycle.
For example if we have an ongoing request and the user is maybe trained to assess a particular entity
we could check if the user has a meter to assess that and see during the request lifecycle and maybe
do something and let the user assess it or simply block the users access.
Now let's get into a kernel that ph B which is in our HP directory or namespace and a lot of arrays
right here that give us an extensive power of customization.
We're going to go to each and every one of this.
So like we said middleware are going to run during the requests lifecycle.
For example Visby right here specifies only the way that we're going to run on every single request.
Lavoe checks on maintenance with a check from it and unsmooth middleware and you can also define your
own custom middleware.
For example if you want to check if the person making the request is of a particular email to give him
different responsibilities or different permissions then you can do that.
You can do whatever you want with middleware OK if you want to check if the request is coming from a
particular IP or particular Kountry middleware is where you can go to.
OK.
So first of all we have this.
And if you have a particular piece of code that you want to run on every single request this is where
you're going to be just like me the way this is where you're going to put your middleware and loveall
is going to run this me to wear on every single request.
If you have middleware that you want to want only on those set of routes on the set of requests therefore
you just need to create a custom middleware group and then you place the group right here and then you
register your middleware in it's we're going to talk about that in a moment.
Now if you want me the way that you want you want only on particular specified routes then what middleware
is where you have to go to.
OK now we're going to go through each and every one of these areas.
And for us to actually do that effectively Let's go ahead and create our own custom middleware by 1
mph.
We recently made aware and we'll give the name of AMI to wear to the test.
Okay.
You can be whatever you want and automatically label is going to save me to wear in our app.
It's to be made aware directory.
There we go.
Now every middleware is just going to be a class with a handle method and that's it.
OK.
And all you need to do is define your code right here and then make sure at the end you return next
which is some sort of way of telling the request lifecycle to continue because the is going to kill
this code and you can either stop the request or let it continue.
OK but you don't want to leave the request lifecycle hanging.
So what are we going to be doing.
We are going to really start this middleware to run on every single request and I'm going to show you
how that works.
And for us to know that it's actually running we are going to hijack the request.
And at this very point we are going to set a session.
OK.
So session flash and we are going to be flashing a test key and we're going to see the first key from
decimeter where it's going to be the value.
OK I'll save that and I'm going to register this me the way and like we said in our commodity the HP
if you want to wear one on every single request you have to put it in this middleware array.
So let's go ahead and we just right there streamed the app that's to be made aware SEST class.
The one we just created.
OK.
So lovely squinch one day on every request.
Now how do we know Lavell has actually done that piece of code and assertion has been flushed.
Let's have a watch or whether picture me and right here we have a request right and we're going to simply
do a little died down right here of a session value to see if we have that value.
So session get test OK.
So if that was actually wrong when we bring this request to the home page that session should be flashed
as a test and we should actually see it there.
OK.
So let's go ahead and make this request.
There we go.
We have this desk from the test middleware which means that middleware was actually one.
Let's go to the next level we have this group or this way for me the way that I went to run on every
single request.
Now let's go to the next.
It talks about Raud middleware groups.
OK.
And think of this as simply a way to run me the way on a particular set of routes or requests.
For example we have two groups that can by default with Lovelle a web group and an API group.
OK.
And like we see right here the web group is going to actually be all the requests or routes that we
match in our web.
So any vote that you register in your web the Peachtree is really going to be under this group.
Right.
And we see in this group we have to wear a check for the CSR with token.
We have me the way that study session and all that for the API.
We don't have all of these middleware but we have the weather Tromso and registar bindings.
Now when you see a string like this rather than a class it means Lovelle is referencing the middleware
register registered in another group which is bindings group and the will grow.
OK.
So for example if we want that all the middleware on the web to be registered in API then we're simply
going to add the web stream right here.
OK but we're not going to be doing that.
So we are going to be testing out the API group and whether we're going to be doing is removing this
registration that we registered under the global me to where I will put it on the API group.
It means every single request from this group is going to have this middleware run right and it also
means every single request from this group is not going to have them in the way run.
So let's go ahead and try to make this request.
There we go.
We have not.
Why.
Because our middle window is when you start on the API.
But we are trying to dumb the session on the vaults that is when you start on the web.
So let's head over to API that ph.
And then more about the different wildfires and a little bit and we're going to start a new route and
it's going to be a get and we'll simply visit the homeworld for this group pass in a close up.
And here again to date them something.
Now if you try to diatom a session value right here we wouldn't be able to do that right.
Because remember you know it cannot be this API group does not have access to the session only the web
has access.
Therefore what head of what you are what test middleware and modified a little what we want to do is
rather than setting a session that's just died on the stream right here.
OK so if we make a request and this me the ways are truly one of the requests we intercepted and the
die and would see this key.
OK.
Therefore our API that BHB route is when you start we don't even need to have anything right here because
this closure won't even be executed.
So let's try to reset that route and remember everything in the API that Peachtree is wrapped with the
API prefix.
OK so in the Wizard of Oz we see test key form test middleware.
Let's go ahead and fight a little LESKIE from test middleware API routes.
Save one that request again.
There we go test key from test me to where I was because we have this diagram right here.
OK.
So that works as expected.
Now I'm going to pull this out and let's talk about our last group are we right here.
And this is the middleware that we want to run only on particular routes.
OK.
So if we want to actually specify a middleware just for one route or two Truthout then you have to register
our custom made aware right.
So I'm going to pull out our cost on the way here and I'm going to register it.
And in this case you notice you have to give a name to the middleware.
OK because you need to identify this middleware from your outfight.
OK so how do we use this me the way in this case I'll head over to my web that me and we can use this
one for any our go because we're going to specifying it on a particular route.
So I'm going to move this and we'll keep the default return head of to my test middleware.
Modify it a little and it's going to be specific routes that is going to be day dawns and how do we
apply this me to where let's say we wanted to apply this to where to this route.
We just need to attach this me to where metho at right here.
And lovely so dramatically going to change that and we're giving the name of the middleware in this
case test.
OK.
So any time we visit that route we should see that middle way in action.
And there we go just as easy as that that may be the way it is running on that route.
OK.
So if we pull that out make that request again.
We have the home page but if we let that in make the request sure enough we have what they dump.
OK.
So that's how we can actually customize application with middleware.
Just to recap if you want a middleware that is going to run on every single request then it's going
to be stuck in here.
But if you want a the where that is going to run on a particular route group then you need to put it
on the other for that route go up.
OK.
And if you want a middle way that you can attach on particular routes only then this is where you are
going to register your middleware.
That's what about having a cost on route groups.
I want us to really take a deep dive into the sun what this world groups are and how they are truly
phone in the web PH BE and API Ph be.
So I'm going to hit pause on this video right here and in the very next video we're going to talk about
that extensively.