Let's talk about middleway groups like Chrisette middleware groups are simply middleway that run on
a particular set of routes.
OK so you can define a route and you can make sure that vote belongs to a group of other routes and
then you can one particular middleware on all of that group of wealths.
For example if I take it your web Dogpatch be you can register a route group in a close vote and inside
this group you can go ahead and define routes of particular similarity and dissimilarity can be a prefix
that you want to put in and you can use the Lovell's prefix mid-thought or you can once attach a middleware
to all of these routes and you can also use the Lavoe me to when my thought love gives us this extensibility
therefore you can create your own Castano middleware groups that we are going to be talking about in
this video loveall ships in which to do for me to wear groups and in our Kanada ph we we can see those
groups.
The first is the Web Globe and The second is the API group the web middleware is applied to all vowels
in the group called weap which are the routes that are registered in the web that should be and the
API group is applied to all routes in a group called API which are those in the API that Ph be.
And I'm going to show you how this happens if you head over to our World Service Provider.
We discover that we have a map mid-thought And this map mid-thought registrars some routes for us because
the map API WILESMITH thought and the map where Prout's method and recheck the map worthwhile.
I thought what it does is it registers some routes and what precisely and it imports all of the worlds
from web that we register them and make sure that it applies a namespace of this namespace which is
here.
So up S2P control us.
And also it wraps all of those routes in Amida where weap.
OK.
So the middleware group is called WEP and it wraps all of the routes in the web the PH BE WITH THIS
middleware.
Same thing with the API Roths.
It really starts a group force in all of the valves from API ph sets a namespace which is this namespace
and applies the middleware API group on that group of routes.
OK.
And it also prefixes API right.
So if you actually want that to customize what is the prefix right here.
You can change it to whatever you want.
OK so maybe API version one or to whatever you want.
OK then you can also customize the namespace of all your API calls.
For example if you want that every single vote that is in the API that we talk to automatically get
control us from an API directory.
All you need to do is apply slash API right here and rather than at SGP control as it's going to go
up it's to be control us API directory.
OK how cool is that level gives us a very large possibility to customize even at this level.
Now let's talk about something fun.
How do we create our own group.
We just start with our own middleware and how do we change everything together.
Let's do that access right now.
Say you have a group of administrators in your application and you want administrators to see a particular
page or a particular action button and you don't want no administrators to be able to see this.
How do you change that up.
Let's quit accustom me to where for this khichri arson make me aware administrates up and this is a
functionality that you might have in almost all of your applications.
So let's go ahead and build it I'll head over to the administrator of the Ph.D. and now in this middleware
what we're going to be doing is checking if the current user is an administrator so if not we'll do
something.
And if they use an administrator we'll do something else.
OK so.
So looks like we need a user base of education system would make this fast with Peachtree or sun make
us.
And that's it.
You have an indication system for us.
Now what are we going to be doing this me the way.
Like we discussed in the previous videos we can't actually create with an administrator or table or
an admin Boullion field in our users table to deploy I mean if they use Eisenman is.
But if you have a very simple application where you have only one or two administrators the best way
to go is to civil administrator e-mails in and away in your configuration file.
Very easy.
And then in your middle where you just need to check if the current user is an administrator.
I will show you how I do this in my Abdur ph be able to find a custom rakli which is going to be for
the administrators of this application.
And what I'm simply going to be doing is actually saving the emails.
So right here I'm going to see administrators and all this to an array and or pictures in country at
France the comb as the only administrator.
OK.
So any administrators in your location will be registered on that is key.
Then in my administration aware what I'm suddenly going to do is check if in a way of user email and
we're checking if it's in the of config mid-thought and we'll get the app that administrators.
OK.
So if it's in that RV then let's just for the moment die down.
You are an administrator.
OK.
Then if the user is not an administrator then would down.
You do not have access.
OK.
So that's what I mean the where does it checks if the Korean user is an administrator or by checking
if his email is among the ones that are registered in our config Abdur administrators.
OK then what we could do right here is make sure that the user is authenticated by saying if Jack then
run days and else would date them slogan.
OK.
So check if they use this authenticator.
If not they don't place logging.
But if they use ice authenticates a check if his email is in the config array of administrators.
And if that is the case Didymos you're an administrator.
If not then they don't.
You do not have access.
Now whether we register our middle.
Let's head over to Iraq in order Ph we like we said we want to quit our own middleware group that is
going to have all the valves really start for administrators therefore let's go ahead and take care
of this right in this group we are going to create our own group and I'll call that mean for now and
in here we need to really stop all the middleware that are going to be wrong for this group of words.
First of all I would like to pulling all the Middle Way to start.
On the other where because we are going to be using cookies starting the slash checking the CSR if token
sharing arose from session and all of that good stuff.
OK.
And then we want to also really start what costs are made aware right here.
So up at TGP middleware and that will be administrates our class.
That's it.
So we start a new admin middleware group and uses all the middleware groups in Web.
And it also has a custom administrates all the way.
Now if we head over to our Web page be we can do something like this.
It's a group and everything inside here is going to be for the administrators and we can map middleware
and we'll pass in Middleware group right here which is going to be at me that we just we just start
right now and we can also add a prefix of maybe at mean and let's just try this out.
Let's really start a route which is going to be a get and I'll just register the home route and right
here we're just going to die.
Don't what was reached.
OK so.
So we have a router middleware group called admin or we just read you start and we are applying it to
this world group right here.
And we've prefixed all routes on that at vulgo using our admin key right here.
And therefore we have SLAs are being registered me to where right now.
And let's go ahead and try to visit it if we visit.
I mean yeah we have police log in let's visit luggin.
All right.
Registar so with when you start and you use up and by the way behind the scenes are ready to kind of
setting up my database and stuff like that.
OK.
And registering with the email that I specified as an administrator.
And yeah I'm locked in.
So let's reset.
Admin right now.
And it says you are an administrator.
OK if I head over to my config and I change this e-mail in some way such that this user is no longer
on the streets so sure enough we have the correct message that says you do not have access.
But if you look at say that terrorists or with that be you can see it.
It looks a little bit messy.
And if you have a thousand of hundred votes that are for the admin middleware group and stockinette
in Sika is really going to make your far too messy.
But we can do better.
Right.
Level has taught us how to customize.
So let's go ahead.
Lots of people write up and we are going to define our own routes group.
And this is going to be this map.
I mean WILESMITH.
OK let's just use the convention.
Now we need to create that method.
So protect it.
So how is this going to be with registar prefix just like we're doing right now.
And that refix would be admin and the middleware is going to be the mean middleware and the namespace.
Let's see if we want to control us to be in the admin directory so would concatenate this namespace
which is the default namespace to administrates us namespace and the group that we're going to specify
is from.
I mean that PH BE therefore in our route's directory slosh.
I mean that Peachtree.
OK so let's create the file routes.
Slash I mean that should be OK.
So right here this is where we are going to define all of our routes.
Therefore this route that we have right here I'm going to pull it out and now it's going to be in our
administrates or the Peachtree farm.
OK.
Now we have a very clean space to really start all routes that have to do with administrators.
And if we were fresh We should have the same results.
We do therefore let's go ahead and make sure this user is an administrator or safe run that request.
And we still have exactly the same results.
OK.
So that's perfectly great.
We've learned how we can create our own custom middleware groups or our own custom routes fairs where
we can have king which start vaulting application.
So just a week up in Canada Ph.D. you start a new admin middleware group and we are registering all
of the middleware on the Web plus our own plus our own custom administrates or middleware.
Ponder this middleware group and in our overall service provider we have a new set of what's called
admin and we're going to place them in the Admin the pitch.
And we are applying that me to where to all of those routes in that group.
So hopefully you understood what we did in this lesson.
I hope it goes a long way to mega-projects to look clean and professional.
I'm going to catch you in the next video where we talk about something more fun.
Thank you.