Let's talk about custom exception handling in Lovelle Lovelle gives us an extensive possibility of handling
different Arolsen application in any way we want.
OK so let's go ahead and see how this works.
We're going to be working on a very very simple basic idea and that's the idea of maybe passing an idea
into your own finding to use or without ID and are putting the Jason.
OK.
And if we don't find an ID we're going to handle the custom arrows that will give us.
So let's go ahead and do this.
First of all I'm going to simply set up a database connection and I'm going to use Esco like in this
case and in my directory database I'm going to create a new database that obscure like fire.
That's it.
I'm set therefore I can run Peachtree and my great and they have tables.
And we think I'm going to simply generate some dummy users factory and I'll get 50 use us on our basis
that my data is OK.
So we have used us now in our database.
Let's have a watch or web that we found and modified this a little.
So when the use of the home page what we want to return is an instance of user and would find that using
an ID parameter that passed in the request.
So right here let's get illuminated at CTP request.
And what I think that sort of levels Konting I would automatically inject it in and would also get the
ID Parminter from the request.
So we need to accept that in.
OK so viscid the home while passing on ID and would return to you the use of that ID.
Pretty simple.
OK so let's get the idea of one we have the sun.
So it works as expected.
What about an idea that does not exist in the database.
OK.
We have nothing right because clearly we didnt find any use us.
Now we'll switch this to a kind of feel.
And this my thought behind the scenes basically is going to try to find a user because you see cause
to find fault here.
And if it doesn't find a user it's going to try a new model not not found exception and passing some
veto into that exception.
OK.
So let's try this again.
And in this case love automatically gives us the four or four Not Found page.
But what if you wanted to do something different.
What if you wanted to handle this section differently without necessarily seeing a full page one if
you wanted to give a custom Jason response to the user or any different kind of customization you want.
Let's look at how we are going to do that.
First of all all exceptions in our application passed through the hand-luggage ph which is in the up
sections namespace.
And what happens is when we have an exception we can decide to report it.
Maybe loggy send an email or whatever and we can decide to render it into one.
As to the response.
OK.
So every single exception that is strewn like the modern Afon exception goes through here.
Now we can hijack that.
Now we can hijack that exception.
So if we try to phone model my phone exception that's imported from its namespace.
So you eliminate the.
Cohen Mardale not found exception.
And what we can do is Lovell's giving us an instance of the exception here.
So we can say ief exception is an instance of model not found exception then would handle it differently.
Let's just say we return a response Jason and the message hey we couldn't find that user.
So in this random thought every exception is going to be rendered using this parents window but then
we want to check if the exception is of type M'Donald phone exception.
And what we're going to do is send a custom message to the user.
So let's try this out refresh.
There we go.
We have our castanet Jason.
And just like that we are automatically able to handle whatever exception that is strong in lover.
Now you can also do this read not for to be exceptions to render custom for all for page and whatever.
OK so next thing we don't want to always handle everything like this right.
What about the situation where we create our own custom exceptions and told Lavo how to render it.
That's going to be fun right.
That's it.
It's one of the newest features we love 5:25 we can create a new exception and at any instant in application
for example if we use our voices and that main page and you know that page is not available to the public
then you can throw an exception.
Let's create a new exception and to created in my app exceptions class exceptions directory and it's
going to be called Hacker alert exception.
OK.
So hacker alert exception.
So Bluhm ph referral would define the namespace and the name of the class is hacker alert.
Now every custom exception must extend the exception clause and we need to use that right here.
That's basically all we need to define our own custom exceptions.
Now we need to tol'able what you do with this exception and there are two methods that we need to reference
just like in the 130th which references a report Meffert and or when the men thought the report mid-thought
sales Lavo whether it should lock this exception or send an e-mail or or inform the administrator that
this exception was thrown and the render method like ricin tells Lavo how to handle this exception in
the application itself.
So if you're defining a custom exception you need to declare or report mid-thought and the render method
if there is no report.
Or when may fall in love we will not be able to handle these requests.
So let's talk with a random thought and what we are going to be doing is returning a response any time
this session is drawn and we can maybe pass a message.
We have seen hacker.
You've got no luck today.
OK.
Dan anywhere in application like the web that PH BE Let's see you have an admin route and you know this
route is not public and someone tries to assess this right without being authenticated if not check
means the user is not authenticate at all.
No exception.
So this is going to be up exceptions Hocker alert exception.
OK that's it.
So if the user has not authenticated and he's trying to assess this and meanwhile from the you are l
then for this exception.
So let's check this out.
I'm going to try to visit that you know and thinks i'm not logging.
There we have our message and things I'm not locked in.
There we have our message hacker.
You got no luck today.
But what about reporting these airports themselves.
So let's say somebody tried to hack application and we want to automatically Those something or receive
an e-mail or whatever when this exception is thrown when we notice there's a hacker alert.
We simply define our public reports mid-thought and we'll do what ever we want to do.
In this method knowing that level is going to call this method behind the scenes.
OK.
So I'm just going to use my lockless right here and I'm going to lock our Critch call alerts and in
case you want to see the methods that we have available for this log you can head over to logging Lobert
Ph be.
And we have an alert Kriti call that takes a message and an optional array warning naughties info and
all of that some in critical and the message is how car tried to hack us today.
So quick refresh and obviously we have our window method caught by vote but what about the report method.
Let's check out our Lavoe the log file in our storage directory.
And there we have the critical lock hacker tried to hack us today as easy as that.
So if you want to send yourself an e-mail any time this exception is thrown as such then you can go
ahead and do that in your hacker exception alert.
Right.
So this gives us a very extensible possibility of handling errors whether they are not phone to be exceptions
or for arrows or five what we or what ever exception we try to handle we can handle it by either using
a custom exceptions or hijacking the Air Force in our to the pitch.
So same thing goes if you want to send yourself an e-mail any time a user is not phone.
Then right here would be a good place to do it so you can see if the exception is an instance of an
exception.
Send me an e-mail with the idea that was passing or whatever.
OK.
So that was a great job.
Hope you enjoyed it.
See you in the very next lesson.