You're welcome back.
Let's talk about supply an application to our cloud.
Now I want to take some time to talk about why we're going to be using love to forge where we are going
to be using the task that we are using and why not just deploy to distortion ocean without force.
OK.
So 4G is simply a service manager OK.
It's just going to help us money to survive.
There are some staff that are really really hard to do on the server.
By our own.
OK.
For example if we want to deploy it or for server or a server that is money for all we need to do is
push call to get help but then setting this up in the server it's not unnecessarily complicated but
there is a ton of work that you have to take out.
For example you have to set up another get remote on your server and then every time you listen to are
pushed to your guitar then you automatically pull from guitar.
That's what actually does.
But then it promotes that process for us.
The second reason why we want to use for is because management stuff like cron jobs management stuff
like deployment failures management stuff like queues and database instances in a production server
are really really time consuming really really hard to do.
But each automatically does this for us.
OK.
So low aflat a fort or something.
It's a great service I use it day to day and I really really recommend that you use it.
OK.
So for me it's not free.
It has a plan.
But then for the purpose of learning for it and learning how to deploy before she can go ahead and sign
up for the future.
And I think you can try it for about 10 days or so.
So you can actually practice how to deploy an application with fotch.
OK so let's get into it which gives you the possibility of setting up a server with distortion leafnode
zone services that's another.
So you'll need a server provider.
So option is the one they go with.
It has the cheapest Blands is very easy to set up.
The other ones are great but it just depends on your choice.
OK.
So go ahead and set up additional ocean accounts and then on the social accounts you just need to come
to your accounts right here on forward.
And then add distortion.
OK.
So for example if I come to my service providers You see I have a portion of that right there.
So you can also add the note of vulture.
Okay.
So for example if you want to add distortion.
This is what you're going to need.
You're going to put in your plan right here and then it's going to redirect you to additional options
to authenticate for Vulture you just need to add your API credentials and it's going to take care of
that.
Same for Amazon.
So you just need an account with one of these many and you're going to be paying for the service all
over and you're going to be paying on for just to manage the service.
OK.
So I'll head over to the home page and to actually create a new application.
We need to understand the terminology.
So for each simply has the technology of surveillance and sites.
So on that server we can have multiple sites.
So for example if I deploy a news server to the ocean it's going to ask me for the credentials the name
of the server or what size of the way where to deploy it and all of this is going to create a news server
on the ocean.
Then it's going to install everything we need to deploy another application.
So this is what makes it easier when we deploy a lot of application readouts for each.
It becomes very complicated to install everything the level needs but then force does this behind the
scenes for us.
So once you create your server you can see a server listed right here.
So if you get into one of those service.
So for example you have a server for cost and it has all of the sites that contain costs.
So in the server you can see all the sites for that particular server.
So you can create a new site.
So think of a server as well.
What does the ocean provide for you a server and then a new site is simply you know a site.
So if I wanted to deploy different instances of level I can do that.
So in this case we want to deploy maybe you don't need that but cast's dot com.
OK.
Because remember we are actually having a server right here.
You need to go to maybe the ocean to configure the domain name to match the server.
OK.
And then on the ocean you need to set up configurations that would allow subdomain routing like this.
We need to choose the domain which means we'll be this site.
This particular site will be available see the cost to come and then the project type is a novel project
and the web directory is public so we can go ahead on the site.
So right here we have the site provisioning and that's it automatically we have a brand new site with
Lovelle.
OK so if we head over of that site we need to decide how we want to install the site.
OK.
So for example we can pool from guitar or we can create or run your wordpress site.
In this case from.