Come back let's talk about the quick reply button.
This would allow us to deploy our code from top to LA forte just by pushing to get home.
We don't need to maybe come here and get poor because automatically it's going to do that.
So I'm going to put on pre-deploy I every time I push to the muster branch I wanted to deploy my app
to production.
OK.
So this is the dupr script.
This is what happens every time we deploy the application.
For example if I click on this button it's going to execute the script and what it simply does is it's
Sidus into that directory where that project is pooled and then it pulls from all region my start which
means support from top and then it installs all composed dependencies in case there was a new dependency
that they installed and then it runs Peachtree we Arrison migrate.
OK so in case there's all my questions that I need to run it's going to run that makes sense.
So you can edit the script to me to fix your needs or feature what you need.
So this is the script and.
You are just in case you need to hook up Lovelle force in Georgia ploughmen workflow for example if
you're using Trabi CII to run your test before deployment then you can simply tell Trevisa to automatically
make a post request to this endpoints.
And he's going to deploy your app.
Ok so you no longer need to deploy automatically once it's pushed but it's going to deploy metrically
once your tests pass on Travis.
OK.
And then the branch that is supposed to be listened to.
For example we want to always deploy from the master.
So we set up my Starbright.
OK.
So that's basically all we need to actually know.
So the next thing we need to talk about is notifications if you want to receive sluffed deployment integrations
to a particular channel you can enable slow interrogations and Vollmann is very important.
And this is and this is where your environment variables are truly stored.
For example if you want to put in your stripe key everything is going to be here.
OK.
So this is private and also your database credentials are going to be here.
So I'll head over to my.
But cost which means the server itself.
And I'm going to show you the panel that we have right here so we can set up as a search key to S-sh
we can search all my skilled databases for example for this new site that I just created and it creates
a new database and I'm going to call it you then me back cost.
OK.
And then I'm going to add that database it's automatically going to create a new secure database for
me right here and I'll head over back to the particular sites that we are working with which is you
Demetre but cost and the main elements.
All I need to do is add this environment and put in my database name and it's automatically going to
collect that database.
OK.
So also we can set up the queue which we're going to be talking about in a second but we can also set
up SSL.
For example if you want to install encrypt which is free SSL you can select and create and it's going
to install for you Demetre.
But costs are going to pull out this one right here because we just want for this subdomain.
OK.
So I'm going to opt in a certificate and this would actually not work if you've not set up a domain.
So Mitry sets up a domain in your ocean because the ocean is the one that is managing the domains for
the server.
Ok so I'm going to activate it right there.
OK.
So it's active if I visit the app right now it gets me secure right here.
So looks like we can visit our our freely and just in a couple of seconds.
Our application is life just like that.
OK.
So in just a few seconds we're about to deploy our application.
We're able to install SSL just by one click.
We're able to connect it or get hoby poetry meaning every time we push it's automatic updates on our
site.
Just in a few seconds so this is why we're using law with fotch.
OK so we're going to continue talking about deployment in the very next video.
For now I'm going to hit pause on this video right now.
So thanks so much and see you in the very next one.