Welcome back I like us to going to a service or truly understand what fortune is doing for us behind
the scenes.
So when you quit to new sites on FOX on your server is going to send you the logging credentials for
that server.
For example it's going to tell you about the use of all sorts of metrically Cretans and for each of
you get into the server you need to use a search.
OK.
So this is a show on how to set up S-sh for the Mac OS.
You don't need to read all of this stuff.
All you need to do is run this command.
And this is simply saying generates a new S-sh key and then you can set up a passphrase if you want.
And it's good to see that to that directory is a try.
And finally all you need to do is copy it.
OK.
So this generates on these copies.
That's it.
So once you copy that key you cannot hide your faults.
And on the keys you can add a new key just like I did.
OK.
So when you copy you just need to do a control V or command V and that's going to be the key right there.
And you can give it any name.
OK.
So if you don't challenge keep doing that every time you create a news server you can head over to my
accounts and and the key is you can add the SS key right here.
Which means every time you create a new server which automatically add that to that server.
Now if you own a Windows computer what you need to do is such an awful lot show like here it's just
sets off the SS key.
So it's a rather lengthy process but all you need to do is download this Puchi application which is
going to generate an SS key for your local machine.
Once that's generated You can not copy it.
And also do exactly the same thing in your forte dashboard.
OK.
So let's head over to my costs and see what's going on inside.
So I'm going to open my terminal and I'm going to see S-sh and the fortunes of Ott's but broadcast the
column or I can actually use to save our IP address.
OK.
So I mean so as easy as that.
Once I set up this message key I can get into my server.
OK.
So let's see what's going on here unless we see that we have a list of Dubay trees and these trees actually
look at the videos on different sites that they have on the server.
If I was locked in I would then I'm going to actually be in the woods.
But then the Fauchery has permissions right in this direction right here.
OK.
So this is the art we are working with.
So I'm just going to see into you then move that back cause a comb and I'm going to glass right there
and you see inside this debate you have an exact replica of our occupation just like it is in our local
machines because we are pushing to get tall and then automatically double front simply Puli from here.
OK.
So this is how the application looks behind the scenes.
Nothing too complicated he just pours into this tree every time we deploy.
OK.
And of course this contributions for genetics and all of that good stuff going on on the server too.
But what I want to show you right now is I will told each direction.
So if I sit in a each and and that's when they say into my office and unless you discover that we have
a label does not follow.
So when you want to debunk the application or your application hasn't ever in production what you can
do is simply Nundle.
Now will that lock and the system going to print out the results or the contents of this law will that
not fall because knobbly still going to keep logging into this file.
OK.
So for example this is the latest that I have.
It says based on your log file you need that but Cazotte whatever.
OK.
So on production is simply going to tell you something went wrong.
But then when you come to your server you can actually see what that was.
OK.
So this is because I tried to visit the site without the plain meaning without my greeting in my database
migrations.
So if you want to debug the application you can actually Kongji are liable to lock fire in your production
server and then check it out.
OK.
So we're going to talk about how to set up better error handling in a future.
But for now you just need to understand how to get to your server and sometimes you might need to get
in.
So what's a fix much conflicts or to fix get problems on stuff like that.
This is how you get into your server.
OK.
So to exit the server I just need to exit.
So that's how we get into our server.
That's how it looks inside.
Pretty much exactly the same thing but now we know almost Phuoc that she's doing for us behind the scenes.
OK so I'm going to hit pause right now.
We're going to keep talking about watching the very next video.