OK guys Welcome back let's talk about something that's really important.
If we look at our website right now we still have these you know toxic stuff from my theme right there.
Burts what I want us to do in this video is actually should to better read the same stone.
I want us to integrate it into our application like setting dynamic headers so dynamic titles and descriptions
such that search engine optimization will be possible in our app and we've done that we are also going
to learn how to push new features in Java application while it's already in production.
OK so that is what we are going to be coding in this.
So first of all for us to do this we're going to be using a package.
So if you haven't installed it go ahead and install this package right here.
It's really good for setting up SU in a very simple way.
OK so once you do that the next thing is to publish the package.
So BHB Alasan vendor publish which is simply going to copy the configuration for this package into over
configuring tree and automatically this package is discovered.
So if you want to publish this one right here just going to select the number 6 and that copy that.
So if you had a lot of SEO tools but THP we have the conflagrations right here that we can set by default
so we can set the sites all by default to be broadcast.
We can set the description by default to be the best web development training ever.
OK.
And then right here canonic are all the stuff you can go ahead and suttee it however you want.
Right here for the open graph which means for Facebook we're going to set but cost and do exactly the
same thing right here for the euro or with some people a certain law right here that uses the current
trial and right here we want to change this to the Twitter handle for this Web site.
OK.
So make sense.
So we set about default configurations.
The next thing is to actually set up the settings in our controller.
So for example when we are truly about rended this home page we are going to copy the configurations
right here.
So this section I'm going to copy it and then I'm going to head over to my phone and call and right
here where we when that was completed I'm going to pass that in and I will get you use as your front
seat at the top.
And every time the speech is about we were in that we're going to set title all broadcast we're going
to set the description to maybe the best web development or churls.
And like I said all I'm going to set it you simply to create your own.
So when I said quest and I'll catch your eye and I'm going to do exactly the same thing for the can
only call you.
All right.
Here we can just replace this with screencast and the true Chando is going to be by our cost and after
we've said that we were the view.
Now the last thing we need to do is head over to our obdurately the PSP which is our layouts file and
pull out all of these massive tax rates here and would let our package do that.
So for us to let our package do that we just need to add costs as you generate right here and all of
this is in the documentation.
So once we generate that if we had about 12 a page refresh we can now see that the head is set to the
correct view page source that gives us all of the discussion that we set in our controller makes sense
right.
So in our control our what if you wanted to set something or the same thing for our show to see the
speech.
So if we want to see a particular service will just paste this in and would set the title to the series
title.
I would also set the description to the series description and I think everything can stay the same.
So lets go back refresh and visit this link and we see the title this article is set right here.
Okay.
So looks like our package is working its 10 legionary its in the title.
Of those is good stuff for us.
But one thing I want to do is keep duplicating all of these.
Its messing up our controller.
So what we're going to do is with headbutts over control of the PSP and I'm going to use CO2 right here
because remember all our controllers are using this particular controller.
OK.
So they're like extended it.
So I'm going to cut out this and things that many duplications I'm going to put the directions right
here.
So public function and I'll call this function set as you and I'll simply paste that right there.
And for now I'm going to see this function for taking the title and the description.
OK.
And when we take in the title we placed the title right here and we we take in the description we place
the description right here.
OK.
So we have this method we can use it in any of our control us wherever we want.
So right here we can just say this set as you and we need to pass in the title which is going to be
broadcast and we can pass the description which is going to be the best web development training OK
so that's done we can do exactly the same thing for the show series.
So pull out all of this and then the title is going to be the series title and the description is also
going to be the Sui's description.
OK.
So once you set that up you see that it really cleans up our controllers.
Then if I head back to this page and I refresh we see exactly the same thing.
If I visit the home page and I refresh which have exactly the same thing for viscid this one you see
the title is set so as you know it's working perfectly.
Ok so now onto the second parts of this detail.
How do you get this to production.
OK.
So that's now what I want us to talk about.
First of all our production server is deployed for Mastani.
But then look at where I'm walking.
I'm working on VELHO.
OK.
So first thing is when you walk in on a production application you never want to walk on the service
branch or the branch that is deployed to the server because you always want to be able to go back to
your changes.
For example right now when I wanted to stop the changes for the SU I automatically went out into the
developed branch and now that I'm happy with everything I've done I can now push to get help and then
make a request for my master brunch.
And automatically it's going to be deployed to my level for each server.
OK.
If I had something like maybe Travie see I've running all my test then then automatically gets up I'm
going to make sure all my test box with the CIA before I develop.
OK.
So right now I'm just going to open fotch And what does open mean.
I'm going to actually run all my tests.
OK.
So you can see after making some changes.
Looks like some of our tests are not passing.
So this is the advantage of actually working on its VELLAR branch because you can Wolbachia changes
or you can actually work on the failing tests before you merge into a monster and then push to production.
So right now I'm just going to hit pause and then I'm going to figure out why this I'm not feeling.
And then in the next video we're going to tackle it.
OK.
So thank you so much and see you then.