OK guys.
Welcome back.
So in the last video it looks like all of our tests were filling.
So it looks like we are not sending that e-mail.
And it also looks like we are not receiving the correct response when the user logs in.
OK.
So to work on this.
OK so I'm just going to copy the first name right here and I'm going to run pH unit futile So this test
with one that individually.
OK.
So we look at the error it seems rather than presuming or 200 it receives or three or two.
So I'm going to head over to that test and right here look up what we are searching we are searching
that we receive are 200.
But if we head over to our logging controller we exit that a little by saying if the request is on Ajax
then we should respond with a status of 200.
And stutters OK message.
OK but then how do we actually test if this is an AJAX because you know what controller we're just making
a Jason post request.
But Lavoe doesn't recognize this as an AJAX.
That's why test is family.
So whatever works or what test.
And I'm just going to open this up.
I thought the law will provide for us and determine if the request is the result of an AJAX call.
And what this method does is it simply returns is as simple as to request meaning maybe coming from
Valsalva stuff like that.
So I'm going to this is my thought and you are going to check out what it does.
So what it does is that it simply checks if this header is set to this value.
That's it.
So we can actually manually set up this header.
So that's what simulates an Ajax request.
So how do we set up headers in our test our head or what my logging tasks and right here the permits
are that we can actually pass.
In today's Post Jason My thought is the header that we want to set so we can set an array.
And the key for that array is going to be this because this is the key we want.
And then the value is going to be this because it's simply checking if this key is equal to this value
makes sense.
So we're going to see more of this key to this value and proceed as a header.
OK.
So that's all we're going to do.
Now let's run this test again and see if Lovewell is going to recognize it as an Ajax request.
Great.
And the test in our process.
Okay.
So all we need to do is set up the header so that we know that these two requests which amortised is
actually an Ajax request.
OK.
So let's run all the tests again and pick out the last one we just fill in and then do with it.
Okay.
So our next step is that this feeling is compelled to confirm your email to us.
So I'm just going to VCDs the registrations test.
And let's look at what is happening.
We are searching that the e-mail was sent and it's now giving us a figure.
So let's reset our registration control law and looks like we are actually sending up the e-mail right.
But let's visit this e-mail to see what's happening.
We are implementing should Q And we made these edits together at Q store application.
So it means we actually clean this Malibu and it's not sending at all.
So what we can do is we're actually going to test that it is cued rather than test in that sense because
it's no longer sense.
Right.
So I'll head over to my registar test and right here Lovelle provides us with an assert cuman thought
which can help us to test that the millibar was cute and not that it was sent.
OK.
So right now we're going to run these tests one more time and see what we get towards this particular
test.
Find me I thought I said.
Q It should be assert Kuder with a D at the end.
Let's run that again.
And now we have a successful test.
OK.
So makes sense.
So this one was failing because we changed implementation form sent into queing and logging test was
failing because we changed the implementation from the turning of a tree or two if the request was not
an AJAX.
OK so now that all tests are passing that's just one that we have a confirmation that a lot of us are
passing.
Which means this code is kind of safe to push into production.
Ok so I'm going to add everything and comments MSH that saves all day tests for confirm email and Ajax
logging.
OK.
So right now you have a choice if you're working on a team you need to push the code to the server and
then create a pool questions you must start which is going to be reviewed.
Something like that.
But then now we are working locally and we are truly one person working on these projects there's no
really need to push get top that make a request before the court is reviewed and stuff like that.
We are shocked that our branch is clean and safe.
So what we can do is simply check out my stuff and then we can merge all the changes from developed
into my.
OK.
So it successfully merged.
And right now if we want to update our server we just had to watch who the website by cure if we visit
the particular Web sites where our application is hosting is hosted the configuration automatically
is listening to pushes form to master.
So if we want to deploy our are all we need to do is see get push or region which means to get up and
with one master.
OK.
So it's pushed to the top.
Now let's look up our fortune server.
You can see automatically in new deployment has started and it's deploying the application right now.
So that's a complete set of view that we can now see that are your settings are automatically set right
here.
So look at the ASIO's settings.
OK.
So great.
Looks like an update from our core has been pushed to production.
If you check out the premier unlock it automatically you know poor form this your all that we specified
and then it also put from master and then it discovered the newly installed package because of a composite
based on those updates.
And then there was nothing to my quick.
OK.
So basically that's how you maybe set up new features in your app and then deploy it into production.
Thank you so much for watching.
And let's continue in the very next video.