OK guys let's talk about a walker remember we have already queued mail so it's not going to automatically
send but it's going to send behind the scenes.
So how do we set that up for each.
Now if I take you to our Q The PH B which is our config you just got are a lot of configurations right
here and the ones you use in production is beanstalk.
OK.
Just think of it as a walk car that really works well on Linux and it's going to actually run our queue
rather than us doing P and Q was stuff like that.
OK so we're going to change our configuration and production to make sure that uses being stalked.
OK so in the envy for what you want to do is set up the queue.
So if I take you to my dad in the fall you have a Q drive right here.
You're going to change that to your beanstalk and lovely so keep your cute life and when stalking is
going to process your q jobs behind the scenes.
OK.
So for you to set up install all you need to do is come here look at the conflagrations set or whatever
you want and you can run it as Diamante.
That's always going to be running behind the scenes.
And then you can start the walk out on the server.
That's it.
That's all we need to do.
So that it is starting to kill Walker and then we need to configure what applications you use Bernstorff
so we can leave this one for now.
But in your environment right here for production you need to change it to being stalked.
Okay.
And then finally you need to install the package for ph.
So companies are required.
This is going to install this package and it's going to automatically register page in your composer
Jason.
And when you're deploying to production it's automatically going to install that package.
OK.
So there we go right there.
So once you said that all being Vollmann to use penstock you automatically you install this and you
start your q Walker.
That's all you need to do.
If you had a million queues that are going to be processed by the rescue worker and you can even start
as many workers as you wish depending on your workload.
OK.
So that's basically all you need to do if you once you actually change just now all you need to do is
get at everything Gates comments say maybe install being stalked by H and just push to master and level
4 is going to install the newly included package in the car that adjacency if you check out the app
view the deployment log.
We can see that it installed Fahnestock right here.
OK.
So once we set up our queue drive level is automatically going to level 40 is automatically going to
take that behind the scenes.
We don't need to worry about it any more.
OK.
So thank you so much for watching and see you in the very next video.